Welcome to the night, the cars laid out for show Star shine is alright, watch the secrets unfold
There's magic in her hands Whisper what the future holds
With a rhythm
Yeah, yeah, yeah
Flow
Hearts in the balance, every card an open door
Feel the romance in every arcane world
What's up, guys? Hold on. It's Samantha.
I'm going to do something real quick. What's up?
I guess you can meet up. I'm sorry, that was kind of obnoxious.
Um, what the hell?
Let's see
Hey, Riz Friday bitches Riz are you mad at me? I'm sorry. Oh, I didn't mean to like, you know
Be in disrespectful to any country's national anthem, of course, you know
Give me you have to give me a break. I've had as I go. Hey, hey, what are you doing?
Yeah, I guess it's got McDonalds. Oh
Have you seen Lisa lately? I haven't watched her in a little bit because I told you earlier
It's kind of turned on me
Mr. I mean my cat my cats turn on me too so hi, babe
Look at the eye, your eye looks all weird.
Oh, you see the neon, you see the neon?
Are you Mr. Tricks?
Hi Mr. Tricks, you watched a little bit earlier?
Yeah, she looks, she's of course always beautiful.
Hi babe.
Joanie was here the other night, but she didn't say.
She was like, this is too much for me so, you know,
unfortunately.
I hope it would be like a cool place for her to be but
You know, I'm certainly not for everyone
Get a clear
You have to everyone. Oh
Yeah, I mean, I had some too. I think it relates to her, you know, and she's a cancer season right now
This is her sign, you know
she's also a Scorpio Scorpio moon as I send them and
That is a lot of water in the chart really a lot of water that is like the little mermaid type of like place
Well, or I don't know what are the two maybe they're both combination of both, right?
But are you guys doing good like I don't know like I had like a lot of people in earlier I had a
This is what I'll talk to you about the panels like I've been thinking a lot about it. Like it was like
You know the panels take hours, you know, it's like I like to be on for hours. I do I just think it's fine
I like to hang out. I loved doing the panels and it was getting to like where
Now it's like it just like a lot of people joining a Christie are gone. What?
But it's getting to where the panels are like kind of getting almost abusive toward me. I mean, it's like it feels like
People like just like just want to do the panel. They just want to like
Come up and talk it. It's okay. I understand. I'm panel open panels like it's cool
And it's like and then people are thinking oh, we're taking you over the show
We're taking over the show people taking over the chat. Oh, I don't know
I mean it's because all this stuff going on also like just the weird stuff then
you know, so
But if I and then it's like, you know
Just you know, we're gonna slow down a little bit some people are bad thing banding me and stuff
You know, there's other people, you know, just like I don't I there's a lot going on, right?
so
but I
Think I figured out a way that I can keep doing them and then my speakers crackling
I think that way I can keep doing them.
Testing, testing, okay, is that better?
Okay, I'm sorry, Riz, yeah, okay,
but I think I figured out a way that everyone can be happy.
No, people want to be on panel.
I want to have this be a good show and stuff like that,
so I think I have to go that way,
but maybe we'll see if it works or not.
Hey, Ms. Liz, how are you?
Hi, everybody, but I want to thank the chat.
Of course, it will be, I'll just tell you right now,
it will be, I have to start having a more limited panel
I really want to concentrate on doing readings for people and I really bring back to Tarot and it's like I turn into this drama thing and then it's like now this drama is taking over and it's like
You know, it's like
There's just like a lot of stuff being said about a lot of people and it's like, you know, and I was I defended like all these people
Like I always had like everybody on the show. I never had a problem with the people like I never was judging
Let me see these same people that I did that to seem very judgmental and like stuff toward you know for me
So I don't know kind of right. You haven't been here all day. Hey, Miss Liz. Well, good to see you
So I don't know. I think there's homophobia. There's like
There's just people that are just troll communities and stuff. You had a copy date. How is it good?
Like glasses back on of course, I just I keep losing out here. They're on the floor
So yeah, so it's like I think I like you know, I really have the panel for like people that are
Wanted to have a reading done on the panel while they're on the panel to and talk
Or, you know, it's like something important to talk about.
I'm not just gonna come and say,
hey, what's up?
Anybody come up and then it's like, you know,
just free for all.
I mean, some days, maybe I'll do that once a day.
I'll do it once a day, I'll just do free,
like all three panels, I'll just do it all day.
Like, right?
Oh, you had an unexpected admirer, nice.
That's awesome.
Yeah, love is in the air, little summer date.
Yeah, but do you guys get it like?
I really want it to be fun for everybody. It's like it's not fun for me
It's like you know, and it's not like if it's just people are not into it
But I think people are still into it
But it's like it's that it's like not fun for me, but it's fun for them kind of thing and it's like
I have to make sure it gets back fun for like everybody. All right
Some things some days were better than others, right? I know it's like stuff
There's astrological stuff going on too. It's like different things will pop up at different times
I know it's every summer like everything gets starts getting heated and it's like it starts getting all this kind of
There's a lot of like weird energy. It's like really
It's like this is fun, you know the summer is like the sun is like the most powerful and so it's like, you know out in full force
Kind of right and so it's like
Give you the break
Okay, you can't have the Sun out all the time. So the moon is very nice, but the moon still has the light of the Sun on it, right?
It would be like Las Vegas Casino 24 hours, a few of the Sun out 24 hours a day, right?
Think about how nice it is to have the duality of like the dark and the light.
We had some Mickey D's tonight
Mickey D's I wasn't very good. I mean, it's like the fries were kind of already already not good when I got them
Stop and I'll show you the report on the heat and some of the
USA. Yeah, it's like it gets crazy out here. It's just that
But it's not really bad in California. It's been like you know, California
You people usually say oh California has like the hot weather, but it's been pretty pretty just moderate out here
Too hot and not too cold
Through the sake you take your rent. Oh, I
Am busy to explain why well, it's gotty. I told I don't know who took it gotty. There's there's there's ghosts in the machine
I think you know
It was just it was random. I must have like accidentally done it and I don't have my phone like right here
I mean is I have to
Yeah, I still love him and got he it's a lot more fun without the wrench because now you can see what the fuck you want now
You don't have to be like oh no
Don't get me a hotter. I know but then that's what
Summer and then what happened in the fall you can't sleep. Well join the club
You know Goddy, I do I love you and it's like I
Want I
Want you I want you, you know, it's a show
Yeah, you got tough love. Hey, I got you
Me you got tough. I think you're tough
Maybe we're both a little good. Let's have tough love. I don't know. I mean, no, I don't know
I just want to give love. I was thinking like I had like this a person. I'm so over hate like there's stuff
It's like I just think I've never like I've never enjoyed hate. It's the only thing I hate is hate
It never this is like never like
Yeah, I never want to harm anybody. I never wanted to hate anybody
It's like I was like even like when sending magic I was like, please if I think if I have any power
I think please do not let it be used for harm. Please don't anything bad
It's like even if I get I hate someone someday don't let don't let me ever like have the ability to curse
Like I'll let me always have like just the ability to bless, you know
Thank You miss Liz. Yeah, you're sweet. You're nice. It's great having you on the on the on the show and stuff
Yeah, I love I love the Australian accent too, you know
But people were saying why am I still you said the best they can do the American accent Americans can't really do an Australian
It's pretty true
Wait, what are you saying Joe? I look like Sid the sloth. Is that like a good thing?
You're the great-looking guy or no
I know I'm probably, I just can't see anymore.
This is what I have to do if I have to look at it.
I seriously like looking at the text on this screen.
It's like seriously, it's like one centimeter like tall.
It's like the tiniest little text you've ever seen.
I need a magnifying glass to read this thing.
Oh, thank you Liz.
Thank you.
And like Spunky's so cool.
Look at Spunky got me.
I don't know if you guys see that.
I mean, it's like a little bit bright
so you might not be able to see it,
but it's like the, it's an alien, so you don't want to see it.
And it's holding a cat.
It's an amazing medium neon that trippy
Kind of a little bit more to do it's pretty cool. It's pink the pink cat and the alien is the green
Not wonderful
Nice you got me some capitals and so the kiddies
Yeah, yeah, I got treats today. So
Very grateful. Thank you spunky and I'm just grateful to everybody that is you know, like a lot of people of
Really like the wish list or you know, you know purchase readings and help me other ways
And so I want to thank everybody. Yeah, it's so cool and some bulls and there's like, let's see Lola's up here sleeping
Well, are you sleeping up there?
Comfortable
Where's I don't see tricks but tricks with this here. Oh, is he over there? I don't know everyone
It's strippy, huh? It's like I can stick as they come
It was a little hard to see because the light is so bright, you know, and I know people were having trouble earlier
but I'll take a picture of it on the
Amazon store. I just had seen it and I was like, whoa, I like I just like it saw through the night and I was like, whoa
I love that and then
Yeah, she's
so kind
Something different. Hey, what's up? So here look here's what the
Hi, Yvonne, nice to see you.
Here's the,
let's see, here's this list.
This is it.
That better, see, I don't look like it.
Good morning, Yvonne.
You're good, okay.
So, yeah, I want to talk about that's my ideas I have but
That's a panel. I don't know if 15 people here
Let me see if I have
Let me see. Hold on
Okay, I did the first song would take a proposal. I don't know. You have to tell me what you think about it and then I
Don't know if it will come off. Well, you know, I just try things right here we go
Okay, you see that okay here we go
Listen to the song
We just put another banner
I haven't heard this either. I just made it. Okay. Hold on. Let me see. Yeah, I can do that
Okay
See how it goes
Oh, that's not gonna work. Okay. Oh
Yeah, so I did you know, I don't know if you saw the saw the the avatar
This will work
Okay
I like the stage start the show Mike open wide
Truth in my voice can't fake this prize
It cuts a little more smiles on the outside battles at the core
They say it's just talk but I feel the flame homophobia laced in every name
I'm the space I'm the peace I'm the soul they see
They were mad.
Okay, no, I'm not talking to everybody, $10, right?
Well, hold on, what I'm saying is I might like start,
wanting to like, you know, have the panel sponsored
in like for, you know, maybe like $10 for a few hours.
So it's one person could sponsor it, you know?
Then, well, that's just for, you know, for now.
I'll see, there couldn't be more in the future or less, you know?
It's kind of a cute song
It just it does make up a lot of stuff, you know, I didn't say very much to it, so
Yeah, it's already diamond I saw 30 diamonds tonight. She's very
She says she's been like sober for a few weeks and she won't pour mom again
So maybe I'll let her back on the show. We'll see. I don't know
There you go.
Oh, look at the cat.
Oh, oh, shit.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Got to take off the banner.
Oh, baby.
There's six right there six here behind me
Buddy
Yeah, it's quiet. You know, I saw like you know talk your ish panel. It looks like there was a bunch of people over there
there's like, you know Alexander I saw and
Summer Christine and I saw Vinny pods and pans and
some other people
You'll be Jimmy's having a geek off. Well, I think this is the place. Hey, what's that? Is that the real Jim Nick?
Yeah, real Jim Nick hooray Jim Nick
There's just been a there's been a fake Jim Nick in the stream at bad old wheels around. I don't know
I just don't know wheels around so I can't really like I don't dislike him because I don't know him. Hey, Paige
How are you sweet? I don't know who it's his will to rank guy, right? And so
No
Yeah, I don't know if you saw it. Yes, like a look at spunky got me
If you can't see it, oh, it's brightness adjustable hold on I didn't notice
They're like I'm sure I'm sure it's like because it's like it's like it's like so bright. It's like it's like blinding
Hold on turn it down
You see as a big like nice. Oh has a nice long cord too. Oh here does have a little thing here
Oh
That's better, hold on. Oh
That better there we go
Hey, come in peace
He's doing
Oh, isn't that cool?
It's spectacular, isn't it?
Isn't that cool?
Yeah, so I don't know him well enough.
I'd like to roast him. He was kind of saying stuff about God.
He sounded like, I don't know, he was saying some woman's voice over and over.
Yeah, it's actually cool if you also got me these cat bowls too. Um, he's like there's like on a little on a little level on a level
So, you know, it's like a more probably more comfortable for the cat to eat like a hey, baby
Hi
Ah
Oh, I thought you got you thought that was like your I thought God he was putting like a
One of the avatars but because the avatars come up for me like when people type type the avatar
It comes up for me. It's just what's like the word it is. I can only on that little screen is the avatar
This is pretty cool, I can't say
The texture
Where is it?
Oh, here it is.
And this is wallpaper creator, yeah.
I mean, I said Joker and then I made it
to her the Jack of Spades, but.
Phil
This is pretty dangerous, huh?
That's like the
Yeah, I'm doing okay. I'm doing okay. Hey, Jane. How are you? Good morning?
Yeah, it's got some McDonald's again. Yeah, you like these is the karma for karma for a picino the McDonald's
No, I got it. I don't have I don't know I you know I get I don't know what happens
I was just in his those in the chat and whatever you know what happened in the chat I
Just was like I just saw he was like talking to somebody and he had the breath
He wasn't paying attention. Yeah, wait a minute grab it and I was gonna give back. I was just kidding
It's because he likes to tease me all the time. So I thought I'd like to make him sweat a little bit
But it's cool. Hey guys so earlier tonight. I had my show earlier has six hundred and forty view
Okay, isn't that great right six hundred forty views amazing, right?
Despite rendia six hundred and forty views. So that's oh
I just built
Okay, so that's great, but it gets how many lights they have and six hundred and forty people
You know, do you think if six hundred forty people think someone like maybe
20% of something would like to push like on the way in how many people like that like this too whoa
I don't know if you are unlikely. I mean it's like 640. That's like 1224 321. It's like
It's like such a small percentage. I can't even fathom. Hold on one second
So please yeah, it's it's basically two. It's like I might as well have two likes. I mean
The only other time I had such little likes was that Mr.. Big Pipes was on and like some guy kept coming on saying
He was taking away like 30 likes because mr.. Big Pipes was on so okay, so I don't know. Okay, Gotti
Here, I'm just kidding, okay
You know, I like you too Liz
And shouldn't I call on charisma. Are you nice person?
Here don't say never did nothing for you
Okay
Thank you guys. I hope I want to respect you
I'm gonna show respect to I want to respect everybody, but yeah, I want to make sure
You feel respected and if I sometimes I joke around you know, I know you too. So that's no uh,
No offense or anything
I'm not a great guy. I'm a great guy. No, like I said, I people are like, you know
We have good and bad qualities, right?
You can't even stream because YouTube has reported. Oh, oh my gosh
Sorry, Jim Nick. That's crazy
The Wizard of Oz when they go from black and white to color. Yeah
Right
Turns into Oz but it's kind of like or just kind of kind of down the rabbit hole too
But it's like I've already been down the rabbit hole two times and it's like boring
And that's not what you know about with you guys, but yeah
I don't know if I can explain that correctly, but yeah, I've been to this rabbit hole before
Yeah, well, maybe I know that you make us crazy that you know by what they reported you
I think Howard they can't you like show you through your idea or something and say hey like I'm an adult
I just look like a good 14 years old or something
I remember that on that with the guy was talking about that that shows he has a predator last night
Saints where a seeker was over he was like
As I remember that at the other things this like lesbian woman. She's like 30 play in her 30s
She plays like this. Well, you're boy. Hey, come on. I made cookies. It's so funny
We'll do rant too. Yeah, there you go. Okay, so how is it? I don't know why it's like guy
He like why what's the beef with you? Like how does he even know you and like I don't know
He just came in here like I promote and it's like oh, he's chasing you around much like how do you find you here?
And so I just don't know. Oh, God is over it. Thank you. So like just like
You're just like just knowing where you are
I don't have everyone finds you
It's like I don't know I have to do I have to do I have to do a AI about
No, it'll be it'll be a secret all the time. I'm gonna do a song of it. It's funny open panel
I think I'm gonna I'm gonna open the panel at $10
Or else I probably I might not do it
I'm not I'm getting exhausted. They just being like
Look at having these hours and hours of panels where I can barely participate sometimes because everyone's just like so loud and then it's like
I don't know. It's like I need to I need to start uh
So if you guys want to you want to chip in with somebody? I don't know. It's 10 bucks. So it's like if there's like, you know
Anybody I don't know
I just uh, no it's like
Like I
I don't know, it's not, and it's not, it's not,
all it is is like, I want people to say whatever they want
and stuff like that.
And it's like, and I know I'm like all on top of people,
I think if I, if they paid the person,
although they'll like, you know, be more careful
with what they say and they'll appreciate,
appreciate like being on it.
And second of all, it's just like a way to, you know,
I like to, I like to read and stuff like that.
And you know, it's like sometimes people are kind of
demanding of the panels.
If I open it, okay, 10 bucks. Okay, I'll open it for like I'll open it for these things in two or three hours
You know, I mean, I don't know for as long as the rest of the night. I'm on it. I mean, do you promise?
Promise promise make a promise that they got as a man. I'll open it up
Well, I'm gonna do this
And it's like people can like, you know, come on and like go in as you gather and see, like if they want to be on the panel too, like, you know, can you say, oh, there's a few people. And so maybe I'll, you know, depending on the demand, you know, I've got a promise. Okay.
Okay, hold on.
Why not?
You're welcome.
So, I do have an open panel sign too.
Oh yeah, it might go up, so $10 is a good deal.
I would say get it on that wall, it's just $10,
because I think people will have fun,
like obviously they have some stuff to say,
and sometimes they have stuff to say to me,
they can say it to me, they can say whatever they want to say,
and they can say whatever, you know.
But uh, you know, we know I'll I'll be here like hosting it and I'll be it'll be good and like I
Think it will I think it's fair
And it doesn't work then I'll just you know, I'll just not have a panel
It's it's a $10 it's a $10 to open the panel and that's like so it's so it's so you guys can pull it in together
Or it's like you can it's not per person
So it's like I'll open it for anybody for the next you know
It'll be so it'll be like one person will be like the hero hero opening it or it's like they can go in together
Like we'll do or if there's a few people want to come on they can say oh we'll do like
Yeah, I'm not trying to make it too complicated. The cash app will be the easiest way cash up addresses on
the
So on form bombs, then, I mean, I guarantee, for the first time I bite the panel, I say,
The bargain yeah, I think I think it's a bargain and you know what that's the thing about freedom in the country
We can begin you know
We can decide to charge and we can decide if we want to pay for that's like that's what a commerce is about and so
It's you know, but I really if I'm gonna sit here because I've been I've been
Sometimes I sit down for like it's like four hours and I say I don't even get to talk or like you know
I don't feel like I'm part of the car like you know
I know sometimes I leave and stuff like that, but sometimes I feel like I either like to see the people talk or it's like
I don't feel like I could contribute to the conversation in a good way
Or I just like it and followed by one of the guests and so it's like if I like and like, you know
So if if uh, yeah, so I will give the person like, you know
I will restart it again, you know, I promise to restart it, you know, it's like, it'll be fair, it'll be fair
It'll, you know, so that I'm just doing
So let's start out like that
Let's see how that goes
Yeah, and it's like and yeah, and then they'll be really discouraged from poor moment, okay
Sorry. Hey, what's up, dude? How are you? What's up?
How's the panel going?
It's a here you know, thank you for being the first thing you're responsible in the panel for tonight and that goes
You know the next two to three hours and so yeah, thank you very much. Appreciate it. Thank you
You know, I think you're worried that you're gonna
You know
First we'll go
But don't break you
Yeah, yeah, we're yeah, we're saying, you know, we're trying not to break to you guys. Yeah, and I've you know
You know, basically the rules, you know, they'll take the panel rules, right?
Okay
Yeah, and
Well, nothing much did you like you see this this is you see that you saw my like, uh, but it's funky on me look
I feel cool is oh
Beautiful
Yeah, that's so cool. Oh beautiful
Yeah
Very cool and
Yeah, you'll fall asleep now. Yeah, three of the ghosts. Yeah, but other people are welcome on the panel now, too
You know it's like it goes kind of response. Yeah, do you want me to leave? Yes, you guys are welcome to join. I can leave
No, no, no, no, no, no, it's you if we want you here, too. Hey
guy you know it's like and I appreciate you you're uh thank you for like you know standing by me
you know we've had some good times yes you know up the downs on the show right
different at you multiple times Tony has different you're more by the way my name's
Okay, well, that's interesting by the way, just call me Tony from now on. Okay. Yeah, are you really are you serious?
Hold on. Are you really serious? Because you know, it's true. All right. Are you?
Are you come on come on, that'd be so funny. Oh my gosh, that would be funny, but no, I hate this shit. I
am a crucible ghost
You are okay. Okay. That would be funny. That would be funny though. No, you're funny. I would enjoy that
Well, you are I stands for thank you. Hey, well, it's oh, yeah
And I want to say thank you for sponsoring the panel for the next couple hours. And so, uh, thank you. Thank you
You're a cool dude
Yeah, so thank you. Oh, come on. Here's the gaudy. Come on, please
Come on
I mean, I was a little joint. Yeah, you gotta think about it. People can come out. I know. Yeah, it's like yeah
But this is respect that I ghost, you know ghost ghost sponsored the panel tonight, right? So
Wait, come on. Even if you suspect in me, let him join the panel
Okay, I'm fine with it
Yeah, I do have the right I do have the right also to like still like you know take people on out the panels
I please but I will be like
Letting you like you know
Yeah, okay, you're good. You're good. Thank you so much. I appreciate that. I love I love that
You know some people would be like, oh, yeah, you're like, you know, just you understand. Okay, so I like that
Yeah, I'm gonna see you having fun, brother
Cool. Do you want one? I'm not gonna ask you for no cards. Well, I'm gonna ask you for one
I want it. I want an animal card. Okay, you want an animal card? Okay?
I got them and it better be a fucking tiger if not
Or a beaver, which is weird. I know
As page as page in the chat, I think so
I want to I want an animal card from page
from her to okay
Okay, I'll take both. Yeah, that's
Yeah, it's like, you know, we're both
Sure, though, I don't think she is
One animal cards for you animal card. Okay. Okay. I'm doing the animal part right now. I got it
It's talk your ish God and talk your ish
Okay
Do me do do me good brother
I'm suffering is it land? Well, tell me tell me if it's like land or in
Water
You got the hawk you got the hawk hold on. Oh
Well, that's fucking land then
Hock is a good second card though. Yeah, Hock it says. Oh, it says he says healing
Vision reverse spirituality says there are many species of Hock each with his own legends and associated
The birds have symbolized healing freedom vision and rebirth
Uh-huh in Egyptian mythology ice is the goddess of abundance and fertility assumes the shape of a hawk
She gives birth to her son Horace who then dies in his reform
She's also becomes a hawk to be joined her husband Osiris in the underworld
Native Americans associate the hawk with potent magic and use its feathers of healing rituals and in ceremonies to bring rain
Yeah, where the fuck is paid she's not here
I don't see her here. No, can you pick your nose in here? Sure. Oh, that's unfortunate. Thank you for that reading though
Yeah, oh, no problem. I wanted to Leo. I I did want the lion, but I'll take the hog
Okay, yeah, I mean Leo's the lion's always a good great car too
But you know other than I love all the cat cars like Panther and stuff Jaguar
Yeah, I think you know for birdie pretty pretty good bird
The greatest thing I've heard is like Leo like your life like your hard-headed which I am or your argument of which I am
Yeah, oh, yeah
Yeah, big ego and they have that you know because they're ruled by the Sun right the Sun is all like by identity and the ego
Right and also they'd love to be like the center of attention
There's a lot out there brother. You'd have to be like the top person in the relationship and
Yeah
And they got a lot of fire
Calibri lion. Yeah, it could be you know, the male lion is kind of like the more or cowardly
So late did you have a panel earlier?
Mm-hmm. I did I did and then I like didn't have my dinner and then I was like in a bad mood
Yeah, I think it I think it for mom
I think it for mom once earlier, but that was not not not the very last show it was by the same person
You know he formed on me. Oh, yeah, I can and so
Uh, okay, let's have a good family tonight. Let's run it. Yeah, let's run it. Yeah, let's do it. Thank you for sponsoring again, and
I don't think I think goes, you know and
Appreciate it
Uh, yeah. So, um, yeah. So, but I was going to say that the female, the female lion is the hunter, the hunter, right?
And the male lion kind of fight with each other sometimes.
What? No, hunt trists. Hunt trists.
Hunt trists. Hunt trists. Yes. The hunt trists. Yes. The female lion.
Like, the female lion.
Does she not get, does she not get the fucking food for the male lion?
Right. That's correct. That's what I'm saying. She's the hunt.
But the male lion, what does he do? He'll come up and hook up all those cubs, which is horrible, hook up all those cubs.
Oh, no. He's the leader of the pack, correct? Yeah, but he does do that. They do?
That's terrible. But you know what? Let me see. I want to see.
Wow, she looks like a lion, yeah.
Oh, that's pretty brutal. Yeah, I know the cat, but even Catholic, I don't know how cats are.
It is brutal. It's fucking horrible.
They sometimes eat, um, they're, they eat, so the baby, if the baby dies, they'll eat the baby.
Oh, it's really disgusting, but I've heard of that. Okay, but it's never happened to me.
Yeah
I was gonna say
Okay, I guess I guess I want to see a page. I want to talk to Paige. I don't know if she's in there or not
Paige wasn't the cat earlier, but she she is not a cat at the moment
I don't know where she is. I don't pay the page. You know, she's not paging. She's not doing her page stuff
She's uh, or she's you know
Round she's out some other cat or something but
You know he's a good friend of the show. Yeah, I like a great friend of the show here tonight
Oh my gosh, we've been on such a journey guys, and it's in a journey and me saying sure need I don't know
Not the best thing okay, there's not even a song called amazing journeys. I just think it made that up. It was not very good
I'm sorry, but
I'll make an AI song called amazing sure these will be great
Okay, let me see you
Well, what'd you guys do? Yeah, what is this? Goddy? Who's that?
What's going on? What's really supposed to? Goddy joined the panel
No, I'm seeing why he wouldn't join the panel Goddy you're always here brother
Oh my gosh, I've got a nice amount left in that.
Babe, so you use the chat GPT ever, Ghost?
Sometimes, really.
Yeah, you do?
Okay, do you know it has a memory now?
Yeah, it's dangerous.
It's dangerous. No, it's not dangerous. Why is it dangerous? It has a memory. So it's able to like
It's gonna be dangerous, bro. It's self-learning
That's gonna be dangerous. It's not learning though because it's just like basically
It's self-learning. This is what's doing
You think it does that? I don't think it's like it has a memory
But it all it does is retain it recognize the information that we able to save it retain it and just remember and reference it
You know, it's just like so it's not that dangerous, right mark my words. It's gonna be dangerous
Wow, well, okay. I mean, it's like, you know, we know AI might be dangerous, but I just don't know if
You've asked for a dad that shit. I'm turning on something. It's gonna be dangerous
You think so I don't
You think I said why why do you think what do you think it's gonna happen like it's gonna like nose too much or something
What is it like the most dangerous thing was that would tell people how to like make crack and stuff like that, right?
And like before they like I'm probably told it not to like talk about certain things. So
Okay, good goes I appreciate if you'd like, you know something like please keep your word. Okay. Thank you
Yeah, we'll see.
But the panel is open, but yeah, I was gonna read some more some of these, you know, I have these great books
Maybe you're gonna look at the hg tutor another one of his books and read some of that
It's uh, he's gonna have me some great books one was called extra system. That's all you're going to bed
We'll listen to me going back. Good night. Goddy. You have a great night. Sleep well friends
Don't let the bed bugs bite
Okay
Quite a show, Gaudi, quite a show, okay, so I think I might want to go through this hypnotic
deprogramming, you can deprogram addictions and stuff, I want to maybe like go read that,
go through that book sometime, but we're looking at another one right now. I think we should look at...
Okay, good night, Gotti
Okay, how about this one's called escape
Okay, so this is called triangulation. Okay, so this will explain triangulation. Do you ever heard of it? It says triangulation.
So triangulation is a common device that we that he's a he's a narcissist
And so he writes this from a point of view of a narcissist because he's a narcissist
But he is trying to like share other people
How he thinks, right?
So your triangulation is a common device
that we utilize when we are seeking to control you
in order to obtain that, our supply of fuel.
With triangulation, we will involve a third element
into our relationship in order to cause a number of things.
Who or what might this third element be?
A member of your family or my family?
Your friend or mine?
Colleagues, ex-partners, a particular favorite of mine?
institutions, strangers, inanimate objects, cars, and mobile phones are common amongst my kind, it says.
By triangulating, we confuse you, make you feel anxious and unappreciated. In some instances,
we use this third element when it is personal, it's harassing, it convinces you to do our bidding.
You often fall for this and you're not seeing that we are utilizing a third party to achieve our aims.
It might surprise you that someone else will be so susceptible to our instruction
to meet out abusive behavior to someone else.
we are able to achieve this because of our innate superiority.
Consider this, how many times have you done something because someone in a
position of authority has asked or told you to do it?
Most people have been programmed to obey authority figures all throughout their
lives. It started with their parents, the teachers,
lecturers, and then the boss. You obey counsel officials, police officers,
and doctors. It follows therefore by acting with an
Arab authority, we are able to tap into this subconscious
add a layer of our infamous charm and perhaps some other kind of incentive that works for
the individual and they will soon do exactly as we seek. You may be wise to our behaviors,
but not see them coming through someone else. If possible, we will use one of our lieutenants
to advance our aims through this triangulation.
In a different method of triangulation, we set you against someone or something and you end up applying your energies trying to defeat the third element rather than actually tackling our behavior.
We often do this where we know someone else is romantically interested in us, as well as you, the second person of course being have recently been subjected to a campaign of love bombing.
We also do this with family members. We will make one of you the scapegoat and the other the golden child.
Now I do not have children but I know that my kind regularly utilizes tactic by putting one sibling
against the other. The narcissist will remain at the center controlling the flow of information
and ensuring that the siblings are kept separate from one another and rarely communicate so they
do not work out what is being done. One of our types who is a parent wants to keep you isolated
and thus they succeed in operating a policy of divide and conquer. By remaining as the sole
They also receive two supply lines of fuel.
They will aim to get a wedge between you and your sibling
and aim to have you compete with one another for affection and attention.
One of our sweetest most potent forms of fuel is when we know that two people are fighting over us
He's trying to outdo the other in order to obtain our approval and appreciation
You may be surprised just how often people fall for this
Of course
It's just all linked to the promise of return to the golden period and since you are so desperate to achieve this
You'll try to defeat anyone or anything that might prevent you from returning there
I recruit colleagues, neighbors, family members, or people involved in institutions to use
them to manipulate you.
I will use them as pseudo-rescuers who think you are able to turn to for help.
The reality is they're feeding back to me what is being said.
They're acting out of what I plan for you and perpetuate my abuse of you.
The first important part of triangulation is to realize that it is happening.
Once you gain this awareness, you must keep in mind the following.
Just because I'm saying it about you does not mean that it's true. Do not begin to believe my lies and propaganda
This is often different when you are at low ebb, but you must adopt a stance recruit test-prested allies to provide you with assistance and strength
Do not react in an emotional fashion if I or someone else tells you something that you were not prepared for.
It is a central theme and triangulation that lies will be told about you with a view to those lies returning to you, usually from third party.
We want you to erupt into anger or tears on hearing these comments.
Remove the energy from them by remaining calm.
Adopt a healthy cynicism to anything I or the third element may say be aware that I will operate several triangles involving you
Once you have uncovered one bear in mind there are likely to be others
Okay, verify comments where you can so you do not make the mistake of attacking or just
believing someone who is genuine.
This will also help you to read out some of our adverse comments.
Your reactions to triangulation are obvious to me.
One, you will strike out at me, recognizing what I am doing by having someone else carry
out my abuse of you and I'm pitting you against a third element.
This striking out will not bother me in the slightest.
It will give me a reaction.
2. You will try and persuade the third element of the triangle that my behavior is the problem
and not you. This reaction on your part also gives me fuel. It is also doomed to failure.
The third element is either possessive their own vested interest in wanting me and therefore
regard you as a competition, brainwashed by me so that your pleas will fall on deaf ears
You do not have to any control over the person you need to you do not have any control over this other person
You need to realize this one you will submit
to the abuser behavior even further as you become convinced that you are at fault.
This may seem unrealistic when viewed dispassionately, but believe me,
I have seen it happen within the dynamic with an exhausted, confused, or shattered victim,
or you depart the triangle. In defeating my behavior, you must achieve the fourth item.
You have nothing to gain by remaining in this triangle. Identify that you are in such a triangle.
Thank you. Hi. How are you? Are you full? Are you full? Yeah. Yeah. I have one more cheeseburger here.
Oh, I didn't get my dinner, brother. Yeah, that's cool. You like it? Okay. Yeah. Enjoy. Yeah, I do.
Yeah, Mr. Gotti was right. I mean, oh yeah, you should eat something. Don't, don't. Yeah.
Yeah, it is poos life, right? We want to eat the good food suit. It's funny. We eat a lot of like
It's Friday
Like this look give me look look freaky Friday
Yeah, freaky Friday
Yeah, I like that black cat. I don't know. I think it's kind of a black cat the best here. Yeah
Oh
There we go. Yeah
Do you hear my house is reading a book and just enjoying the night another beer and that are my coffee
It's already it's already
Coffee Wow
It's already it's already 5 p.m. And I will go off in a few minutes later
Enjoy your Friday. Yeah. Thank you. I appreciate you. I love you
Like a friend not not a weird way not
Okay, I'm continuing out
So it says, the only power you have in this dynamic is over yourself.
You cannot control what I do since I do not operate in the same world of logic as you.
There is no appeal to our better nature since we do not have one.
We cannot and will not appreciate your point of view since we do not have a capacity, capability
for empathy.
You are unable to influence the third element for the reasons outlined above.
You may feel empowered by telling the other two elements that you know what is happening
and you are not engaging with it anymore.
with triangulation is to refuse to engage it any longer.
This cut, that is the only response
that will work in escaping this form of manipulation.
Okay, there's no contact.
Oh shit, one percent, okay.
Okay, is this the end of the book?
Oh, it's almost over.
Okay, so that was that book.
Yeah, isn't it quick?
That was all I wanted to read in that book.
Okay. Okay, so let me see. It says intimidation. It says, the purpose of intimidation is to
I will do this, I will also do this and to try to confuse you by using subtle threats
of intimidation which have you wondering whether they are real or not and whether they will
actually be acted on.
This is done on purpose as you are then worried by them but also concerned not to cause a
fuss and involve other people for fear of being seen as overreacting.
Remember, I will of course suggest to third parties that you are imagining things and
touch with the ghosts of the crazy.
Intimidation is the little brother to anger in terms of exerting a method of control.
In order to deal with intimidation, remember that you are not overreacting nor are you imagining things.
I want you to believe that to be the case in order for my manipulation to have its effect on you.
If you perceive I am intimidating you, then I am.
You should record the act, making a brief note in order to use at a later date for the purpose of evidence should you need to.
Convince others of my intimidating conduct.
One, I might have got in first with other people,
but you're just diarized, and recent record will trump my oral
recollection.
And two, you may need it as supporting evidence
if it is necessary for you to escalate matters
using formal means through the courts to protect yourself,
or, for example, reporting the behavior to superior
in a work context.
Do you not make mistake of showing me this documentary record and helping
approving that I have been doing what you say I have been doing so that I may
recognize that and that I might change? This is not going to happen.
All that you have done is show me the evidence that I will then destroy and it will aggravate
me resulting in the worsening of my behavior towards you.
Keep the record somewhere away from home.
Work is useful or a trusted friend or relative.
Make sure you're updated.
Do not be tempted to shy away from recording every act.
They soon mount up and will prove very helpful.
You may think others will regard it as trivial, but does it feel trivial to you to be intimidated?
There's no reason for doing it while we're touching on documenting behavior
You carry a camera and video camera with you more or less all the time by virtue of your mobile phone
You just record my behavior and send the
Food or footage to an email account
You know I cannot access and from then send another email account
I may access your phone see where the first email has been sent to you should document and record throughout
There's never anything to be gained by showing this material to me as I will try to deny it even though it speaks for itself
Suggest you have obtained it out of context or even doctored it
I will not acknowledge the reality of what it shows, as it does not record with my reality.
You will need these documented examples to remind yourself what you are escaping from,
that you are not going mad when I gaslight you ultimately in the support of more formal sanctions.
You may need to seek out and should the need arise. For the sake of brevity, I shall not
mention this with each technique, but always ensure you have a record of what has happened.
You need to remove yourself from the scope of the intimidating conduct.
So leave the room at the building where it is taking place. I'm unlikely to escalate the
convict when you leave as initially you were wrong foot me and I'll be left wondering why you
have done this rather than stay and challenge me like you usually do.
We are actually predictable creatures and we expect people to be similar.
Often you act in the same fashion because our behavior has been designed to achieve
this and you have been conditioned to act in this way.
By breaking the repetition of your behavior, it will leave the wrong footed and gives you
an advantage.
do not regard the intimidation as minor. It is not. In fact, it is a form of insidious control.
By not reacting to it, either by complying or challenging, you are denying me a reaction,
therefore I will soon stop. I may shift to other techniques, see below how to nullify them.
But by denying me any kind of reaction, I will not waste any further energy on trying to intimidate
you on the occasion. Ultimately, or unfortunately for you, I am not very good at learning lessons
but you know how to deal with it. Call me, leave the situation to sense yourself from it.
This immediately stops you having to be subjected to it so you feel better.
The lack of reaction from your nullifies this potency so I will stop.
You can make a note as part of your greater design for extricating yourself from me
or managing my behavior. If every time I try to intimidate you you respond in this fashion
And then we get into, let's see, let's skip ahead.
Gaslighting, gaslighting says,
gaslighting is a particularly insidious method
of controlling you.
I'll present to you a completely convincing front
whereby I can possibly not be wrong,
even though your perception of the situation
suggests that I am.
I behave with an overwhelming sense of conviction
so that you will question yourself and your own judgment.
The key with addressing gaslighting
is to recognize that it's happening at the earliest juncture
and to avoid its terrible impacts from gaining a hold.
Once it has, no matter how hard you try,
you will struggle to imprint your reality on the situation
and will invariably acquiesce to what I am saying
as being the truth of the situation,
even though it's a fabrication.
I'm not going to accept your version of events, your recall or your recollection.
I am convinced that I am right and that is why I am engaging in gaslighting.
If you try to convince me to the contrary, you are giving me attention and engaging in
my warped creation.
It will often please me to see you trying to challenge me as this is giving me attention.
I know you will not succeed and all you are doing is beating me and exhausting and frustrating
yourself.
Instead, reinforce the fact that you are correct.
If you actually get to the habit of recording certain key events and decisions, you may
be doing this to counter intimidation, then you have a written record.
Again, do not produce this to me in order to try to convince me that you are right because,
look, here it is written down.
I will just accuse you of having written it down in that instance, or if you did earlier,
you'd misremembered.
Use the recording to reinforce your own mind that you are correct and preserve your correct
so you do not start to slide back in the false reality I've created.
I'm especially skilled at manipulating arguments and running rings around you in an argument.
Keep to the forefront of your mind because I'm doing this does not because I'm doing this does
not mean I my arguments are valid. I will try and blind you into submission with dazzling but
ultimately ill-conceived arguments. You must not think I am right just because I appear to be
Do not be afraid to rely on your supporters to validate your position.
I will denigrate them as well and suggest that they are not to be relied on.
You do not need to tell me that they support you as I will not accept this.
You should use this to reinforce your own position and utilize it as security.
It will also assist your frame of mind to be able to share what is happening to you.
Do not blame yourself for the way I'm behaving.
Do not think you can fix it.
That is impossible and you will only be exposing yourself to my machinations again if you do.
Focus on sensible and practical thoughts about you. I want you to see the world that I created
You must fight against that and to do that you need to keep yourself firmly in the real world
If you allow yourself to think about my behavior, you will get sucked back into my false reality
Okay, everybody here, why is everyone gone? What happened?
There's 17 people here know what it's talking, okay?
It says, love bombing.
My massive attention overloads,
charm offensive, verbal seduction, and flattery,
along with excessive communication, gifts, giving,
and other worldly, has all make up love bombing.
I am rather pleased that people actually refer to it
as love bombing,
as it makes it sound like a pleasant experience.
I know that when it is happening,
it certainly feels wonderful for you.
But you will now be aware and has a much more sinister objective.
One thing you will well do with the outset is to change the label.
It is grooming.
That description signals danger and it should.
This grooming is actually the major defense you should hone.
If you see through the seduction and do not fall for it, you will avoid all this other
manipulative techniques that I can utilize.
Grooming is a bridge into my citadel of anguish and regret you need to ensure that you do not cross it instead burn it down
So there's no never any temptation to go do walk over the bridge
How might you go about beating my grooming given the heightened level of charm and seduction that accompanies it?
1. The combating fraud lived by the adage of, if it seems too good to be true, it usually
is. Adopt that mantra at the outset of a relationship. There is nothing wrong with
someone sending you Amur's text, but not 50 a day. Sending flowers is romantic, but does
not have to be a weekly occurrence. Recognize the substance of the compliment. If someone
praises your hairstyle after you have been to the hairdresser, it does not make sense.
If they repeatedly talk about how athletic, honed, and feeling your body is when it isn't,
You know the compliment isn't realistic. Pay special attention to outlander
declarations of love and commitments such as,
you are my soulmate. I will die if we aren't together.
I will never love anyone like I love you. I love you and I always have.
Oh, okay.
So look out for some choice examples in the seduction stage of my book, Evil, as well.
Remember those phrases and keep them as watchword in your heart.
Again, somebody saying some of the phrases makes sense after several months of spending
time together, but not after two dates.
You find yourself vaguely embarrassed by the comment or you regard it as toe-curling.
Trust your instincts.
You're being flattered to deceive.
Be aware of my kind and me saying that we have some kind of special connection very early on in the relationship
How on earth can we have that if we only really recently met do not fall for explanations such as we have known each other a long time
Yes, we may have known each other
But that was as colleagues or people who pass on the street. It was not an intimate basis
We'd love to make you feel special and we'll refer to the spiritual connection that we have or intense sexual bonding
Even though we all we have done is kiss so far
2. If I seem to know a lot about you, be wary. How could I possibly know all that unless I have been stalking you?
Normally we find out about one another through spending what time together and conversing.
If I seem to have encyclopedic knowledge of your likes and dislikes, I have been heavily researching you already. This is not healthy.
If I appear to be sharing a lot of secrets with you, you should be vigilant about this as well.
I do this to make you my co-conspirator and draw you into my web of deceit.
We're all special brothers? Yes, we are.
I am doing it to make you feel special and also in the hopes that you will yield secrets to me,
which I can then use to threaten you at a later stage.
Would you tell someone you only had met before your most intimate secrets?
No, you would not. So why am I?
Hey careful attention to how I talk about other people in my life. Am I dismissive about family?
Do I have a few long-standing friends?
Chances are these people have already worked me out and therefore have I have discarded them.
Not everyone is walled to nests and with their family or has a stable of long-standing friends, but it is certainly an indicator.
Six, how do I refer to my exes?
If it is with a bitterness and labeling them as nasty and crazy your
We either get rid of them or they are rid of us, but the tone, extent, and manner by
which we refer to them should not be malevolent or hateful.
If it is, it's a clear warning for you.
Seven, when we first meet, do I cover a lot of topics with you?
If so, be wary of this, especially if I seem to change opinions about certain things or
like some things which are diametrically opposed.
I am working my way through a checklist of items I wish I intend to ascertain, which
you like and which you not, so I can then agree with you as part of my mirroring technique,
but also to create a bond between us.
8. Trust your gut instincts. Would you say and do things that I do so soon? Yes
We all approach relations of differently, but a healthy approach is one of cautious interests
as we find out about one another.
If it is too fast, too wonderful, and not too fantastic,
and too fantastic, chances are this falls.
Nine, our early conversations all about you
and little about me.
While we narcissists are well-known
for wanting to direct everything back to ourselves,
we will share the limelight or even pass it up at first
for the greater gain.
If you're learning very little about me,
more than I agree with what you like and dislike,
there's a reason for this.
I have something to hide.
I move in the shadows.
I'm reading that it's called escape how to beat the narcissist by HDTutor. He's a British
author and narcissist and so it's interesting. It says, 10, if you find your behavior too
overpowering in the early stages, distance yourself. I want to engulf you and my desire
to do this overrides my any sense of proportionate behavior on my part. I also do not recognize
See boundary violation below 11 be cautious of excessive gestures such as expensive gifts and trips
It feels exhilarating to receive them, but again, they're designed to sweep you off your feet and get you off your guard
12. Talk to your trusted friends about what is happening. You should share these developments
with friends. Pay attention to what they might say in response. I won't have had a chance
yet to condition these people to like me or even recruit them as my lieutenants. I am
unlikely to denigrate them too much for fear of alarming you. This is a narrow window of
opportunity for you to receive some independent advice about how it really looks from someone
not cut up in the maelstrom.
13. Maintain vigilance for discrepancies. I am prone to bragging about my achievements
and boasting about matters such as job, money, and popularity. Take these assertions against
information from third parties to establish whether what I've said is true. Why not undertake
a credit check against me to establish if my declarations of solvency are true?
14. Observe how I react to you having friends with the opposite sex. I am not able to tolerate
you showing an interest to other people, especially those of the opposite sex, and I will engage
in disparaging behavior about those people or do something, which means you have to divert
your attention to me. Invariably, this behavior will be childish in nature, such as purposely
spilling a drink or just happen to break something, so it requires your attention and takes away
You said you've heard people say I am a narcissist is it true or false?
No, I'm not a narcissist at all. So what a narcissist is I mean, it's like, okay
So everyone is on a spectrum. So and it's like I'm in Los Angeles, right?
So you get and I'm also on
camera and I have to have a little bit of it a little bit of it
healthy self-confidence, but no, I don't not in not like a malignant
If I'm a very lower level
I'm not hardly I'm hardly narcissistic. I just have self esteem. That's only just because it's like there's you don't think so
Yeah, thank you. I
Know I know I don't think I'm the best person
I don't think I'm like, you know, I don't think anybody's better than anybody. I think we're equal, you know, and I
Like to like at least look at people as equal and as human
Imperfect beings like right but
With I think most people want to improve
Huh, but interesting
So that's that book I mean, but I have a lot of interesting
Interesting stuff. What are you guys interested in?
I actually have probably had like thousands and thousands of books about everything
You probably have a book about it if you name the topic, you know, because they have a lot of free books to give away on
on Amazon
Oh the guest
Alex yo yo
That's beauty on a freeway, and you pulled me over what would you do to me?
I'm gonna fucking ask you for license and registration
I'm over time. It's not good, and I'm gonna throw you in the bushes homie
In the bushes right there on the side of highway. I'm gonna give it to you right then and there
I'm gonna pull your pants off your little panties, and I'm gonna fuck you in the bush
I'm gonna give it to you. So I'm gonna make you come two times because I care about I care about your
So I'm gonna make sure you you have multiple orgasms in the bushes and
Then I'm gonna leave you there getting my car
and that's it my boy, that's it, no cameras around
no documents, it never happened
you know the number one rulers of the mob
if no one saw it, it never happened
I don't know. I know you're talking about
If no one saw it it never happened he killed them did he
You can kill a hundred people, bro
But if no one saw you killing a hundred people it never happened
The ways that United States works is proof you have to prove it in a court of law
People can say he killed a hundred people
Move it now you got to go into court
You got to bring up evidence either an audio a video or a witness without that you're fucked
And that's why the United States is the best and you know what runs the planet?
$600 an hour lawyers and that's actually cheap. That's what like the you know the low level
You know lawyers run the planet prove it motherfucker. He shot a hundred people prove it if you cannot prove it in a court of law
Yeah, it never happened. Oh J. Simpson went free, right?
Because he had the top-notch lawyers that made a mockery of the law system like you can't prove it
Oh
Do you have a witness? No, this is the only way to prove it, bro
By the way, you need a witness and audio confession or a video
You have no case. I went DNA evidence though because there's another six
Yeah, yeah, I mean I'm saying I'm saying that everything or it's like, you know actual crimes, you know
You know DNA that's crazy, but but the whole point is you have to wrap yourself in burlac
You shave your head you put on a fucking hazmat suit you put on rubber gloves
No evidence and if no one sees it ever happened my boy
But what about what about it? No, please. Okay, but we basically that sounds like very pre-meditated if you're like putting on like an outfit
Because you're gonna do something do it right
You don't just kill the one out of the blue
But if you're planning to you know, take care of your enemy you're gonna do it, right?
So what you're gonna do is make sure you don't leave DNA evidence behind
Because that's the top line evidence now forget the video evidence
Obviously, there's not video or witness or audio
But they might find the pubic hair and link you to the crime
So
I laugh at forensic teams. I laugh like good luck with that forensic boy
Good luck with that. You know my favorite tactic is like
You take the person and you show me in a bottle of acid and it the same grades them to
I mean, it's not very pleasant. I don't think it was very pleasant. I don't know very pleasant kind of conversation Alex
No, I
Mean, I don't like that kind of talk. Oh god
Okay, well, this is interesting. I just pulled this my card for today
This is actually the card on my for my birthday. So my birthday lived the second dick content of Capricorn
So that's yeah, so it's there
You can see there's these people checking out this guy and he's making some progress a little bit of progress, right?
or smaller gloves, okay, so it says three of pentacles.
It says nobility, elevation, dignity, rank, and power.
It says a sculptor is working in a monastery
compared to his design, which includes the eight of pentacles.
This appearance, apprentice or amateur therein
has received his reward and is now at work in earnest.
So it's a divinatory meeting.
Métier trade, skilled labor, usually however regarded as a card of nobility, aristocracy,
renown, and glory, says additional divinatory meanings, if for a man's celebrity, for his
eldest son.
And it says, theory, the fire of the seventh house, which rules the contact of the self
and the not self, the relations between both, the executive ability and man.
So this must lead to the idea of well-doing and the noble demeanor, owing to the sun and
venus.
Compare horoscopes of the sun and venus in seven.
Well-conducted relations denote civilization, aristocracy, and the proper expression of
It's Missier, as Wade had said, it's profession, marriage, and employment.
So this card has to do with workmanship, which is well expressed by the drawing of the card
in a set of weight. Time period. It's from Capricorn between January 1st and 10th.
It's well dignified. Construction, increased growth, financial gain, the building up of
favorable conditions, gaining commercial transactions, rank or prestige, and vocation or
And it says, he were constructiveness.
Interesting.
Dennis Nielsen did that with acid and blocked his drains up.
Oh, that's gross.
I mean, it's like, oh, that's giving me the heebie-jeebies,
right?
Let's see.
It says, when Smoky bin bags Justin,
he says, I will be your next dog.
Oh, my god.
My key MC, you want to?
Yeah, so anyway.
So that's interesting.
So let's continue to check out some interesting stuff.
What do you guys think?
And if anyone wants a reading, you know,
I would be happy to do readings,
just all you have to do is type in the crystal ball, you know?
I just do short free readings.
Or if you'd like a longer one,
you can look at the banner.
Okay, so what do we got?
How does Gotti have a wrench?
Oh, how does he have a wrench?
He's had what he died. Well, he's had a wrench for always
Isn't it has any
He I don't know he stole it from my mind my mind just drawer. I don't know what he's I don't know why he has one
He's running around. I can't find him right now
Keep trying to take it back
We're just playing we're playing ratchet games
Okay
So, let's see
Oh, how about a how about a sign?
But somebody tell me their astrology sign I'll read about if you're um the dark side of the sign
But but I do guys care who has a wrench you know me longer
Well, Arthur
Didn't she like misuse your wrench and I had to take it away from you
I thought or you said something terrible to me one day. You're like you called me like a scumbag and like
All these terrible things you through saying to me
Wait, Elzo's a mod? Why?
Elzo's a mod, but Elzo also just he donated like 25 memberships that day, too.
It's really, as you know, it's really
stood up for the show, like
Well
They talked the other scenes and fly against you
Oh, who does oh, yeah, who the boot right my mods. I don't think I've got it does someone give me a sign
Me I used to have a wrench over it's gonna have you have one you have a back and you know
I mean I say I
It's not a big the bigger deal as long as you like promise to like behave with it
But people just keep misbehaving with them
God he didn't he didn't really perform on me again. He just
Can he can this gaudy ban people
What if you're a mod? Yeah, you can you can ban people with a mod
But he never has actually he has this for like, you know people saying like terrible things. I agree with him on it
No, it was like everyone in that group was asking for a wrench and that is like is like I'll just give one to God
If I don't have to give one to everybody, then you know.
Yeah, because that it seems to appease,
let's make them happy.
You have that wrench back then?
You'd like the wrench?
Okay.
Promise not to misuse it?
I don't want to hear any more bitching, okay Arthur?
Just stop, okay?
I don't want to hear it again, okay?
Stop.
Yeah, you just back in your hands before you even for even said that right now you we stop bitching though. You're welcome. Okay
Okay, please behave please just behave
Okay, give me a sign everyone something someone's right there sign. I'll read about it. I'll read something about the dark side of it
Come on, please
28 people someone throw it right at astrological sign
First one that comes up I will read
Some
You mean I made your day. Okay, cool
We make time you may make my day if you like, you know, just like the same wonderful person you are
Thank you. Just as long as people support my show. I'm happy to like
let them
Can you supermod when you can ban mods? Nope
Yeah, it cannot be a managing mod. Libra. Okay, so let's see about Libra
Okay, so this is so this is called born on a rotten day. And so I'll go Libra
Okay, so Libra says
It says mirror mirror on the wall
And it says element air lever produces a constant droning in your ears
Leavers idea of rational discussion is that they discuss and you listen rationally
Evidently I've been no eventually you'll feel like you have your head is trapped in a beehive
The quality cardinal lever is Boston backbiter belittler and bimbo
Symbol the scales off balance permanently tipped in leavers favor swings both ways
The ruler Venus the goddess of plastic surgeons and mirrored ceilings. They were pastime smirking
They were book how to marry yourself role model Barbie and Ken
Dream job the devil's advocate key phrase on the other hand
Body part kidneys will have gravel from the teeth they grind at night to compensate for all that phony smiling during the day
To the approach with caution, Lieber's symbol, the scales, represents life's
continual balancing act. Lieber lives in the seventh house of partnerships.
Sugarcoated astrology tells us that Lieber's are harmonious, impartial,
diplomatic peacemakers who seek truth, beauty, and the perfect mate.
Truth is, beneath the glowing smile lives a self-indulgent, indecisive gold digger
who has the personality of a leaf. Lieber is ruled by the bad girl goddess
In Taurus, Venus bestows a greedy nature and that craves possessions.
In Libra, she bestows an endless hunger for perfection.
Libras are never satisfied with either themselves or you.
Being one of the bossy cardinal signs, Libras viewed descent as a personal affront.
They powered if you change the radio station.
Libra's idea of peace and harmony is your total agreement with their philosophy of the moment.
Have some fun by telling yours that his or her horoscope disagrees with the fortune cookie
that is read to you.
That should send either gender straight for the aspirin and a cold washcloth.
It says, Libras are subjective, not judicious.
Their skewed sense of justice distorts their ability
to accept any argument or opinion that is other than their own.
Being born without the justice is blind gene
has rendered them unable to remain truly impartial.
Argue with one, and a sudden,
suffer a sudden explosion of rage.
Groove your point and vacillating,
or vacillating Libra may verbally agree.
Finally, he or she will never forgive you for being right.
Okay.
You can't be on me but you can't be on me Mikey you wouldn't I
Can be on you. Okay, so it says if you are one foreign ratchan, okay, so it says
Forget what you need and only think about what you desire, Donna Caron.
It says, your sole purpose in life is to be right all the time, you're constantly
changing your mind in order to ensure that fact.
You have strong opinions that you always change in the face of disapproval,
since you never act on any of your endless declarations,
your friends and family quickly learn that your advice is worthless and ignored, and you.
Your most cited intellect is merely an inborn talent for knowing 50 ways to say on the other hand.
This endless hemming and hawing is actually an avoidance mechanism designed to protect you
from choosing sides or taking action. Leavers flee from decision-making faster than the Sagittarius
from a commitment ceremony.
Okay.
You have a vulgar shouting matches and so did emotional scenes unless you are the ones losing control or you hate them
Actually says even when angry you can't act decisively you deliberate over all the actions
You could take and wonder whether you should ignore the incident or go postal
By the time you decide the person you're mad and has forgotten you exist and moved to Bolivia
You are the most social sign in the zodiac and use any excuse to party.
That's because without an audience you bore yourself to sleep.
You can however, intuitively sense when someone needs help.
This is extremely convenient considering it gives you plenty of time to rush home and
take the phone off the hook to avoid getting involved.
You're a dedicated social climber as either Aries or Capricorn, however, you have neither Aries Honesty or Captain's class
But since you haven't the faintest glimmer of self-awareness
You quite cheerfully assume that no one thinks your sudden interest in an 85 year old Lotto winner is odd
Libre is a sign. Good morning, Dingle. Libre is a sign of an actor, double agent,
transvestite, and paid escort. You also make excellent politicians because of
your ability to talk out of both sides of your mouth at once. You are a fount of
useless minutiae, forever analyzing your problems like a cow chomping its cud. You
treat the people you love like projects and take perverse pleasure in pointing
out their faults and get offended when they tell you to piss off. You play the
You have such beautiful eyes. If only you lose some weight, you might be able to use it to see them.
You're so kind-hearted. If you only had the common sense to match.
If you are so shallow that your feelings get hurt, someone skips your party to check in the hospital for emergency surgery.
Since you inherited Venus' bed-hopping perspective on romance, you have secret affairs with people with whom you wouldn't be caught dead in public.
That's okay with you because you're so vain, you rationalized one night.
That one night will with you will magically improve your thermos rule a lot in life you long for a meaningful relationship
But anything less than blind agreement from the one you love sends you to bed with a near stranger
You don't want a partner you want a clone
Okay, old Libra couples are easy to spot because of their matching hairdos
However, you're also capable of pursuing a goal with a single-minded determination that borders on obsession
your deeply held beliefs set you apart from the rest of the world once you learn to avoid the petty
jealousies and soap opera theatrics which you frequently indulge in you learn that no sign alive
can distract you from your dreams um your flaws okay so that was that good you know i want a reading
okay i'm selling for one reasonable price one wrench as a decent uh new uniform you want to deal
Um, no selling wrenches, guys. You can't sell wrenches.
Okay.
How about this? This is good. This is called Top Secret.
It's called Silent Weapons for Quiet Wars. Okay. Can I hear this?
This is the top secret.
I've read a lot of it, okay, okay, so the Programming Manual for Control Society.
Security.
It is passionately impossible to discuss social engineering or the automation of society, i.e. the engineering of social automation systems, silent weapons, on a national or worldwide scale without implying extensive objectives of social control and destruction of human life, i.e. SLA, the E.R.Y., and genocide.
This model is in itself an analog declaration of intense. Such a writing must be secured from public scrutiny, otherwise it might be recognized as technically formal declaration.
Oh, shit. Hold on. I can't read all this. Hold on. Okay.
Let me just go ahead. Okay.
Okay, it says.
All science is merely a means to an end. The meaning is knowledge, the end is control.
Beyond this remains only one issue. Who will be the beneficiary?
It says, in 1954, there was an issue of primary concern.
Although the so-called moral issues were raised in view of the law of natural selection,
it was agreed that a nation or world of people who would not use their intelligence
are no better than animals who do not have the intelligence.
Such people are beasts of burden and stakes.
on the table by choice and consent.
Consequently, in the interest of future world order,
peace and tranquility, it was decided to privately wage
a quiet war against the USA public
with an ultimate objective of permanently shifting
the natural social energy wealth
of the undisciplined and irresponsible many
into the hands of the self-disciplined responsible
and worthy few.
In order to implement this objective, it was necessary to create, secure, and apply new weapons, which, as it turned out, were a class of weapons so subtle and sophisticated in their principle of operation and public appearance as to earn for themselves the name silent weapons.
as conducted by the magnets of capital
and the industries of commodities and services
is the establishment of an economy
which is totally predictable and manipulatable.
In order to achieve a totally predictable economy,
the low-class elements of society
must be brought under total control,
i.e. must be housebroken, trained and assigned to Yoke
and long-term social duties from a very early age
before they have an opportunity
to question the propriety of matter.
In order to achieve such conformity,
the lower-class family unit must be disintegrated by a process of increasing preoccupation
of the parents and the establishment of government-operated daycare
centers for occupationally orphaned children.
The quality of education given to the lower class must be of the poorest sort, so that
the moat of ignorance of isolating the inferior class from the superior class is and remains
incomprehensible to the inferior class.
With such an initial handicap, even bright, lower class individuals have little of any
hope of extricating themselves from their assigned lot in life.
This form of slavery is essential to maintain some measure of social order, peace, and tranquility
for the ruling upper class."
Wow.
Interesting.
Yeah, some of this is a little bit too controversial, I think, to read, but you can check it out, too.
It's also in this book called Behold a Pale Horse, right?
There's also a book called by William Cooper, right?
Yeah, I do love to read. I love books.
And we need more of a kind of like a little break from so much paneling, paneling, paneling.
The hours of hours of I like when things are accomplished, but it's like sometimes
It's not this project because I want to dig it to be
So
Dingle dangle if you guys want me to do a a picture of you draw a picture of you like I don't know if you have any suggestions
Stuff to do
Otherwise, I'm gonna be just doing what I feel like
This one's called Sitting Target.
Who hasn't had a picture drawn of them yet?
Hey, Seiki, I'm not kicking you make,
go ahead and reach your stream.
Okay, yeah, thank you.
This is called Sitting Target.
How and why the narcissist chooses you, okay?
By HGTutor.
It says we never choose our victims that because he's a narcissist, right?
And so he's writing from the point of view tonight. He's a British guy. He's really pretty interesting
But he's he's a lot of books. And so this is so it says we never choose our victims that random
We can gaze and careful and measure selection of those who we wish to draw into our world and serve our purposes
People put a lot of effort into choosing where they will live and what type of career they will follow
We put plenty of effort consideration and planning into choosing our victims
You may have performed the dance with the narcissist and now have been largely escaped. You may be wondering why you?
Remember you chose an entry like a queen and then thrown off the pedestal into the dirt below that the narcissist decided the
outset to subject you to this bewildering contrast and behaviors or were you just unlucky?
You may still be in the grip of the narcissist and you are searching for answers as to which what drew you to the narcissist and
In order to gain some understanding
Which would give you the peace of mind and allow you to plot your escape
You may know someone you care about who has been targeted by our kind, and you want to know that you can reach out and help this friend or family member.
Finally, you may belong to that rare group of people who knows about me and my kind, and you want to ensure you see us coming.
You want to know what...
It is that it tracks our kind to your kind so that you can be vigilant and take steps
to evade our clutches.
It may be the case that you know other people who have fallen foul of our machinations.
You may belong to a victim or survivor group where various war stories are swapped as horrific
tales are exchanged about what has happened to each of you.
Interestingly, many of these groups become a little more than forums for two things,
the detailing sometimes on a day-to-day basis, of the abuse that has been doled out and a
Some clearly find it cathartic to explain in detail why the narcissist did to them today or ask others what their views are about the way the victim has been treated.
Often these groups will go around in circles as the victims ask another, why is he doing this? What should I do? How do I make it stop? The bile and hatred for the narcissist is spewed forth and this is entirely understandable.
Okay, the narcissist choose you because you have green eyes or blue eyes or brown eyes
The narcissist choose you because of your job
Do you choose you because you have long hair or short crop locks?
Do you choose you because your choice of music the favorite food or was it because you happen to be stuck in a lift together?
Does the narcissist just choose anybody to be his victim and in reality has no discerning taste as to who he thinks his fangs into?
Is it the case that anybody and everybody is a potential victim for the narcissist and everyone is at risk of becoming ensnared?
I will be addressing
Consideration such as these. Okay, so let's see. Let's go ahead to the chapter one
Okay
So it goes through the types of nurses and says, hey guys,
linky, linky, you guys in the linky?
Okay, come on, linky, linky.
I know, I mean, they are, right?
But they used to be a smaller percentage,
but now it's like an epidemic.
So it goes through the types of them and stuff
and goes through the big, okay, so it goes,
there's a cerebral, it feels like kind of like a mental,
like they have to be the smartest, the somatic,
they have to be the most beautiful.
Okay, the elite,
And then it talks about fuel
Is why you were chosen, okay, why are you chosen?
It says
In continuing to examine why you are chosen and targeted by us, there are two
cheap considerations. The first is based on what we are, the type of narcissist we
are and therefore what needs arise from that and what is it that we want in
those we target. The second consideration in which segues with the above is
whether you are primary source or a supplementary source and what attributes
you have that we will meet and fulfill our needs.
As with everything that governs our existence, and it's all about us and what we need, we target you because we see that you will fulfill our needs.
The first and foremost is that you will provide us with fuel. You will give us the attention fused with emotion, either through act or words.
It may be positive or negative so long as achieved fuel from you. If you will not provide us with the fuel or your fuel provision will be weak and intermittent, you will not be targeted.
because the most important consideration when we target somebody, we need to ascertain their capability and reliability
is for providing this essential essence. I will explain in later chapters how we go about ascertaining your suitability,
but this juncture you need to understand that it is your capacity for providing fuel and fulfilling our prime need,
which results in us targeting you.
What does this look like then?
Why do some narcissists seek out a particular type of victim
compared to others?
Our targets share several traits in common,
and then there are others which are a greater attraction
depending on the type of narcissist we are.
Okay, so here's the traits they look for, okay?
The love devotee, okay?
We require our targets to be committed
to the concept of love.
You want to find love, experience love, love, and be loved.
The idea of love is central to your existence.
You truly believe that our purpose on this earth
is to love others.
Not only does this mean loving those around you,
but also above all else, you believe in the fulfillment
that arises from having that one special person
who you're committed to.
who you will do anything for and who you make sacrifices for, the existence of love is the reason
to you to exist and therefore you must find it and once located obtain it and maintain it.
Yeah, yep, then it says if they should be compassionate and then they should be decent people,
moral compass, caring people, honest people,
You need to understand people, people striving for the truth,
supportive of the underdogs, good listeners.
So those are some things.
OK, so that physical traits.
It just goes into so much information.
OK.
And then the hunting grounds.
bars, nightclubs, restaurants, academic, hospitals, bank, office, concerts, libraries, sporting events, debating society, museums, arts, crafts, clubs,
outdoor pursuits, shopping malls, neighborhoods, clatch, charity organizations, swimming, gym, springing venues, social media, dating sites, right?
Bars, restaurants. So those are all these places that people will meet. They basically are always at these places.
Okay, this is a masterclass in gaining the information about the person we have in our
sites.
So we know they're a viable target for our subduction.
This is how we ascertain whether the person is someone we should pursue and also how we
know that they will be a waste of time and therefore should be left alone.
There is often a preparatory work undertaken before we've contacted you or spoken to you,
and then we are engaged in drawing information from you, both spoken and from the way you
behave.
Which confirms to us you have the generic class and hopefully the special traits too.
Your presence in the environment is of course a key indicator, and something which suggests
that you are more likely than not going to take the class traits, but we need you to
fulfill the generic traits also.
Occasionally there are people in an environment who would not normally be there. We must weed out these anomalies
We focus on the better targets
We will look at the various steps and we take and demonstrate how these are used in certain environments that have details above
So you're able to recognize how we approach you and target you
This is not about the way we seduce you. This is for a different time. This is about
What we do when we are targeting you prior to the
seduction commencing, invariably where we make contact with you to gather more
intelligence to ascertain whether you'll be in valuable contact, there'll be a
degree of charm and the seduction will commence. If we gave you to not be a
good target, then as we've broken off, although or given our background checks
the environment situation we have chosen, this is rare. However, keep in mind that
this is about the way we target you and how we do so.
It's okay. I mean, most people are it is a it is a
Spectrum and so it's like everybody is like
Even if they're like very low-level most people are just like, you know
Most people as long as you don't hate yourself you're basically not a narcissist
They know sometimes some narcissists do hate themselves though, right?
It's like they could they were narcissists because of insecurities, right? So that
I mean it's a psychological explanation. It's not necessarily a real thing. It's one of our concepts, right?
Narcissism. This is the victim narcissist.
Physical appearance. The victim narcissist will easily observe your physical appearance to ensure that the target is not physically imposing compared to him,
nor to
considerable attractiveness so that he or she might prove tempting to somebody else.
Okay, so talks about the victim narcissist and all the different kinds of narcissists.
Anyway, what else is there this is kind of what I'm not one of the better books you love yourself too much
You should be I think people should really love themselves like a lot
I think they should because people are are usually hardest on themselves and like
Or their own worst enemy, right
So what is too much is
too much is like
As long as you're not fucking yourself with your own dick. I think people are not loving themselves enough
Let's not make it about you. Yeah, exactly. Well, you know, we're just talking. Okay, so I
Have this stuff about it's called Confessions of an Illuminati. Let me see
I'm talking about a lot of weird stuff right here. Let's talk about all this kind of like
Crowley Crowley stuff, but I see it's a better chapter
Okay. I can't talk about that. A lot of this stuff infiltrating a UFO code. We'll go into that.
Some of this is pretty shaky.
I can't read most of this.
I can tell it's just too controversial, right?
Here's a book about brainwashing.
Since in order to better understand modern mental torture, we must constantly keep in
mind the fact that from the earliest days bodily anguish in the rack were never meant
merely to inflict pain on the victim.
They might not have expressed their understanding in sophisticated terms that the medieval judges
and hangmen were nevertheless aware that there is a peculiar spiritual relationship and mental
interplay between the victim and the rest of the community.
such painful torture and hanging had to be done as a public demonstrations.
After suffering the most intense pain, the witch would not only confess to shocking
sexual debaucheries with the devil, but would
herself gradually come to believe the stories she had invented.
that would die convinced of her guilt.
The whole ritual of interrogation and torture finally compelled her to yield to the fantasies
of her judges and accusers.
In the end, she adjourned for death.
She wanted to be burned at the stake in order to exercise the devil and expiate her sins.
The same judges and hangmen realized too that their witch trials were intended not only
to torture the witches, but even more to torture the bystanders who albeit unconsciously identified
themselves with the victims.
This is, of course, one of the reasons burnings and hangings were held in public and became
the occasion of great pageants, terror that became widespread, and many judges spoke
euphemistically of the preventative action of such torture.
and the general tendency to identify with others.
Crazy, that's pretty crazy.
And then it says,
all knowledge can be used for either good or evil,
but in psychology is not immune to this general law.
Psychology is delivered up to man,
new means of torture and intrusion to the mind.
You must be more and more aware of what these methods
and techniques are, or, of course, they successfully fight them.
they can be more painful and mentally more paralyzing than the rack.
Strong personalities can tolerate physical agony, often it serves to increase stubborn resistance.
No matter what the constitution of the victim, physical torture finally leads to protective
loss of consciousness, but it's to withstand mental torture, leading to creeping mental breakdowns,
demands, and even stronger personality. What we call brainwashing, you attack with the devil once,
Okay, thank you, share it please, I appreciate that.
So what we call brainwashing a word derived
from the Chinese, Sino, is an elaborate ritual
of systematic indoctrination, conversion,
and self-accusation used to change the non-communist
into submissive followers of the party, Hunter.
Menticide is a word coined by me and derived
from men's, the mind, and cadre to kill.
Okay, so both words indicate the same perverted refinement of the rack, putting it on what
appears to be a more acceptable level, but it is a thousand times worse and a thousand
times more useful to the Inquisitor.
Mentecite is an old crime against the human mind and spirit that systemized anew.
It is an organized system of psychological intervention and judicial perversion through
which the powerful dictator can imprint his own opportunistic thoughts upon the minds
of those he plans to use and destroy.
So it goes into all this kind of stuff where it's happened in different countries and stuff like that, pretty crazy stuff.
So you know about Pavlov and you know about the condition, responses and stuff. Let me see.
Is anybody studying psychology? Hey, KT.
Are you like doing Hellboy?
So Pavlov, I'll tell you the story about Pavlov.
I'm sure you've heard of Pavlov's dog, okay? So he was the, I think, a Russian, let's see,
says, in the latter part of the 19th century, the Russian Nobel Prize winner Ivan Petrovik
Pavlov conducted his famous experiments with a bell and a dog. He knew that salivating
is associated with eating, and that if a dog was hungry, its mouth would water each time it saw food.
Habloff took advantage of this useful inborn reflex which serves the digestive process to develop in the experimental animal
the salivating response and an answer to the stimulus which would not ordinarily create it.
Each time Pavlov fed the dog, he rang the bell, and each feeding the dog's mouth watered.
Then after many repetitions of the combined food-bell stimulus, Pavlov rang the bell but
did not feed the dog.
The animal reacted to the bell alone, just as it had previously reacted to the sight of
food and its mouth watered.
Thus, the scientists had found out that the dog could be induced to salivate involuntarily
in response to an arbitrary signal.
Is it that sound with the smell and taste of food?
OK, interesting.
From this and other experiments, Pavlov developed his theory of the conditioned reflex, which explains learning and training as the building up of
messiahic of conditioned reflexes, each one based on the establishment of an association between different stimuli.
The greater the number of learned complex responses, also called patterns, the greater the number of conditioned reflexes develops.
Because man of all animals has the greatest capacity for learning, he is the animal with the greatest capacity for such complicated conditioning.
Hmm
Let's just talk about how this could have been used for good that was used for evil purposes. Okay
Now man is being conditioned like that unfortunately
Interesting animals will do anything for food but that because there's a hunger, you know, it's hard
Peaceful exchange of free thoughts and free conversation will serve the condition reflexes and is therefore taboo no longer
Are there any brains only conditioned patterns and educated muscles in such a taming system neurotic compulsionist looks upon as a positive asset?
Instead of something pathological the mental autonomous become the ideal of education
but there's different ways they do it. It's not about medication or like, you know,
programming. There's a lot of ways they do it, right? Hypnotism.
And sometimes the entire population is going to be hypnotized. It says, let me see.
The charming characters who are easily able to influence others are often extremely susceptible
to suggesting themselves.
Some personalities of this tremendous gift for empathy and identification provoke in
others the desire to yield up all their secrets.
They seem somehow to be the father confessor by the grace of God.
Other empathic types by reflecting on their own deceitful inner world can more easily
provoke the hidden lies and fantasies of their victims.
why one man should inspire the desire to give in and another the desire to resist is one of the
mysteries of human relationships in contact. Why do certain personalities complement and reinforce
one another while others clash and destroy one another? Psychologists have given new insight
into these strange human relations and involvements. Then we'll talk about the truth serum.
Okay
So they're talking about how the you know, it's Japanese but like
Brainwash people into like you know the soldiers into like there's announcing America and stuff to be free and stuff
And people would do it so
But it didn't mean it.
OK, so the mysterious masochistic packs.
In Arthur Kossler's Masterpiece, Darkness at Noon, he describes all the subtle intricacies,
reasonings, and dialects between the Inquisitor and his victims.
The old Bolshevik, Rubyshav, preconditioned by his former party adherents, confesses to
plotting against the party in his party line.
He is partly motivated by the wish to render a last service, his confession as a final
sacrifice to the party.
Rather as part of the mysterious masochistic pact between the Inquisitor and his victim, which we encounter too, in the process of brainwashing.
Oh, where the person being tortured likes it. That's fucking scary, right?
The term masochism originally referred to sexual gratification, received from pain, and punishment later became every gratification acquired through pain and objection.
It is the last gift and trick the torturer gives to his torturer.
It is as if he were to call out, Be good to me, I confess, I submit, Be good to me and
love me.
After having suffered all manner of brutality, hymnotism, despair, and panic, there is a
final quest for human companionship.
But it is ambivalent mixed with deep despising, hatred, and bitterness.
tortured and tortured or gradually form a peculiar community in which one influences the other.
Just as the therapeutic sessions where the patient identifies with the psychiatrist,
the daily sessions of interrogation and conversation with an unconscious transfer of feelings
in which the prisoner identifies with his inquisitors and his inquisitors with him,
the prisoner entrapped and raptured in a strange, hard and unfamiliar world.
identifies much more with the enemy than the enemy does with him.
Unwittingly, he may take over all the enemy's norms, evaluations, and attitudes toward life.
Such passive surrender to the enemy's ideology is determined by unconscious first processes.
The danger of communing in this kind is that at the end, all moral evaluations disappear.
We saw it happen in Germany. The very victims of NAVI came to accept the idea of camps.
Which is scary is that happening like today? I hear here's like some kind of thing and I don't know
I don't want to say but the initials are a a right you want to come back as a cat, right?
So then it kind of goes through the steps
And then it goes through the first day we're doing people now they're doing the whole society's public opinion
the movies the TV
Sports every human communication
is either a report of straight facts or an attempt to suggest things and situations as they do not exist.
Such distortion and perversion of facts strike at the core of human communication.
The verbal battle against man's concept of truth
and against his mind seem to be ceaseless.
For example, if he can instill this eventual future enemies
fear and terror in the suggestion of impending defeat,
even before they're willing to fight,
my battle is already half won.
The strategy of man to use a frightening mask
and a loud voice to utter lies
in order to manipulate friend info
is just the oldest mankind.
Primitive people use terror-provoking masks
with magic fascination or self-deceit
as much as we use badly spoken words
to convince our subs.
others or ourselves. These magical paints and we are ideologies. Truly we live in an age of ads,
propaganda, and publicity, but only under dictatorial and totalitarian regimes have such human
habit formations, mushroomed as a systematic psychological assault on mankind.
Okay, then it goes into the future totalitaria kind of like that scary concept totalitaria
Okay
I can't I can't really read too much of this more, okay
So I think it's almost over. Oh, we're actually not let me see
Wild accusation and or the purge this has been interesting. Okay, so we'll go to this okay
Some places you eat food and if you're lucky enough to spend time in their cages inside a shelter
There's a small amount of cats that actually oh
Oh, yeah, I get a lot of cats come back. You know early or not
You know on the street and stuff, okay, so this is
The in okay, so this
Oh, this is about magic, okay
Okay, so the weapon of terror has been used by tyrants from time immemorial to make a meek instrument of man in totalitarian we use this weapon
The use of this weapon is refined to a science, which we can wipe out all opposition and dissent.
The leaders of totalitarian rule by intimidation. They prefer loyalty through fear to loyalty through fate.
Fear and tear frees the mind and will.
It may create a general psychic paralysis.
In the panic caused by totalitarian tear, men feel separated from one another by an
impassable vacuum, and each man becomes a lonely, frightened soul.
Even panicky hovering together could be suspected of being conspiracy against the state, separated
from any real emotional contact with his fellow men.
By his own inner isolation, the citizens of totalitarian become increasingly unable to
Totalitarianism is constantly on alert for social sinners, the critics of the system, and accusation of dissent is equivalent to conviction in the public eye.
Insinuation, columnity, and menaceation are staples of the totalitarian strategy.
The entire nation is dedicated to the proposition that every man is a potential enemy of the regime.
No one is excluded from the terror. Any man may be subjected to it no matter how high his rank.
The secret police create awe and panic inside the country while the army serves to create
awe and panic outside, just as the thought of the outbreak of terror or even a possible
future terror makes men unwilling to express their opinions and expose themselves, both
the citizens of totalitarianism and those of the neighbors are affected by this general
fear.
A clear example of how fear parallels this operation reality, you've seen the fact that
as far back as 1948, Western Europeans who felt the shadow of anticipated totalitarian
thought it was safer to criticize and attack their American friends than to find fault with the
totalitarian enemy who might sweep in suddenly and without warning. In totalitaria, jails and
concentration camps, uh,
By the score are built in order to provoke fear and awe among the population.
They may be called punishment or correction camps,
but this is only a cheap justification for the truth. In these centers of fear, nobody is really corrected.
He is, as it were, expelled from humanity, wasted, killed, but not too quickly, lest its terrorizing influence be diminished.
Oh, maybe yes, exactly. Come back as one of my cats. Yeah, it would be happy.
The truth of the matter is that these jails are built not for the real criminals, but rather for the terrorizing effect on the bystanders, the citizens of Territaria.
Jails represent a permanent menace, a continual threat. They may be put almost in supportable strain on the empathy and imagination of those citizens who are temporarily, at least, on the outside of the barbed wire.
In addition to the fear of undergoing the same cruel treatment, the fear of abasement, humiliation, and death, the very concept of the concentration camp arouses every man's deep-seated fear.
of being himself expelled from the community of being alone, a wanderer in the desert,
unloved and unwanted.
There exist several milder forms of masquerade since the strategy of no political arrest.
In totalitarian, a man is always caught by some form of official planning.
He's always conscious of control and surveillance, of spying, leering powers, lying in wait
to chase him and punish him.
Even leisure time and holidays are occupied by some official program, some facts to be
learned, some political meaning, some parade, quiet and solitude no longer exist.
There's no time for meditation, no pondering, no reminiscing.
mind is caught in a web of official thinking and planning, even the delights of self-chosen silence
are forbidden. Every citizen of totalitarian must join in the singing and slogan shouting,
as he becomes so caught up in the constant activity that he loses the capacity to realize
Okay, then it goes, Wild Accusation and Black Magic, okay?
It says, Wild Accusation and Black Magic, like other timing, taming tools of totalitarian,
are nothing new, but in primitive civilizations and prehistoric time, the craft of Black Magic
was rather simple. The shaman had to merely destroy or mutilate a small statue at the accused criminal
to point or thrust a special stick at the man itself or to curse or berate him with furious words
and gestures in order to bring his victim to collapse and death.
In his blind acceptance of the magic ritual, the victim was possessed by fear and often
gave himself up to the spell and just died.
This magic slaying of the foe has a plural psychological implications.
The victim of the magic spell was often looked upon as representative of the tribal god,
the internalized authority and the father.
He must be killed because of the very existence of our guilt and remorse among his people.
His death may silence the inner voices in every man which warn against impending downfall.
Sometimes the victim comes from a different tribe than that of his accusers.
In this situation, the stranger is an easier scapegoat, and punishing him serves to steal
the clash of ambivalent feelings in the members of the killing tribe.
Hate for an outsider checks and deflects the hate and aggression each man feels toward his own
group and toward himself. The more fear there is in a society, the more guilt each individual
member of society feels, the more need there is for internal scapegoats and external enemies.
In totalitaria, the heirs full of gossip,
columnity, and rumor, any accusation, even if it's false,
had the greater influence on the citizenry
than subsequent vindication.
Bills of particulars made out of whole cloth
are manufactured against innocence,
especially against former leaders
who have been able to develop some personal steam
and loyalties among their friends and followers.
From subcharges made against us
will always revive unconscious feelings of guilt
and induce us to tremble.
The fact that character assassination is possible reveals a frailty and the sensitivity of human
sympathy and empathy.
Even in freed and democratic societies, political campaigns are often conducted in an atmosphere
of extravagant accusation and even wilder counter accusation.
The moment the strategy of wild accusation with all its disagreeable noises of by-true
tension behind the words and find ourselves influenced by the shouting and name-calling.
Maybe we say to ourselves there's something to the story. This is of course just what the
slanderer wants. In the minds of fluid politicians, the illusions still persist that the end justifies
the means, but campaigns of slander produce paradoxical results because the very fact
that an unfounded accusation has been made weakens the moral sense of both the listener and the accuser.
There goes spy mania in totalitarian the vicious cycle of the true creation reaches its fullest flowering
ground in a serenity suspicion the citizens of totalitarian which suffer from a terrible delusion of
persecution the spionia the spy mania
He is continually on the alert watching his fellow man
His good neighbor may at any moment become a saboteur or a traitor the citizen of totalitarian
Harley ever looks for confusion or flaws in his own soul
What projects them onto his scapegoats until he finds himself finally becoming the victim
of someone else's spy, Noia? Every citizen is constantly trying to search out everyone else's
innermost thoughts because one's own hidden thoughts are projected on one's neighbors,
thinking in itself becomes the enemy. This great fear of the inner thoughts of our fellow man
is related to the general process of paranoiac reevaluation of the world as a result of fear
the denial of human loyalty and the constant illusion of treason and sabotage were expressed the whole infantile mythology of totality area and its repudiation of mature human relationships.
through interrogation, character assassination, humiliation,
mental terror, and demoralization, such as happens
in individual and collective brainwashing,
men can be so utterly demoralized
that he accepts any political system.
He has nothing anymore.
Why should he oppose matters?
In totalitarian, there's no open policy, no free discussion,
no honest difference of opinion.
There's only intrigue and denunciation
with their frightening actions on the masses.
It's kind of scary, right?
The strategy of wild accusation is used not only against totalitarian citizenry, but also
against the rest of the world.
Totalitarian needs the images of outside enemies, imaginary cruel monsters who spread plague
and disease to justify its own internal troubles.
The remnants of the individual citizen's conscience are calmed and held in check by the paranoiac
attack on the rest of the world.
The enemy is poisoning our food, throwing beetles and bacteria in our crops.
The myth of an imaginary world conspiracy aims at bringing the fearful citizens of Tuthalus
Heria into a concerted defense against non-existent dangers. It conceals at the same
time internal failures leading to diminishing crops and lack of food.
Hello. Good morning. Hi Paige. What are you doing? I was just reading that interesting book.
I
Haven't seen my little my little headphones
They're easier my ears these are kind of tight
Yeah, I'm just sitting with the kitty cats. Hey come on down
How's your day
It's yeah, like just the stuff with the breakup and stuff and pushing a lot of things down so I don't have to deal with the motions of it.
Mm-hmm.
You know, today might be the sad day for that, I don't know.
Oh, I'm sorry.
And then I got my grandparents to check, they heard like go check cows this morning, I just got back.
Huh?
And so.
How are they?
Do they feed the cows or?
Yeah, but there was one injured calf and so like, it's not very good.
Oh.
Are you able to
treat it?
How does it injure?
Yeah, um, no, it's just uh,
they get, yeah, no, it's just they get stomach issues sometimes if they, uh,
they can twist their stomach or eat something bad. I don't know what it was.
If you give them an item that I can usually find.
Uh-huh. Oh, ivermectin, I've heard of that. That's um,
is it, hold on, is that, is that like a,
ivermectin, is that um, where's tranquilizer?
Hold on. I ever mix them. I've heard of that. It's like they used it for something else. Okay. I can't really say what they used it for.
Antibiotic. It's like an antibiotic. It's kind of a cure-all for everything that they have. Like, worms, parasites, worms, like, infections, and bacteria, anything like that.
Illnesses.
Yeah, for cows.
For cows, right?
No, you can use it on all livestock and actually people have been using it in small doses, but it's for a livestock. Yeah. Oh, okay
Yeah, well, I've heard of it some interesting like
Things that humans use like there's something called
Primarin-primerin, okay, it's like a bio identical hormone, but you know what primarin means it's a it's a synthetic form of something else
It's a pregnant mare's urine. It's the answer pregnant mare's urine. Yeah, that's what they put in birth control
Oh, they do? Yeah, it's called a PMU burn.
PMU, yeah.
Yeah, Pregnant Mary urine, yeah. And so, Premarin, kind of, I just remember like who did it, like
Suzanne Summers was really into like the
alternative medicine. She also, she had breast cancer and she injected herself with Iscador.
That's the extract of mistletoe.
And that, she was actually
cured back then, but then she passed away like a few years ago, I think, but eventually
that's years later.
So I don't know if it worked though.
Interesting.
I wonder about some of these alternative cures.
Who's there?
Oh, is anybody there?
I thought you were talking to me.
Well, I was talking to you.
Just my mic went off.
I said, yeah, that's great.
Yeah.
But can be good or bad, sometimes you just kind of have to look at the, the death toll
If it's a common that people are surviving then maybe it's something to look into but if it's not and it's just a dumb idea
I guess you know right, but it's like you know
It's like who how are you supposed to find out like the regular the doctors won't like won't are not supposed to share
Because there's some natural cures that they can't talk about or say they're putting medical claims for but then it's like then they
Can't make those claims about the
that the pharmaceuticals, right?
Chinese sweet gates, a lot of frog legs,
and they're talking about eating animals in the chat.
China eat frog legs, and they're eating China.
I think frog legs before.
I've had them in Mexico, but we were at Club Med,
and they had like a French,
kind of some French food, and they had frog legs.
Yeah, when I lived in Calgary,
a place called Globe Fish used to do like wing night,
but it was frog leg night, so it was 25 cents per frog leg.
Are they good you like them? It was good except for like my brain, you know a couple legs in was like this is frog
Yeah, it was like no, we're not gonna eat anymore
Yeah, I remember tasting like chicken a little bit, but then it's like that's like, you know
But then like really thin bones like it's the both are so small and like big soft that it's like it can be chicken, right?
So they go the hell is it?
But it wasn't bad. It wasn't bad. Yeah, it tasted like thickened in sauce, honestly
It was textually a little bit fucked up though. Like I said, my brain identified it right away as being a foreign object.
Yeah. Well, yeah, I'm trying to think of some of the weirdest stuff I've eaten. I really haven't.
I'm experimental and stuff like that, but I guess it'd probably be some kind of sushi or something like that.
Why are you upset, rapper? What's wrong?
Who's that other rappers dig I think I think that's big, huh? Hey, and Jenny's saying hey to you. Hey chat
Okay, I need to have a morning hoot with my fam
My grandma she's like so my grandparents obviously don't fucking an adult woman. I can do what I want, right? But um
What was I do? I had a hood off of my Benjamin was out in the field
And I didn't realize it like blew back and like they go up through the cloud or whatever when Hannah starts coughing. She's like
birthday later what is in that she's giving me the gears about it and I was like
because she always heard me called like tobacco vapes douche flutes
she was is that one of them they're douche flutes you blew in my face I was like no no
there's a pendulum she goes who's that pendulum
Oh my god, that's cute. Yeah
I always got my dad really baked off stuff like that cuz I'm like he's like hey cool
Let me see that I'm like you better try it's the coolest and I'll convince him to try whatever it might be
Whatever we're up us refer up to
Yeah, I'll just get him raxing. I'm like see you're you're not cool anymore. You can't hang
But he
Grace is the same thing to me and calls me cringy all the time. So I guess it works always doesn't it?
I just pulled you a card page, I just pulled you an animal card, guess what card I pulled you?
Um, the owl, one of the horrors for the cow.
You see?
What is that?
The raven, and then raven started beowing and seeing it in that picture.
Oh, so in my screen because it's reflecting off of your screen onto my card, it looks like a fucking, it looks like venom.
Yeah, it's not a snake. Okay says Raven. It says creation magic illumination
Raven is frequently associated with powerful magic and omens in symbolism parallels
that of a coyote and the rabbit in Native American myth is worshiped as a deity the haida and
Clingent people of Western Canada and Alaska
Revealed the Raven as a hero and helper of human beings. I'll go reflected in a bird's prominent position in the totems of the Northwest
The raven is believed to have placed the sun moon and stars in the sky bringing light to the people both day and night
There you go. Beautiful card
That's beautiful. These are by Susan Boulay. There's the art. Yeah, she's like she's a very famous art
She's doing all this and it looks really cool. This one's a wolf right there
Okay, what's your last name again?
Buble?
B-O-U-L-E-T.
It's like Susan said on Buble.
And she, like, if you look, she has all these, like, really, like, ethereal, like, let me
see another one.
Let me see.
So here's the lion.
Like, there's a beautiful lion.
And we have the, uh...
This is the birds this one is this is birds, right?
Yeah, it's birds and it's like she's all these birds right there
You know, it's a kind of big bag on a look right there. Great Indian it
It's okay, it's warmer on my grandparents up the road
I feel like there's an alien with a cat.
It feels like it's real.
It feels like he's like coming.
It's like, it's all like trippy and like,
it looks real to me now.
It looks like he's all 3D.
And like, it's like, what if it comes to life?
If I do DMT, it might come to life.
I'd be right at my...
All your cards, stuff just going to be crawling out of them.
Like the page master comes real.
You're the page master.
You're the page page master.
You guys are filming that movie though,
with Macaulay Culkin?
Hmm, I don't know if she was called the page master the page master. Yeah, he gets like locked in the library. Oh
Never any story. Yeah, it's like about stories like sort of like horror and
Yeah, it's like the well it sounds like the never ending story remember like fashion like passes out in the library's attic
That's for you and fashion. Hey summer. How are you sweetie?
I love the page master. Okay, that's Macaulay Coltskin. I guess I've never heard of it rapper. Can you turn it? Yeah? Hey summer
We're just hanging out and
I love I love cards and I even love like just even like one card is like there's so much information on cards that it's like one card is
They always look at the message. Oh, like the never ending story. What was the horse's name in that movie?
What was it? I remember that when the horse drowned. I think it's bad. Yeah, the fucking scarring one part that scarred every child in all of eternity
Then our in our generation or era I guess before and after a little bit
I don't remember the worst name, and he's only there for a quick blip.
Let me see. I kind of remember because the guy was yelling it out. He was like,
oh, wait a minute. What are you doing now? I've smoked way too much pot, remember that, I think.
Gotcha. Gotcha, he says. Okay, let me set my phone in my little area. I just use tarot boxes to set it up.
It's almost like they're having a cat and stuff in Chinese restaurants. There is a movie called gummo
It's by the guy that made kids movie. Can't think of them as Larry Clark, right?
And gummo is about these two brothers and they're kind of inbred they're in the south and they
They walk around, you know, unaliving cats and like flexing them and they sell them to a Chinese restaurant
It's really weird. It's a really weird movie. It's like I would never like when I'm watching a movie like that, but it's kind of
more of an interesting movie
You know, I don't like to think has what happened
Come on. Oh, sorry
I got a little, I put in a little bit of...
Does that sound okay guys? I'm not sure how it sounds.
Wait, my golf game doesn't, isn't as shitty.
I need to repay or to reduce some of these
emojis I think there's just gone.
But they actually came out pretty cool, some of them,
but some of them I can't really tell what they are.
Like the little
This one I can't really see
The bigger to you guys I want to be oh
It's an LOL. I need to find a better
Okay
Have you seen the emojis or I'm not sure if you've seen the emojis, but they're pretty cool. But they're so small, they're so small, but I think they're really good.
Well, I'm going to get more colorful ones and stuff. I think I need more, more like a color coordinated set and stuff. I'll work on them.
I love doing graphics now.
Like formatting it makes it really easy something's really easy like you can resize the thing commit perfect size for any social media thing
And like one step really easy, but then it's like if you need to like transfer something from one place to another sometimes
It's like hard and figuring out getting better at it
I never was able to figure out Photoshop, I was like, so...
Photos? Like, pasting your head on someone else's body?
Well, yeah, I mean, but it's like, you know, it's just a general good graphics program.
Like, you know, people were just making graphics on that, but it's really complicated and technical.
Like, and so this is like, I just use Canva, it makes it so easy and simple.
Like, I'm pretty like, I'm not done.
So I'm not that smart. I'm kind of smart. He's not that smart. It has his AI thing
Tell him what to make and I'll just make you stuff. Yeah
Oh
Good morning. Good morning summer. So I'm just gonna say morning to read Dingle. Most we have slayer
That's it for this morning rapper
Jenny everybody black RG
It's just a little just a little bit of people in here Toran and hey, it's pretty early
Okay
Look at this. Oh, you see that that's pretty cool. See made that that's what today is guys
Yes
Oh, those are cool. Let me see. Are they zombies? Are those zombies? Yeah. Yeah, it's a really interesting book.
Cool. You like some Band-Aid? Do you see this one? Do you see this Band-Aid on the screen?
It looks like one of those like raves that you do the dust painter, I really...
Yes, I've been named for every day now.
I do like that.
I'll give you a choice. Alexander's in the back. Alexander's in the back. What do you think?
Well, we don't know till we don't just see what vibe it is. Okay, right now fucking early, but yes
Hi Alexander hi beautiful
Is that a new sweater
More I see great. I see a great tank towel
No
Checking cows, so I needed a warm sweater or jacket. I make you better baby
When you're in the mall shop when you close you're gonna actually laugh and be like
But now you got a new job chasing golf balls. I don't know how God did that you haven't made
So you have a job
Crazy I wish I had that job. That's the greatest job on the planet
So what your next paycheck I want to see you at the mall
I don't really shop Alex. I'm not I will I'll do it for you though. I'll just go for a little shop
Yeah, please
Please
If I see those green black pants again, and the way tank top, I don't know what I'm gonna do
I want to see double tank up yellow tank top pink green
Every color thanks up
Do you like Lulu Alex? Is that appropriate? Is that bougie enough for you? Yes? I've got all
By the way, I think it's because the covers have your whole forehead
Which is gigantic. I can play fucking
Handball also forehead you in psyche. Are you are you related to psyche?
Thank you. Look at your forehead
We're cousins
My my forehead is bad. She is I got a normal forehead. It's like, you know
You guys travel it looks like oh like the Berlin wall
Like the border like I need a ladder to get over that boy. Oh
Alex come on
Beautiful big beautiful house. It's not a big brain. You know have you heard that?
Oh, that's kind of funny. Okay. Yeah, so
Hey, you're only in psych. Oh, honey
We're some kind of delicious Italian dish, oh this guy thinks I'm gonna buy a sweater
Okay, oh yeah guys guys who I am
Oh, yeah, so I have um, I do have merch guys. I was gonna say I do have merch
I'm gonna try to like I think a few people I'm gonna try to send
Uh, we can try to get some samples and like send them to a few people like you know
White looks good on me, but black does too, so I'm gonna have to get bold
Yeah, okay
Yeah, I look really good in white though
Well, I don't fucking know that because you never came up. I know
Captain likes to judge everybody, but you're just beakin because I've never seen you
Thank you so exactly
I just see you for like one second
I need to see you again
Yeah, so he said
That's what he said
That's what I thought
I look like me, that's what he said
I look like me, I look like me
You look like yeah
Alex looks like him, okay
Alex I think you look like sound that's why I put my like what you look like you sound and you act
I feel like I just put this persona of this person of you. So what what does that do though? What color eyes?
How can you do it?
I think you have dark hair and I think you have like a lighter colored eyes. I don't think you have dark eyes
Like the government taxi driver. I think I think that the detectives like Robert DeNiro taxi driver
I think it'd be like that. Thank you. That's so cool. That's so cool
I don't think you're super tall though. I'm 5'8. That's pretty tall. Okay. Actually if things taller than me some
No, it's so according to your standards. That's like a fucking
You're like a fucking the space jam guys when they get really
5'1
5'9 with boots 5'10. I don't know
I go by my license. I have a new stage driver license and whatever that says is my height, you know, they know
How tall is the same 5-1?
I am an organ donor as well
I'm an organ donor on my license. Are you so if I die in New York?
They're gonna they're gonna find my ID my wallet pull it out and say he's an organ donor
And they're gonna send me to a hospital and chop me into pieces. Ah
Not cool and say little kids like some kid in Chicago needs a heart
No, that is not cool. That is cool. No, it's not that they're killing somebody for them. I mean, it's horrible
Well, no, if he didn't do it, I'm a doner, I'm a dite, I'm a doner, Dice wasn't.
Yeah.
Well, that's fine, that's good.
I got out of it because of that.
Ah, that's good.
You got out of ticket?
Yeah, and I was like, yeah.
And he was like, that's really kind of you.
And he's like, I'll let you go on a warning today.
Because all he did was like, I run red lighters.
I was yellow light, I don't know.
It was not even in the wrong.
Not quite.
He's making quota.
Anyways, and he's like yeah, it's really nice that you're an organ donor
I'm an organ donor too, and then you just went off about it, and then you let me go
So awesome be an organ donor and save some lives. What do you need your body from and you don't need all of it and I
Need it
Well for what to do to rot with or to burn with like it's fine. I'm just saying if I could save some poor kids life
Well, yeah on a waiting list for a long time
Yes, I had it no, of course, of course, I'm just kidding
I bet I would be afraid they'd want to top me up prematurely now because you need to be still alive and have your
But I know this lady and the yeah, okay guys. Well, she needed a heart transfer like a heart transplant
And so she got this heart of like this like a 21 year old gang member
It's like a gang member who like that and shoot out or something like that
She got his heart and that they I think she like feels like some of his memories or something like that
She always had like this weird and she's like a lady in her 60s and 70s pretty interesting
There's a few stories that are confirmed like that
Uh-huh certain parts and then they're just they feel like or act to have certain traits are pretty crazy
Yeah, like some organs might have like memory
People are walking around fake hair like extensions, not fake hair, but real human hair and it's other
And trauma and they're just carrying around and going I'm so beautiful
Well, you know, did you use that in magic that you do use like the other
petitions and stuff that collect the hair and stuff and we use the magic rituals and stuff
Kind of scary sometimes to think about
Okay, so I don't need something I never used on you before that sounded really bad
Well, let's do it
I'm just kidding
Any new decks and board of these I think I don't like a lot of the ducks. I have like that
I don't use a lot of them. I guess I'd go grab for them
Too many animal decks
Well, when you when you're telling it's real big you can like know like some giveaways and stuff like that
You know and like, you know, some of like you some of the decks are doing whatever you'd like to do
I've got some plans. Awesome, not big enough to do like anything crazy though.
There's like a winner for that every couple weeks.
Yeah, I mean you can actually you know
You hope you like when I get monetized sometime because then you can do members only shows and then you can like you
Kind of can have contests and stuff like
The lady I know clumsy would you like have contest you like say guess how many decks I have ever got closest to the number?
She sent a deck to so I have one of those decks that she won I won from her
It's really cool. It's called Guardians of the night, but I don't have an only fan. So you're a liar
Joe is another page. Imagination that I have one, you know, you can fantasize about whatever you want, but no, I don't have it.
Oh my God, you want me to go put makeup on? That's retarded. It's like five in the morning and I just went and checked cows for like four hours and sauced it.
And I worked, or I guess I ended up working a little bit last night because I went there.
I just really bummed out, so I just need to not don't make fun of me right now. Okay. One more time. I'm just not having a nice day, okay?
Sorry Paige
Here to cheer myself up not to you guys cheer me up most time
You hear me up
I look like a nightmare though right now I get it like a daymare a morning mare
Okay, so these are what they look like like
You see you know that it is
Hmm spirit animal cars of it. Oh, yeah, I think I have the deck I have is for the same person
I call it read. It's like a different deck, but it's like cool
She's
She's the AI for the her dining it
Yeah, I for her like traffic. Yeah for designing it
I think that's what she said in her book for her cars
ever
No, she put it she put them I mean it is an art to put it together like she's like, you know
I think I haven't I think I will say it on her back of the book. I have it says like she would
Do some kind of AI on it, but she knows but she made it, you know, yeah
I'm planning on actually making a deck and I would like to use AI in it. It's a stick right here
Uh, as guardians of is it? No, it's actually actually a different person. It's not by a different person. Okay, but but uh
Yeah, this one's yeah, I have that one cool
Yeah, is that my person?
Did these are wait?
Her name is M. J. Lane. All right. Actually none of that. That's the uh, that's the who made the cover
But I think that she made the whole thing. Okay
What the heck
Well, I remember it says something about like design the deck with it
How'd you know this deck this is like one of my older ones too this and the intended map I think I got together they really
Don't ever use that one very often either that's awesome or my oh and I have a bunch of stone
You have to connect with it back, you know, yeah
I just have different different like moods and stuff and then I pull out different text
But I've been using pretty much the same ones for a little bit. I'll get bored of them soon though. Probably
So we had the snake spirit come out with the parrot spirit
number 55 number 45
The snake spirits is time to heal and the parrot spirits has watched your words
Let's read that
If you want what I have to because I've never really opened this book
Where are you Steve's friends?
I have pasties really bad now for my weed only crepes
Do-do-do-do-do-do
Where'd Alex go? Did you kick him off or did he leave? No, he just left. I think he just left.
You're a good Alex. That was a good, that was one of his better appearances. He was just like so. Yeah, that's not, I like that.
Relatively, right?
I like it. Yeah, I love being
It's one of us my favorite that's funny. I actually don't care about the so let me call me e t e t the other day
So did the little e t finger for them, and I can't ever run see it anymore
And sometimes I'll just look at myself and look camera when I'm big when we're doing live is not just one first don't laugh in
I can't see it about myself. It's fucking great. It's like easy. We're in pink lipstick
You're like a sexy
Great for Halloween. Okay, it's here
Not a bad idea. It's like the one time a year you can dress like a total slut and no one can say anything, right?
But a slutty ET what if you're like what dresses a slut with a ET head, that'd be funny.
Okay, okay.
Hey, come on over to this yoga.
I'm trying to find the page.
I would do it. How would I dress though? Like just wear a...
It's a really easy mask, and it's sexy, because sexy outfit is easy to ask, but it'd be funny.
It'd be hilarious.
My free energy, I'm just down to try new things, I guess.
Okay.
There's so much in this holy crepes. So time to heal. So your oracle message pretty much is that all of us need healing at times
And when snake spirit appears it's time to repair a renew and I just stuttered replenish yourself and your
vulnerable heart self-care and main work are needed so that your fatality and
Oh your fatality can arise
Give yourself the space to nourish on your own well-being, and vulnerability is a necessary
for friendships and partnerships to work, which means all of us will have tender emotions
at the times at this time.
Be gentle with yourself and others now, shed the past and step up into the new way of being
This might be a good time to honor the work that you've done to heal, grow, and repair any damage within you.
And within those you care about.
This is really repetitive, eh?
And within your community.
Celebrate together how far all of you have come on your healing journey,
and that all of you, and that all the life that all of you have created.
Dude, I swear I'm not, like, having issues with my, like, I can read.
The way that they cut certain words off and the way that they have
Pugsuated this makes no sense to me
Do you ever find you fall into that? It's like just broken up words or like
Yeah, I think I think sometimes maybe AI like old AI wrote it or something. I'm not sure
But it's like or she just doesn't do perfect English
I think it's my eyes create like these weird like unless to the rivers in the in the words
Does that make sense down the beach? Yeah, you're really fine. You're really fine
I got you just irritates me. So all of that together. So, yeah
This might be a good time for you to work on or to honor all the work that you have done with your growing and repairing any damage within you and
Celebrate together and like make a big make a big thing of it
You know, we should do an appreciation like night on me you beat his channel like everybody's
Unactive, you know and or well my family doesn't give a shit really so
But I'm burdening yourself from anything that no longer supports your wellness, prosperity,
positive relationships, and well-being, and the open door for the healing to occur.
So it's like that's the only door that you're wanting open right now.
That's the only window you're going to crack, and it's the healing window.
So the protection message. No matter how much you may have lost or how you have been disappointed,
you are called by Snake Spirit to shed the past and practice radical self-acceptance now.
Only by forgiving yourself can you move on, regardless of whatever anyone else is ready for.
When your tender new skin first becomes exposed, you may feel uncomfortable.
Love yourself anyways and remain.
Okay, remain vulnerable anyway.
You have been weak, but now that you are becoming strong and developing wisdom and you will
do better in the future.
Thanks spirit reminds you that-
Hearts can be so easily wounded and apologies and amends go a long way
But self-forgiveness for your role in what happens can help you heal the most
Remember it is the one who has been wounded who has often the greatest power to help others heal
So it's like what I always say right you have to feel to heal to learn to teach you do you have to go through things right?
so for you
Next next transform, you know, they should their skin they should girls can
Wow, that's a beautiful card. I like the beautiful thing out the back of that
And then the parrot came up with it if you want it
It's that it went a car, right?
The colorful one the rainbow, huh? It's like the red at the red and uh, yeah for colors
Beautiful and the one that it's on
Rio is what they're blue diamond or some what are they blue something blue
parrots. Oh yeah and they're from Brazil are they
Rio de Janeiro. I think we at least have an Amazon parrot it was green with like a
One, let me just say one, three, six, I should put my graph in.
Three, two, okay.
So parrot spirit, watch your words, oracle message for this card.
What are you saying to yourself and what message are you repeating?
Is it something that makes you feel good about yourself or that reminds you of your strengths and...
potential. Parrots mimic the sound around them. And when the parrot's
beard appears, it's time to be more mindful of your
self-talk, psyche, and its qualities.
What do you say to others?
Are you repeating what you've already used?
What? Are you repeating what you truly believe?
Remembering to speak with light and love can become a habit be generous with compliments and thanks
Affirming all it is good to what's good so that you're loving hold on you guys. I can't see worth a shit
Sorry
So be generous with compliments and thanks and affirming all that is good so that your loving healing words will be heard throughout the jungle.
Cutting through the noise and inspiring others all around.
Listen for the words that remind you of the strength, abundance, and joy in your life and in the world around you.
And then repeat them, affirming what is real, true, and maturing to the soul.
As you leave a story to tell words matter so choose ones that lift up and inspire others to remember the beauty that
surrounds them and
vice versa
So are you aware of what you're saying to yourself and others perhaps spirit shows up in a reminder to heal the wounds. Oh
Yeah, to heed the wounds
Heed, what does that mean again? Oh, yeah, they're like pay attention to pay attention to them. That's right
So again, paying attention to this
Flow from your mouth your keyboard or your pen
So be mindful of the beliefs that you have initialized or internalized
Are they what you choose to believe? Are you communicating with integrity?
Parrot spirit wants you to listen to what you say and your motives for saying it
Very interesting
Makes me think also a little bit about like
self-talk is like what you it's a lot of times repeated like what you hear from other people you'll not feel like
They'll put their so it's not like you're saying it, but if anyone said that so it's like you'll
Tell yourself that right? It's like so we have to be careful like we just repeating things we
ourselves
But sounds okay. Yeah
Interesting thank you so much for that if you want a car for the animal deck
I'll pull you on yours like what for the animal this other animal deck like that
It's more of a the guardian of the night
Well as for one
Yeah, go ahead. Is it that's the same deck I have?
Yeah, no, it's a oh, yeah, yeah, I think you have you said you have this deck this guardian of the night
She went with in there for stuff. Yeah
Oh, let's pop down. Okay. Okay. You got the ace of swords. So this is the truth
Okay, you know the ace of swords. I'll read from the book, but there's a beautiful ace of swords
It's a bats right there the looks me a laurel crown, which is a victory. There's also the sword
Ace of swords is usually associated with truth. It says life is going to trigger you a curve ball
When the Ace of Swords energy is present, you will have the clarity to see an obstacle forming.
You will know you need to plan for a challenge. The Ace of Swords calls on you to seek out the truth behind your circumstances.
Use your logical mind to find the answers. When you see your situation
objectively, you will better understand your role and as a result you will be able to move with swift determination to resolve any conflicts.
This is a challenge with preparation and commitment you will win.
When the Ace of Swords appears, your situation will benefit from a little honesty.
It may not be easy, but you will find those who can support your cause will listen when you speak your truth.
Leading to the Ace of Swords energy, we need to clearly articulate your needs, express the certainty, and operate from a place of integrity.
The Ace of Swords bring one warning. Be careful of illusions that may mask themselves as answers as they make cloud your vision.
You will benefit from using a combination of logic and intuition. The bat's superpower is the ability to travel across the darkest skies with precision and grace.
Call on the bat's energy when you need to navigate through any moments of darkness when you need to hone in on a clear path to success.
When you connect with the bat, you tune into your intuition, you can feel the vibration
around you and make quick, decisive decisions that will come naturally.
The bat offers grace and flexibility and will guide you when you need to change your course
on short notice or if you are expected to fly higher than anticipated.
The grasshopper is a symbol of being true to yourself, of living your life, not imitating
others as your life is about to take a leap forward.
It says bat, magical, intuitive, quiet, esoteric.
There you go.
Beautiful.
I love that for you.
Do you like that?
This sweetheart.
I love you Paige.
Oh, okay.
Hmm.
Do you like it?
Yep.
I did.
That's beautiful.
I was just taking a picture.
Hmm.
Oh, it's good good cards. We've had some really good readings actually for like ourselves and other people
Actually, it's the first one I've had in a while, but you always pull me a card, which is lovely
I don't buy your reading from like Etsy and I was like no I'm not gonna do that cuz I was looking at cards. I
Like some of the unique like personalized decks that people have made on there. It's a really nice and
Nice too, but I could make some of that. I
Love it. Yeah
Hey, I don't know if you ever looked but on on team move
They do have like a lot of decks that are like they charge you five and ten dollars for that are like, you know
Very expensive some of them but some of them are gonna be maybe
Different prints of the deck and like that, but it is what's worth it
If you just want to take some some that's just very out of my price range
It was nice by five decks for like 20 bucks, you know, so I'm gonna have like five decks
Even if they're not the nicest deck still I think
As long as it's a complete deck and you know, I don't know, I don't think it's the quality of the deck necessarily, but it makes the reading, I think it's the reader, right?
The reader, the energy, of course.
I'm looking at the, I'm reading about the fool, I'm gonna like, you know, have this book about the, um, the tarot, and it's about the, can I read about the fool a little bit?
Okay, it says red feather and cap not a worry ridden across his face and fancy dress the full walks chin and air to the edge of the
Cliff a white dog lapsed by his feet
Behind him are snow-capped mountains a bright yellow sky and a white sun
Slung over one shoulder the bundle of the all's earthly possessions on the other hand between two fingertips. He holds a single white rose
Says the fool the fool's a harbinger of new beginnings when this card appears the forthcoming life path is one of unbound potential and
Beginnings that come with a deeper spiritual meaning
The white Sun represents power and a strong vibrant aura emanating from the speaker
But the seekers power has not yet created will do substance of value. It is about power, but no product
compared, number one, the magician, a figure whose harness power was constructively or destructively when in the reverse.
When the fool appears in a reading, it is about to point in a seeker's life when the next step could either suddenly seeker flying into the air over the cliff
with a present of accomplishment or falling down hard from naivety.
The temperament of the fool is one pure in spirit, open-hearted, and like a child, innocent and naive.
There is a Peter Pan mentality, boastful, careless, a bit arrogant,
addressing a willful refusal to take responsibility, or be mature.
Yet the seeker is a beautiful, creative soul, perhaps.
someone with the foolish belief in the attainment of impossibly beautiful goals.
There is a trace of swagger and flamboyance in the fool.
He is a swashbuckler. The fanciful style of the fool's clothing suggests
one who is attached to superficiality, a seeker with great pride in his or her attractiveness.
The fool card can also mean a choice is being offered, one of great significance.
The choice before the seeker may seem minor, but a choice could affect the lifetime,
so it should be with caution, otherwise the seeker might fall off the edge of the cliff.
Compare, there are cards in the minor arcana that also indicate presentations of choice
between the speaker, such as the Seven of Cups or Two of Swords.
The minor arcana choice cards indicate matters of immediate concern from day to day life,
when the fool is drawn and represents the choice being offered, that choice will have
a profound impact on the entirety of the speaker's life or the progression of his or her spirituality.
Compare the lovers which can also suggest the choice being offered the lovers card the fool or the choice often has ethical undertones
With the fool the choice is not over ethics or morality
It is a choice between two forks in the path one fork will lead to attainment flying transcending the cliff
the other will lead to likely the mice falling off the cliff and
So that's that's basically it interesting about the fool. So I also considered one of the most powerful cards in the deck
But it's also, you know as the numerical value of zero that in zero
It's infinite possibilities because it zeroes like there's like a hole or a circle, right?
Everything comes out of that portal maybe
Yeah, I might spay it out a little bit. Hey Vader. How are you?
How's everyone doing tonight?
I'm pretty feeling better another to eat some food
I was giving it a little hangry and, uh, itchy, I get a little bit, I get a bit itchy sometimes. I'm sorry.
Hey, Catzilla, you just woke up later? Wake up! Why don't you go do a little make-up?
So what's planned for what's we got going on today? It's Friday. Happy Friday. Happy Friday psyches. Happy Friday
Um, I have to work
230 I think
And then probably nothing
Do you sleep during the day like right now ready this around this time or do you are you like?
I will go nap like I used to try to anyways most time I can but
I haven't been able to sleep very, I haven't been able to sleep very much lately or nap or like anything.
Just sleep is just not my friend right now, but yeah, I do sleep or I'd be dead.
Yeah, I'm saying I sleep during a day a lot. Like I usually when the sun comes out then I like to like
just go under the covers and I wake up in like the afternoon probably like four or five.
I was like, oh it's already time to, for the night it's like I would set my days to my night
I
See vampire hours
I was just gonna say that
vampire
I went to suck the blood. I don't really
Put around and like toss and turn a lot in your sleep or do you have to fall asleep on your back?
I like to sleep on my couch and so I like to sleep against like what there's one of the usually one of the cats
Cuddling under it, but I like to sleep like kind of like next to something and like against against it
But then I don't have like someone to live, you know, I'm like a big man, too
I love to I just want to cuddle like a man. You know, it's like that's all I want, but I
Don't want to have sex. I just want to cuddle
So my boyfriend better want to make out he's really bitter when I go
Watch it gets smoked a lot of pot and like watch Netflix and
That's all I want to do. I hardly ever want to go out
Let's take me to a nice restaurant. You got some weed. Good. I got some we too. It's half of baked left
I think oh, oh, it's all spread out, but there's some in there. I'm sure
So yes
Oh, yeah, sitting right in front of the camera.
Because we're back, you're not going to go.
Good girl, Beans.
You figured out where you said to get the attention, right?
You used to love me, don't you, Beans?
Yeah.
You good girl?
She's so soft.
I
Just a primordial pouch
You little kangaroo a kangaroo kitty when she runs like swings it could blacken both of her eyes
Really get your I mean burping which is a tush in my face, honey
For you, what are you doing today?
Well Saturday, so I'm considering I don't know. I'm like I'm able to
Well, I'm really happy that I clean my house. It looks so good right now. I'm just like
Enjoying being a clean house and like I can't believe it's like clean now
I
Couldn't does the people that held me they like clean the floor and it was like that was gonna be the hardest part
It's like scrubbing the floor cuz she's like it was like totally like a different color the bathtub was a totally different color
Oh my god
Stuff gets so dirty. So yeah
Okay, the cat is the cat is saying cats are so awesome independent and then it's Friday. Yes, it is Friday. Hey, well, no, man
How are you it's Friday?
Friday it also is known as
Venus day. It's a
Aphrodite's day
Fray is day. It's Fred, but you know same same basic archetypal goddess goddess of beauty in love
You know, you know, you in Japan they have a disease or in Indonesia they have the G sound and they go young, young
Young
That's what the frame makes that sound. Yeah
They just want that meomics and they want you to deliver. Please deliver it. Yes
Why do you have plenty? Oh
Yeah, I'm definitely a little tired today and everything's just catching up with me. That's probably why I'm so like feeling emotional too. I think it's just
lack of
Everything in life right now, but it's fine
There's this person saying that I can make $24 an hour with kick. Wow. How do I do that?
I mean, that's amazing. I would love to do that 24 dollars. I mean with 3,000 subscribers. I don't know
How does that does that work? I wonder I wonder I wonder wonder maybe it will some people do make money on it
Like you make money on
Tick-tock I have a tick-tock account now, but it's like I don't know how to make any followers. So it's kind of like
It's complicated a little bit
But as soon as you have a thousand you can monetize tiktok
And maybe I'll do like little shorts on there like where I just like
Do like really quick little readings or the quick like card
Descriptions or it's all pretty content on and see what happens
having fun
Yep
Cool to be multiple platform streaming
But they have really strict rules on six octo. I look you can't even be like it's like you can't have weird
You really can't be too weird. I said, I was like, oh my god, what did it mean?
When the cat needs help who will seek it right? Hey, thank you everyone. Hey Grim Reaper network. How are you?
I'm looking for something to share with you.
Let me see, if you're a fairy tale,
let's see if there's a few fairy tales.
It says, okay, do you like to hear a fairy tale?
I think these are more like new age fairy tales,
but they look kind of good, let me see.
This is called a tale of two sisters.
It says, in the beginning, there was oblivion, a vastness and an abyss comprised of darkness
and nothingness, until there were two sisters.
One of them was made from the internet connectedness of all things, a precipice of stories, a treasury
of things gone and things to come.
Her name was Cosmos.
I hate it, Vader.
It says, the other day, the other was made from the tricorn of darkness, black magic
waiting to be born, inkwells of feral power and rebel thoughts.
Before they had floated into the abyss, as all celestial beings were left to do in the end, their father told them to go to a binary system
to never ever let go of each other.
He warned them that together they could build everything, but apart nothing could exist.
So the two came together and imagined a tapestry of moving, living stars that inhaled around each other.
They pictured impossible things like planets, helped thousands of different beings,
and balls of fire keep warm, and whole atmospheres help them breathe.
and this was how the love of two sisters wrote the first ever eternal poem into magical living
existence a single poem a christened the uni first oh that's beautiful um okay whispers from from the
Where are the stories for the wicked girls, the ones who are told perfection is a lie?
Where are the legends fashioned from nuance, the ones that cause the hero and the villain to blur lines?
Where are the myths for darker things, the ones of us who were never snow white pure?
Where are the lessons for naughty children, the ones who want to be lost in the forest and folklore?
If you're looking for secrets, you will find them here. These words have been resurrected from old fairy tales ruins.
This is a place where those stories can be reborn from the wreckage of mercy, things more human than humans. Hey, Rizzo.
Interesting.
The Queen, I said this is called the Miller's Daughter, she says.
The queen addresses her firstborn after the fall of Rumpelstiltska, says maybe magic ends with me and it will never cross your path
But I want you to remember that survival is an art. The world is falsehood
So you rely on your smarts. Princes fail all the time, passions sometimes goes cold, and
princesses on days of fortune can turn straw into gold.
kind kings become greedy and dragons can have soft souls.
Aries cast the wrong spells, mermaids can be drowned, goblins and trolls can be heroes,
and giants can fall without a sound. And even the darkest things can be defeated
once their names are spoken out loud.
And it says, half of Ruppelstiltskin seeks redemption.
Half of Ruppelstiltskin speaks to the miller's daughter.
Since tearing myself in two, the half of me that remains has been learning how to grow and crafted apology worthy of you.
Sorry. Okay. It says, I offer no tricks, only regrets for not understanding in my childhood that guilt is sometimes necessary, a way to remember good and never forget.
I have heard that excuses make for bad apologies, so I'll stop there. All I want to say is this, I'm sorry, but I do not say it for forgiveness's sake.
You're welcome
It says there are no asterisks here, the feelings are completely valid, you are under no obligation
to pardon me, I have yet to earn it for putting you through fear.
What I'm trying to say is, I know now that becoming kind is worth every single exhausting
effort and sometimes it takes a thousand years.
Today I apologize to someone I owe an ocean full of immense to, tomorrow I will teach
myself the kindness alphabet from scratch.
If this is not what an apology looks like, if this is not what growth looks like, I do
not know what they are.
And then it says, why tinkerbell quit anger management?
I have to give up on their remedies.
They keep saying, they keep trying to make me less angry,
but I refuse to surrender my rage
because whole kingdoms have already spent millennia
trying to keep women subdued
only to be discarded in the old age.
My fury gets things done, it has saved lives,
it has made the world listen.
Where I could not speak, my anger has screamed.
Think Helen of Troy when they took her freedom.
Think of...
The Ronnie of John C leading rebellions to give Joan of Arc armies
Leading armies on what she dreams
Now I love my tinderbox heart so easy to light up all it takes is half a spark the woman's anger could change the world
I know mine can and this is not a gift. I will give away. I am small and I'm angry
It is how I channel my energy and I like me that way
That's her picture
Kind of looks like page a little bit
Hold on
Sorry page your microphones a little bit echoing a little bit. I don't know if you're trying to talk. I'm sorry. Is it better?
It's echoing it's my oh, yeah, it's better. It's better. Yes
It probably echoes off this box that are off me. Yeah, probably this boxing. Sorry
Okay, it's just stable and it doesn't wiggle around so I thought it would be worse if it did
Well, did you like those, the way I read them all, or did you read them on Kaka?
Well, let me, ooh, some of these are good, so this is called the stepmother's tale, it says.
It says people are going to betray you the way Judas betrayed Jesus, the way
Brutus betrayed Caesar, and you will love them anyway. And betrayal comes in so
many different shapes and forms no one ever tells you how death, too, is a form
of betrayal. How life, too, betrays you by robbing you of the person you depend on,
your soulmate.
Says she didn't start that way. None of us is truly born evil evil is man-made
Once she was a beautiful young girl who grew up working in her father's flour mill a good daughter with a light heart
Those were expected to be during that time if you never complain no matter how hard or burdensome the work was
When she turned 18, she began to accompany her father to the market to sell the flower
they made in a rich, handsome merchant saw her, this lovely, hard-working young woman
with an easy smile. Unlike most of the men of his time, he was progressive. He thought
asking her father's permission immediately to marry her, he asked permission from him
first, and then her father, if he could court her. He wasn't handsome, but he had a soft
heart. Stop looking at his eyes and gentle hands. Hold on. And it was long into their
that they married and had two little daughters and as fairy tales like this go should have lived
happily ever after but life instead had a tale of woe and plan for this woman and her girls.
Soon after the seventh birthday of her second daughter, her husband took ill and died and
whilst grieving for the man she loved she learned how unkind the world is to a single mother of
where she once had plenty of comfort to live in and provide her children with,
soon the debt collectors started peering at every hour and a quarter.
She looked for work but found nothing suitable for the mother of two small children.
Months faded to years and slowly they grew more and more to shoot,
and so she did the only thing that she could do in dark desperation.
She found another man when she did not love, but he was grieving his lost love too,
and married him, promising to give his orphan child the mother.
Desperation turns people sour, and she saw in that life as an open wound, a shallow promise,
a dark thing that should have loved her, but instead tried to drown her.
Her beauty fading, she recognized that she had failed to pass on her looks to her two
daughters.
And now she knew how important it is for women to be beautiful, as it is the only currency
she truly had in the world, she became even more bitter.
So when she saw Cinderella in her goodness and her beauty, all she could think is, that
used to be me.
the more she wanted to take it from her to Cinderella would understand how awful life can be.
She is cool to Cinderella because she wants to teach her in her own terrible misguided way
that life is not going to be kind just because you're pretty and yet your beauty is your only
true currency. If I could just teach you how to be cautious and cool instead of so naive and kind,
I can stop you from becoming yet another me. Wow. That's kind of crazy. Kind of dark. I'm sorry,
Wow, that was yeah
No, I know it's like I don't think it's like some of these books. I got probably for free
but uh somewhere and so it's kind of a trap shoot as to where
They are what they're really about or like I don't know but it's I love fairy tales though, and this is kind of like
modern
Stuff that seems kind of a little bit dark
They're short and sweet. Short and sweet and dark.
I'm going to do one more. Okay, so I think this one.
It's the Shahar-Zad. Have you heard of Shahar-Zad?
It's like an Arabian knife. Yep, oh yeah.
It says a clever woman is more lethal than a freshly crafted magic wand and that is why she's feared
She's unpredictable and unpredictable is another word for threats when a woman wears her wealth. That is why they try
Just snatch her power away vilify her by saying she's dangerous manipulative insane
With no and the fight out of the daughters early so they don't turn out like her the vixen the vamp the witch
They have so many words to convey the dislike of this woman because she holds her own on a planet clearly not built for humans
Like her but how else is the woman supposed to survive if not by her wits?
Look at the tale of the sultan Shah Yar, who got fragile masculine energy, punished a thousand innocent women by marrying them and then murdering them the next day for a single act of unbatefulness committed by his wife.
And no one could stop the strife being crammed down on the women of the kingdom until he met his match in a girl arm with nothing better than her wits and a thousand stories, one for every girl he killed.
It says imagine the girl Shaharizad visiting the dead lake where the bodies were drowned speaking with the women like they were her sisters
If it ends with me
I promise you it ends with me and no other girl was ever harmed after she told
Sharia her never-ending story full of spirit tales of the women
He so mercilessly murdered until he couldn't help with being trans by her spell open sesame a girl becomes a queen
Open sesame of this year's daughter out with the king
Open Sesame. A crafty woman is stronger than a band of 40 powerful thieves. Open Sesame.
This is the oldest kind of witchcraft that has ever lived and never leaves. Open Sesame. Open Sesame. Open Sesame.
Okay, this is called
Wonderland villain.
Says, yes, I am dreadful and I am desolate and I am difficult to digest.
No, I do not apologize for the things that I am for what makes me today.
I am the dark thing that you'd love to hate, now the tear that keeps you awake.
Call me gross, call me stupid, call me disgusting, none of those names can ever hurt me again.
I am a thousand treacherous things.
I was not made to be lovely for you, I was made to eat monsters for me.
I never lied, I never claimed to make mistakes.
Not to make mistakes, I never said I was a saint.
When you bullied me with those names as a child,
you made a horrible mistake.
This is not silence you saw in response to you.
That was me putting on war paint.
You can hate me for it, for I am both nightmare and sin.
I wear thunder underneath the skin.
I am both storm and calm.
I am the queen of all hearts I consume.
You made me this thing that you do not like.
Now nothing will save you when you look in the mirror,
when you try to sleep at night.
Crazy
Pretty good. Hey, there's Arthur. Say how do you
Arthur are you a mod yes artists now mod congratulations Arthur
My father's a weirdo in a creep
Yeah, well, he was I he was a mother for a long time, but he's back
Yeah
A lot of the mod family is growing. I just need good people I trust here, right?
We've transitioned to bedtime story streamers, Joe said.
So,
I'm kind of introduced though, like some kind of like
new twist, how a hero becomes a villain. Okay, it says
Prama left untreated has the capacity to make a villain out of you
No one understands how little boys who save villages who become war heroes who have fathers that just expect them to be brave
No matter what the cost to be the insides of their mind become villains
Without even trying to how then hearing the word no becomes a trigger how love rejected becomes cautiously pierced
Self-worth dissolved and how the thought of losing love and it being given to someone else makes this entire facade
You have carefully constructed fall how you weren't always the arrogant self involved
obsessive bad guy, how that is just the way you project yourself to keep the vulnerable
little boy hidden, that is what is expected of you, the strongest man in the whole village,
how obsession is a symptom of a dark thing that's untreated, how it truthfully under
your brash surface you have kept a beast inside you secretly hidden, and what seeing the girl
you love hand over her love to someone who looks just like the demon you fight every
night does.
This is how a hero like Gaston becomes the devil in the story which could have been
about his only chance at finding love.
Take this as a reminder, not all heroes wear capes.
Somewhere darkness, somewhere wounds.
Let's see.
What's up?
Where'd you get this?
Oh, this is on, I got it on Amazon.
I don't know if I bought it or we got it for free
We give away a lot of free stuff, but it's pretty good
It's called a dragon which is daughter
Yeah, it says
As a child, in every book she ever reads, the dragon, which his daughter chooses the side of the dragon, the witch, the evil sorcerer, because from an early age she knows that just because other people may say someone is bad, it does not mean that there is not some good in them, too.
As a teenager, she learns how inheritance is a cold creature and how children sometimes
inherit their parents' troubles and heartache and other times their parents' flaws and
mistakes.
She learns how intimate she must be with loss to grow up as her mother's child.
She learns how to adore her own gifts, exquisite yet terrible things her mother gave her, and
only then does she realize how the daughter of a villain in hindsight can become sometimes
the luckiest of them all.
taught love to defend themselves and had to learn the hard way how to survive.
Her mother taught her how to breathe fire so that if they ever threw her to the wolves
she could set their hearts aflame. And that's her picture.
Yeah, these are nice and short and sweet. It's like,
That's my interesting ones.
It's called the evil queen. It says, that's not a couple pages.
It says, oh, dearie me, did you come here looking for a damsel in distress?
A queen patiently waiting for a dashing knight to save her from herself?
Do you really think there was going to end with you playing the hero by bringing the kindness out of the evil queen?
Look again, love. Someone has lied to you about my hidden virtue. I have always loved being the beast.
And there's one called Gretel after Hansel says did anyone ever tell you what happens if you kill a wish before you grow up?
that you would be part of yourself in that storybook place,
saccharine suite with bitter memories,
your half fairy tale half girl,
with parents who chose to abandon you,
a brother who swore he would never leave,
and found a wife and left you,
and here you are picking yourself apart,
breadcrumbs by a breadcrumb,
trying to learn how to swallow survival,
but part of you never left a witch's door.
You still have the grit and determination
that stopped the child eating a monster and her tracks.
That wasn't Hansel, that was you.
damaged though you are, the girl is still there. Our story didn't begin end to end
because men were once trusted to have left them. We were made whole to start
with. Independent tales of strength and madness. What I'm trying to say is Gretel,
you define yourself without your brother. You define yourself with your courage,
which was already imprinted on your bones. No one taught you how to survive.
Darling, you did that on your own. Even without him, you can bring down monsters.
Wow
They're really short to the point, but they're like they're really there's quick
Yeah, they are right. Yeah, they're definitely deep
Really, please
This is called Lessons from the Not-So-Wicked Witch for Dorothy.
It says, I once knew a girl like you, and if somebody had told her these things, she
too would get the kind of fairy tale ending where she was happy.
Instead, she had the fairy tale ending of a villain.
She turned out you see to be me.
It says, when they tell you how unkind I was, how cool I was, how ready they were to get
rid of me, and how much of a kindness you had done by getting rid of me, I want you to know
that I was once a girl just like you full of dreams and ambitions.
I became this way because of a malicious lie, the stories other people told about me.
Not a single one of them was true.
They called me wicked because I refused to become a pretty little thing that simply entertained
Don't let them judge you by your appearance. Your appearance will change over time, dearie.
And do not want people in your life who fall in love with your vivid blue eyes
when they turn a faded blue because those are the kind of people who will leave you.
Remember that your heart and your brain are far more important than the way you look.
They will stop the wrong people from guiding you. Your heart will see the lies in their souls.
Your brain will be able to hear the lies when they spill from their tongues. You are better than that.
With the mind and heart full of bravery that helps you set free the lion, the scarecrow, and the tin man,
you are more valuable and important to the world than you will ever know.
You have such softness in your smile it shows your true heart. Don't let anyone take that from you.
They took from me and made me hard. All I'd ever do is bring me sadness. Your softness will only bring you smiles.
that no one ever reduces your prettiness no matter how good of a friend, partner, soulmate, parent,
teacher, friend they are. Definitions of you are for you to make and for you alone. Beauty without
kindness and bravery is just a pretty empty shell, my dear, and you can find plenty of those on the
beach. People use them to decorate their rooms, so I hope you aspire to be so much more than just
beautiful. I hope you aspire to be so much more than a pretty little thing that decorates the room
That's that was quite fun
And I like the way that they're worded
Yeah, it's like poetry, you know, it's like a very poetic definitely different. I love it
Raven my goodness man
Much why are you so obsessed with me
Here's your little cute little mouth.
Oh, I'm tired.
Wide open and just meowing at me.
Go play with your sister.
Go do cat stuff.
You're trying to be a person.
Is this fighting the process?
Oh, I found it.
This one's called The Trolls.
So this is perfect.
It says that we have talked about them before it appears their numbers have doubled have tripled and quadrupled since
But here it is the origin story that the monsters amongst us
With no princesses or prince the story vanished beneath bridges. There were once brewing beasts. We gave a different name
We called them trolls short for transformations failed to humans with hearts of souls with hearts and souls
So in desperation to save themselves from the dreadful damp, the low bridges, a rumor
broke loose, nailing the coffin into their lust, that collective shred of decency, that
devour a human's heart would give them what they need so they begin to prey on humanity.
but the more they tried to hurt us the more we fought back until one day we finally managed to
beat them back until the story became legend and the legend became myth. Yeah this is where the
story really begins. You see the trolls were never dead they were simply asleep inviting their time
waiting for us to forget them to leave them as fairy stories. When the first child turned on
his first computer a tremor was felt and that's why when they rose from their man-made prison hell
They wore new avatars and had learned to embrace their lack of empathy and morality instead
of hearts they now had devoured, hope, dreams, and entire human just being.
They seek out the depressed and find the lonely.
They make targets out of children and sow divisive seeds amongst friends and families
all through the words on the screen.
They make weapons, sticks and stones, shovels and buried dreams.
They break open souls, eat whatever happiness is left inside, and cause death and alivings.
Destroy families and cause loss.
Using just words, lies twisted into more lies.
We cannot hide from them cannot beat them back. We cannot turn them into stories again. You must face simple facts
They now live amongst us their bridges are burned and gone. They were armor made of code
Still lacking hearts no songs in their souls for them to truly hold
We cannot protect these our children from these evil beings
We can teach them how to protect themselves
You see the trolls may have taken over the internet's highways and chat rooms and Instagram Twitter Facebook
But they have forgotten something crucial that humans know all too well
A monster is only a monster if we allow it to live in our minds and swell.
So we teach our children now that even though monsters exist, the best way that we can defeat them
is to never give them influence over the way our minds make thoughts or over what our hearts express.
The hungry caterpillar, I don't have that handy, but you know, I do like that story too.
Hold on, here we go.
Oh, is it cute?
Yeah.
Yeah
Thank you, you like to be a song for trolls. Oh, yeah, I did have one. I did have a song like that. Yeah, thank you
Where did you put all that music that you mean?
All the music I can't I need to at least see if I can put it on my discord. I'll do it. I'll check right now
I'll check right now
My co-worker kept like catching the like back end of some of the just the tail end of some of the songs
But we could had it here the page like
Was that just singing about you and you're look you're what she called your YouTube friends. I was like, yeah
Why how did that happen? Who's doing it?
I want to hear it and then she keeps asking me if I got it or not. I'm like, no, he didn't put it. Okay
Yeah, typical man. I'm gonna look I'm gonna look I'm gonna look on this for I wonder if I can hopefully I can post audio files
There I'm not a hundred percent sure. I probably put them in though
I was trying to make videos
Yeah, just make some changes to stuff
Yeah, I know it's
There's so much
There's so many things that you gotta figure out how to like streamline all the AI with together
I hope they do some time we can put all the companies together
They're already kind of almost there you can ask chat tbt to draw to draw you stuff now it will
Create images for you banners. I'll talk all about advice for your business
Oh remember thing it always mentions like Lenore and Rudy like oh, let's just talk about Lenore and Rudy is so funny
It's like
You don't tell it what to say
No, it's like because I just I mentioned them before for like
Like this is like the songs and stuff and I said I told of my cast names are and so then I was like
Well, kind of like the investing suggestions for how to incorporate the cast into the show
It's a tablet and has a little lines for them like oh the Norris makes up the queen of the house
And it's just okay. It's like the only thing I was really say it's crazy
Discord, let me see if I can get onto the scores. I have just for here
And it's called what it's an app
The the app that does
No, it does what which would have to one
Does this stop this stuff for you like is an AI?
Yeah, it's called AI
It's like I write the lyrics on the chat TPC
I like tell chat TPC what I want the song to be about and I'll give some information about like put this in the song
like the names and stuff and something about the person and then we usually like
elaborate on that and then
Yeah, and then I pick up I take those lyrics I copy and paste them into the
music generator and then put the style
There's like a thousand styles you can choose from it makes it so long in that style like one minute. You can put it here
So let me see if I can post it. It's really. Oh, yeah, I can't post them here. So I'll see
Okay, see files. Hey, it's just okay. So it's like I put files
Okay, I can
I'm going to put the one, I'm going to put the one, the discord right now.
I think they're going to go on, so.
Okay, perfect.
I'm in.
They'll be there.
I'll be there.
Okay.
I'll just do the three that I see here right now, but I'll put the rest on to you.
I just think I can do three right now, but there's three.
Okay, there you go, hopefully that works, yeah, okay, so yeah, I'm getting a lot of people from the
of the
I'm glad it's making you listen I'm saying if he does it you know that's scary
world we're living in that's terrifying this song is gonna be terrifying let's
see what it comes up with what are you doing this morning don't be scared don't
be scared page it don't hold my hand go along for the ride just hold my hand you
Didn't say some shit I wanted to say
Let's see what he comes up with
Figure it out so so it's just like a song generator, right? That's the three I just does exactly you just say um
You say a couple things and then it makes a song about it basically
They're just give it key points and names and stuff and then correct and the AI takes over and gives you a choice of music like jazz disco
Whatever a million choices, but you just type in keywords and like what you kind of want it to be in the AI
Takes over and just makes this crazy song
It's pretty cool at the same time. It's like not weird. Yeah
I don't know anyone could do it
Well, I think yeah, and technology, but I don't like that because it's taken away from like human songs
Like humans using their brain to make one
No, but is it like the AI stealing or?
Logically
Just taking over the world and drawing drawings as well
and we know he's we've seen his drawings yeah I don't know what you look
you know what they I can do can suck his dick
well that probably yeah yeah AI's not gonna stop the loneliness problem on the couch
well
He's to go out to a bar or grocery store, which is where all our grandparents bar grocery store
I'm just kidding as a joke. It's like we're all over fucking no, it's true. You're right. You're right
But when not an online thing, you know, he's not like that though. No, he's not you know, he's not like that. So
No, you're right. Yes more fun up here with us than going to do that
Yeah, he's pouring bomb to enough to like not have to do that
Poor guy
That's what I'm scared to go on like how my life for a guy
Well here I'm gonna be to get like just the stuff I see it would else go through
I'm like, I don't know if I could can do that like on a busy night if everybody was in really bad mood and wanted to cook
Yeah, I could kick people off
But if I was trying to like host something or do games or I would just take a lot
and
How do you even just
Hard to let trust anybody never mind just you let people up there, and then they could fuck you around
Yeah, that's how you learn about humanity who you can't trust
Without the internet, you know, but
There's two people I trust one of us me the other's not you you can't trust no one no pretty much
If you look into a man's eyes in bed, and you having sex with him, and he tells you he loves you
He's lying. You still can't trust him, right? Isn't that crazy?
That's fucking crazy and this advice for us if I'm laying in bed with a woman, I love you so much and
then you know
Like who the fuck can you trust pretty much no one are we being pessimistic?
I mean, I'm obviously not like I agree with you. I'm just saying do you think I trust my page?
That's just my theory. You trust me. I trust you
Is it cuz I'm nice or cuz I haven't fucked you over
Both maybe
Are you just a good judge of character? You guys there? Yeah? Oh, it's a triple
Triple you both it's gonna have a guy. It's almost there. We're almost got the song
Almost completed our love song. Yes. You've almost got it. It's a real love song. We love it. I love it
I'm gonna love the love song
Hey, who made your guys?
No, the cartoon I lecture lecture made the the one with Alex and then the fish tacos when I was the lord of the group
But yeah lecture made the fish talk this talk was one. Oh, that's pretty funny
Yeah, okay, so it's just still creating it
I'll give you a hint. It's called it's a country song. Okay
Country song and it's called
Alex a break my heart might pagey pagey heart
No, it's funny called page your own knee broke out
Oh, country music fucking blows. Honestly, this is my least favorite, except for there's a couple songs right now that I'm really, really digging.
Three country songs.
Raven. Where's Raven?
She's right here. She's not near me right now, meowing in my fucking-
Thank god.
In my face, so just don't summon her it's called it's called page. Will you fall in love with me?
Okay, it's about
Okay
You don't hold my hand page and just go with it. You should be gonna be afraid like under the moon or something just hold my hand
Okay, I don't, okay, I feel like this is over.
I'm gonna call the call.
I'm gonna call you yourself, Alex.
It's ready, it's ready.
Hold on, let's see.
ready, I'm just one minute. I trust you the anticipation just killing you. Yeah, okay one second. Here we go
It's gonna be a wedding song and our honeymoon song and the first time we fuck song. Oh my god, don't talk to me like that, please
weird
Okay
Here we go
Okay, it's ready
Why are you doing this to us?
You're gonna lie. It's gonna be funny. It's gonna be funny. I'm already upset with it
It's never you heard it yet. It's already
Hush it hush it up missy and listen to a love song. We're gonna make love to this. Okay. Here you go. I see all the love
I call the fuck
Oh my god, what is this? It looks a hazard theme song
Sounds like Boss Hog is coming around the co-
No psych, what the fuck is this?
This is not a love song, dick.
Why can't you hear it?
I can hear it.
Yeah, no, make a new one bro. That sucks. I don't think I didn't hear a word of that and this for some reason God likes
No, thank God
song ever
Make a new song dick. I don't hear that shit ever again. Seriously. I told you make a love song
Okay
Okay, I think you might have to listen to it. Can you listen to the TV at all? Do you think?
On the TV?
Like on mine? Yeah. Or on your tablet or TV because it'll play through that probably.
I don't think you can hear on yours like we were talking on. I think it has to be on like the
Because a separate device. Are you able to turn on the show and another device?
Maybe I'll download the other version because that one probably was not the best one do I even want to hear it like
Yes, you what you do you do you do it's funny. It's funny. I swear. He just like interrupts it. He wouldn't even listen to it
It's like
Pricey
It's a TV Apple Box thing
Down here maybe?
No? Oh, yeah, it is right here.
Hold on.
Burn this out into the living room.
Um, where's the remote? That's always fun to find in a child's bedroom.
Well, obviously, it's easier than it ever has been. Perfect.
Now, her little room.
More joke girls, you know, get away, please
Okay
I got you be the I was like a beat up
I didn't have to find the link. Where is it?
Alright, it was all messed up. Let me see.
Thank you. I'll be right back.
Okay.
It's like a caveman waiting for this thing. Good morning everybody. Morning beats. Morning Vader.
Rizzo. Excited. Sassy.
Ghostface.
Who else that's it for now? I
Said good morning, Katie. Good morning. Easy. Yeah, I got the link now. Okay, so now ready for the here's the link
Okay, guys before you come up just listen to the song. Hey guys. Are you ready? Okay? Nope. Not quite yet
Just one second. Okay. Okay. No problem. You have it. We have a special Alex Allison Paige
Love song looks like it's not really love science. It's like will you will you?
like me Pedro. Also was not suggested by my idea. Yeah. So the Alice's request but he's like
couldn't even like give you a second to listen to you. I mean yeah maybe country but. Well
now I'm kind of nervous to listen to it because he lost his shit over it. He didn't hear one word
of it. He was like just like screaming over the whole time. I was supposed I mean he's like
But they'll think right after I play it. I'll put the link. Okay, so you too, but then just go to your channel and then mute the phone
Yep. Oh, and then yeah, then you can go mute this way. Yeah
Okay one second
Okay, okay, here we go
like the stage start to show Mike open wide truth in my voice can't fake this
oh that's not it hold on i'm sorry i put the wrong song oh my god i don't do that
oh what did i heard it not on my phone just now okay interesting
um okay so this is it here okay this is a fall in love song here we go this is it
One second, okay, here we go.
I've been missing in my sleep
He's gutting trout, he's eating steak, somewhere in the middle they both take a break, he'd trade his nightsticks for a fishing pole, chase her laughter like it's his patrol page, don't you know you're the catch of the day, and this cop's got one hell of a line to say.
That's good, I liked it, see Alex
It's kind of catchy
And I don't really like country but I can't nail that
I like that there's lots of cool shit that I like to do in there like fish is accurate, but
That's what I put, like I know like little things to say
Yeah, here's my style
I know how to like say to the AI so it like puts it, makes it good I think
AI is just doing the most
What's the secret? Why am I so happy? It's because
What's your like, because I go to a stream so when I get really unhappy, then it's like I usually get pretty happy after that
So I don't know
Hey, you seem to like the song. Will you marry Alex?
Sorry Alex bro. She said no
They're running away, they're running away bride. Oh boy. Hi, Bita. Good morning. Good morning. Good morning, sunshine.
Good morning to you. How are you doing today? Good? Yeah, how are you on page? Oh, poopy, but you guys are making it better, so we're all good.
Just fucking thoughts in my head, you know the stuff that creeps in all the things you said all the things you said
In a long time weren't they like actual lesbians in that they were they weren't they weren't they were
There was supposed to be but they were because they had that they were kissing in the video
But they they really weren't lesbians in real life. It was just like
90s wild to early 2000s
Crazy. What was it? What was it? What did they call it? I forgot. Like there's some Russian bands. Yeah
We know psyche loves them Russians
Love this Persian half Persian and half Russian girl
She looks like a famous singer, but she's actually very gorgeous.
Just watch her. She's fucking savage, like you can't fuck with her.
Just imagine the combo. It's fucking crazy.
She's like, you don't like it?
Did we see her up one time? Did you introduce her to us or something?
No.
Like 100 like 125,000 subscribers. I don't know. I just like I think I was watching you or somebody
and then I went up on vertical and then I saw her she's like a tarot card reader and I was like
who the hell is she she's like like
She was like getting she was like gangster. She was like, you know, like you're this you're that and but she's like pretty
She was like very very pretty so then I was like who's this and then I send it to fight you
Have you talked to her you didn't talk to her
That she like to do lives or does she do like the free tapes or live
This thing that is maybe a good idea for you on page to do, she'll go down the line and go from like Aries to Torres to like Pisces and do like a quick reading for all the signs, you know.
I was thinking about doing that actually like one of these days because it is easy to just do some air signs and then you just do a quick message for each one of each sign and each element, right?
Yeah, because that way like the chat everybody has a sign, right? So I was like, oh, yeah, that's my sign
It gets people to engage and exactly
You know, yeah, that's it. Hey, it is it is quite time-consuming. It takes a couple out
I'm gonna do the ones I see they figure
Yeah, but that'll be just like if you just want to focus on that they'll be like
Yeah, or to do that with or you can do a quickie
Yeah, that's a great idea.
That was my buddy KP when we when I first started kind of going like live with him and stuff too
just doing collaborations not that I should we didn't show my face or anything really but anyways
we were doing those and um
And because it was so detailed for like both of our sides to do it
It did take quite a while
But I think that if you just kind of not breeze through it, but if you did
keep a time limit for each and you just knew what you were doing, what cards you were using,
kind of keep them all equal and then you could probably breeze through it.
Yeah, but the super chats were crazy. It was just like constantly getting super chats. So yeah,
I'm definitely looking for that. Thank you so much.
Thank you. Why did you horrify page with that awful fucking music with Alex? Do you want to give us all nightmares?
Yeah, and then he like started screaming at me when I like when he did it and then I even hear one word of it
He starts screaming. I don't like it. Like it's like
Break I was like I just like fucking just try so excited for his screams at me
She's Alice. Come on. Well, yeah. So, yeah, what's today's
friday? Maybe that's one of the good news. I love fridays. Oh,
also, I'm drinking this McDonald's. I think the McDonald's
got me all high, too.
Hello, hormones or these chemicals and stuff.
I'm looking for like
hormones and chemicals are getting
The burger was like I had two cheeseburgers on the fries. The fries were kind of already cold and like the burger was I also had nuggets too
They're better heated up. They're good. They're gonna heat it up
How long have you been live? Let's see four hours
Yep, it was cute it was cute. Okay. Hey sassy. Hey, Joe. Yeah
Yeah, I'm looking for like a video editor to use like is there any like a free video editor?
It's like everything has money and it's like I need to
Yeah, I would love it cuz I can put pictures and like I can even like I don't even a still photo
I can like animate
Some of my programs you can animate them to like get up and walk around and say like this. It's so weird like
On TikTok they have this one of those filters, too. I'm sure you've seen that you can like
Make take your photo and then it will make it like walk around and animate it and stuff. It's kind of funny
Let me see if I can find it on TikTok brand new news to me
Tiktok is Tiktok is actually are you on Tiktok? I used to be and I'm not anymore
I don't happen to my account
I think Grace is like got me locked out watching something on there when she's
They're trying to make an account when she was sharing a phone with me
And so it locked my account out or shut it down and then I just never started another one out
Yeah, well to get monetized you need a thousand subscribers, but Emma once she had like twenty three thousand five thousand or something
Oh, you did wow it blew up way before fucking YouTube did like really quick, and then it freaked me out
People got weird on there
Yeah, I mean I wouldn't I don't I've never watched it and all I see is like a bunch of like self-help stuff on it
Which is kind of interesting, but
I want to see about like people doing readings and if I could do readings on it maybe or just like do a little quick. I did
Yeah, you did like people. Yeah, they definitely definitely got it grew a lot faster really really quick like I said and then
Yeah, it's just um, what you can go you're eligible
You're monetized I think right you can get a thousand so I think you just need a thousand to be monetized
Just it's all that my old videos the same ones I posted on YouTube too. It's just funny to post the same content
And it's really hard to it's much harder to grow on YouTube than it is and to get subscribers and followers and whatever
And take off it's a lot harder to make monetization money too
So I had so I posted like a video and it's like I already have 42 views, but like nobody liked it or anything
But that's a lot of views now
Thank you
I don't know. I just think I was just testing I just like just the first thing I saw but they're kind of dumb
Oh, my fucking service kept shitting out. So it's trying to do reading yesterday in a lot
It makes my AI picture like walk see
Hold on it's gonna go
This is strange, I don't know and a weird looks like you
You're gonna be turned into AI. Are you AI?
Well, that picture's patent mostly are but it's okay. You know our friend psych
Really you psych she tried to turn you straight
We were I don't know
Page would not try I don't even like anybody. I don't ever want to date gay. Why would I do that to him?
You go ahead and be gay and enjoy live your life
No, she's you if you're too restrained, but you mean she wouldn't do anything about it
She was just just want me to fall in love with her and I was just like I'd die because I would be so sad
But never be able to anything anymore become miserable. I've become oh my gosh
You look at you having a bad week, but maybe like
Not a bad year, bro
We all are some of us. I can't speak for everybody, but
No, it's been an all right year just bad things have happened. So
But also will probably be good more most best at some point, you know
It may be just really weird
away out of my
Emotional house, so and Nick comes back sometimes like a monster and is like raar
Look at this one. It made me like that. Oh, I don't look like an Italian
Had my hair
How's your hair doing
Remember, yeah, it's all tangled. It's fine. It's open. Okay. Yeah. It's all good now
I say no, it's actually it's still
You see it, it's like, oh, yeah, it's I come at night. I braid it and then
It's like a it's like a purge. It's like a signature purge of
My gosh
You gotta use a little
It took three days, but he got it. Yay. Okay. Oh my gosh
Yeah
Handsome thank you Barbara. Thank you. She's a very handsome guys. Thank you
I'm gonna get these Jeffrey Dahmer glasses to and I'll look even more handsome. No with the black creams
I do check it black frame ones. Yeah, cuz he's like the kind of aviator ones. It's a hurt a little bit
But it's okay. It's like and it's still like not your framed ones with no bottoms like for the frame lenses
Okay, you know people like those are like what old stylish gay men wear
I think I'm getting it like yeah, I'm really like liking them because actually like they serve like a really good purpose like
I can't really can't see anymore or like close up. I used to be near-sighted now. I'm like
Farsight or something because it's like I see fine, but not close up anymore. I
Know it's terrible. It's like I don't know. I'm sorry
Hello ladies, I don't know where he went. He left. Okay
That hurt that hurt just that and like hold my hair apart. Okay, I think I fixed it. Okay
I don't know how to, it never broke my ear.
Well there's no point because me and Bita are gonna come tonight at fucking, as soon as you do close the eyes and not Brito Blanket and we're gonna tell the cats to watch.
And we're gonna see you in like videos.
Good morning and have the same one back.
Little kidlock Brady and James and we're gonna get you.
That's like, well there's like this book called The Golden Ass, I think I've read it before.
It's a promise. Oh, thank you. I think I want to read this big page to you because well
It's a couple pages like the guy goes to an inn and then these witches come in but it's really funny
Hold on because it reminds me of what you did with saying
Yeah
There's three of us be dead you're a page in beta
We
Suck in my head for like a week, but I didn't know if you remembered it or not
And we haven't had a moment to talk about it. So I'm glad you remember
Asian pie that
Is that your friend?
Which one that guy was the Australian or something his name is like. Oh, yeah. No, he's not my friend leggy
You know, he just joins like
Wow, I don't know. He joins once in a blue moon
Mm-hmm. He's kept disappearing and changing. It was funny. He kept trying to come back and show off stuff
Yeah
Things in the department
He's got a cool cat though. I give him that yeah, he's got a really cool like me mean one the big cap. Mm-hmm
He's a little cuckoo brain though. He's ever joined our psyches. That'd be it. Yeah
It's a chat would have a people would have their way with him. Yeah, he's not he's he's very annoying
Human Alex would fight immediately. Oh, yeah, they'll go on forever
You won't be it don't be undetermined winner
Years later
Yeah, he was here tonight and I like I wanted to say but yeah, he's like I don't I cannot stand him
So let me see okay, so this is called the witches and LaMaine
Let me see if I can get in here shit
Can you change the names of the witcher to please and Rita when you're reading the story?
You want me to yeah, yeah, thank you. We'd love that
Thanks
We're easily amused go back to the basics. We are easily amused
I agree that's okay
Okay, okay, so let me see hopefully we all are because we're all here and at our channels all every day
Okay, so
This is a preview log into oh my gosh. Can I repeat you log into your school? You should make a song about me you and betta
I will
Yeah, we'll make one. I mean you aren't you aren't yet
betta spins poetry so she could she could write a song
You are in a couple like, you know, there is a, you know, there is a beat a song and then there's like a just beat a page summer and Christine.
It could be.
The funniest part was like when he did my song.
What is it?
She goes, why is there, why is there Muhammad Ali in the song?
She thought it was Adalame.
It was like, it's my cat.
Like the freaking like boxer Muhammad Ali who's asking why is there Muhammad Ali in my the song
Because in the middle of it. He's like, I don't know. It was like something a be da da da da da and Muhammad Ali
Sounded like it's longic, but it wasn't it's just my cat
my cat
There was someone came into my live yesterday with the name
And it was a cat picture too and it said Muhammad Ali Muhammad. They felt they just said it weirder
Backwards, but they used your cat's name. They get the fuck out of here
It won't that I mean that's a common name to you know, I know the cat picture
Which means a little sass, but definitely one of my cats
It was a cat to look like your cat kind of but it wasn't an exact picture
No, I
Didn't look like in this little picture. It's too small and he pissed me off to tell them please
Poor poor guy just could have been his name could have been Ali Mohammed and he happened to have a cat
He's stinky. Yeah. Yeah, I could have been no. Yeah, I don't even care if it was him or not doing it
Just he was annoying anyway
He was a beaker beta like to beak
What's a beaker person who just goes off at the mouth beacon
We call it in Canada, you're beacons.
What is Joe writing?
Alex is more obsessed with gay guys with rainbows than clips with Nicole?
Yeah, I'm just kidding.
Alex is more obsessed with Peter, he doesn't even know about Peter.
Rainbow clips with Nicole?
What?
I have no idea.
Gay clips.
Huh?
Well, a rainbow is,
is like gay, right?
Good to know, Nicole. Apparently, you and I are,
we're an item.
Weird.
What's Stikey doing?
Stikey's doing brain surgery.
You want to hear the story?
OK, here it is.
It's called The Witches of Thessaly,
an extract from the golden asked by Appalachus.
OK, it says, OK, so he, let's see,
it is called Chapter 21 through 30,
the story of Telephone.
Telephone?
OK, it says, Sagae Thessaly, the witch of the Thessaly.
So I guess, which is the Sagae?
So it says,
Lucius is traveling through Thessaly in Greece. By chance, he meets a lady called Byronian, who invites him to a dinner party.
At the party Lucius has asked what he thinks of Thessaly, he replies that he's impressed
but worried by stories he has heard about the local witches who are in the habit of
cutting pieces of flesh from corpses.
One of the guests laughingly points to a man hidden away in the corner of the room, saying
that he has suffered his fate while still alive.
The man whose name is Thel...
Frankie.
Yes, Lily Frone, no, it's not me, Lily Frone, is urged by Byrenia or Bita to tell Lucius
the story.
As a young man, sitting out from my leadess for the Olympic Games,
since I had wished to visit places in the famous province,
the whole of Thessaly, having been traveled through, I came to Larissa.
And while wandering through the city,
Larissa is the city, I think.
While wandering through the city, my traveling allowance has,
having been diminished, I was seeking remedy for my poverty.
I caught sight of an old man in the middle of the forum.
He was standing on the stairs.
Proclaiming in the blood boys that anyone was willing to guard a corpse. He would receive a large reward
And I said to him someone passing by what is this I'm hearing our corpses accustomed to run away here
He was hush
There should literally be silence is here fly for you are a boy and I'm your stranger and naturally you do not know
That infestedly well, which is frequently bite pieces out of the faces of dead men
Which are supplements for their arts of magic and he replied I said what sort of protection is needed?
He goes now first your plot you must
We'll stay fully awake for the whole night, and with your eyes open, sleepless eyes directed
all the time at the corpse, and your gaze must never be diverted, since the most wicked
witches keep up secretly, since they haven't been changed in whatever animal you wish,
for they take the seeds of birds and dogs and mice, and indeed even flies as well.
Flies as well.
So the man ends the warning that if anyone fails to deliver the body intact in the morning,
he is forced to replace the major piece of flesh with pieces sliced from his own face.
So, these things haven't been understood, I strengthened my mind and approached the
old man at once.
I said, stop crying out now, there's a garden ready, I had scarcely finished when he led
me to a certain house where he showed me a weeping lady, wrapped in mourning clothes.
She arose and led me to a bed chamber, there she uncovered with her hand, a body wrapped
with shining white sheets, and she had anxiously pointed at the individual feakers she went
out.
Hellefron begins his visual. I was left alone for the comfort of the corpse
My eyes having been rubbed and prepared for guard duty when I soothed my mind with songs up to the middle of the night
I stayed away then however fear was built upon within me and suddenly a weasel
Creeping and sit in front of me and fix its eyes on me such great boldness and such a small
Disturb my mind
Finally spoke with us go away. You spread full creature before you you speedily experienced my strength go away
the weasel turns his back and forth will goes into the bedchamber without delay so deep asleep
suddenly overcomes me and not even the god of delphi himself i.e. apollo could have easily decided
out of the two of us lying there oops okay uh the two of us lying there uh
sorry sorry
Who is the more dead? At last, having been awoken at first light and terrified by a great fear,
I run over to the corpse in a lamp having been brought near, the face having been uncovered.
I inspect everything carefully. Nothing is lacking. Behold the poor white person we think.
The body having been inspected, she pays the reward without delay.
While I was recovering my strength in the street next to the house, the body was brought
out.
Because it was the body of one of the leading citizens, it was carried in procession.
Around the former, according to a local custom, as it was taking place, an old man suddenly
appeared.
He was weeping and tearing out his fine white hair.
He ran up to the beer and embraced it amidst sobbing grounds.
He cried out, for your sake of your honor, citizens, he said, for the sake of your public
duty, stand up for the murdered citizen and punish severely the most vile crime of the
For she and no one else was killed with poison, this wretched young man,
the son of my sister, to please her lover, and for the sake of inherited profits.
She, with tears pouring down and swearing by all the gods, as piously as she could,
denied so great a crime. Therefore, the old man said,
let us refer the judgment of the truth to divine providence.
Here is Zachtlas, the Egyptian, a very well-known prophet,
who has promised that for a large fee he will lead back the soul of the corpse
from the nether regions and reanimate the body for a short time.
The prophet was certain to action. He took a special herb and laid it three times on the mouth of a dead man.
Then he took another and put it on his breast. Then he turned to face the east in silence and prayed for the sacred disc of the writing,
rising sun. The people waited at the expectation of a miracle.
I pushed myself into the crowd and standing on a stone beside the beer, I watched everything with curious eyes.
Now the chest of the corpse is raised by swelling, now the body was filled with breath.
And the corpse arises and speaks out,
Why I beg you, do you bring me to take care of the transitory life?
Stop now, I pray you stop and allow me to remain in my rest.
The voice from the body was heard, but the prophet said rather forcibly,
Why do you not tell the people everything about your death?
For the beer here flies, and with a deep groan, the people does.
Murdered by the evil arts of my new wife, and sentenced by a poison cup,
I have yielded up my well-embed to an adulterer.
I shall give you very clear proof of the truth.
I shall reveal what absolutely no one else could have known or predicted.
Then pointing at me with his finger, he said,
When this very keen-witted guard of my body was sleeping at the intensive watch over me,
Some witches eager for my remains appeared in changed form, since they could not elude
the unremitting diligence, finally a fog of sleep, having been cast over him, they buried
him in deep rest.
Then they had been begin to arouse me by name, nor did they stop until my sluggish joints
and cold limbs.
struggles lowly and obedience to their magic arts.
However, he who was alive and only dead in trance
has by chance the same name as I.
So with the sound of his name,
he got up unwittingly, proceeding mechanically
in the manner of a lifeless ghost, he goes to the door.
Although the doors of the bedchamber have been carefully locked, first his nose and then his ears, having been nibbled through a certain hole, he suffered his mutilation in my place, and the witches attached to him wax-shaped in the manner of his ears, which had been cut off, and fitted a nose similar to the one cut off, and now the poor fellow stands there, having earned a fee not for his hard work for his mutilation.
Terrified by these words, I begin to test my appearance.
I grab my nose with my hand.
It comes away.
I touch my ears.
They fall off.
And while the crowd identifies me with pointed fingers
and nods, I, if you would sweat, escape.
being between the feet of those standing around, nor afterwards thus maimed and thus ridiculous, and I returned to my native land,
and I have hidden the wounds of my ears and hair hanging down on my side of my head, and indeed for the sake of decency
I've covered the disgrace of my nose with a piece of canvas. Well, that's terrible, but yeah.
I didn't really tell what, but then which is the comment, which is the comment, Pia, how much?
Also, like you you got like that's what we're doing out at night when we're up all night
I swear to God. We didn't have all that plan. That was a lot a lot of people involved
I didn't the pope like I don't know the whole guy in your hair in your sleep, dude
Yeah, me and pager not that elaborate dude like we just fly with a broom
We just come over and then frame and we just leave why that was a lot
i was so lost like i took my red and then put it back well we didn't want to make you into the
zombie you did not know i didn't say that was you i was just remember i'm gonna be like i don't
know if that was the same story no you okay fine we can do that if you want i don't want you to
i don't want that i don't want you to you gave us the gestures now no i'm not that was that that
Oh, it's the wizard in the wizard in the golden banana. That sounds good. No, please. Please. No
I'm so confused. I smoke. I'm not gonna. I'm not gonna read it. I don't even know what that last story meant
No, I don't know I don't have way through my eyes. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. Okay, never mind. I guess I thought
I just love that book that it's like oh, I see stories
That was actually the first novel ever written in the world by Appalachus. Oh, really? Oh, okay
Educated yeah, that's true. I didn't know anything about yeah
It's like I just I'm just self-educated
Like I just think I just was being asked it when he was writing that
I don't think they had acid back then.
He was in Thessaly, so they were on The Witches'
Salve and stuff like that.
So it was like Belladonna and Hensbane
and all kinds of poisonous like.
Plants do you get high on to be high on them you just high on to what watch the dosage of them because they are poisonous
Usually like Bella don't ride the plant
Laughing like she knows something about the sassy. Are you part of one of the witches, huh? What is happening here?
What is
Which is the best way she knows about the story and I never heard of it in my life
Are you heard you've heard of the golden ass? I don't know. She's a fire. Yeah, that's what it's called the golden ass
The golden butt
No, it's actually a donkey. He's certainly the donkey golden ass
Yes
Okay, the guy wants the guy wants to like learn witchcraft or like we're learned magic
And so he goes to this like wishes house in this place this city that's full of wishes and so whatever and so
He like starts sleeping with like the basically the her maid
And then he asked him and then he starts asking the maid
He's like hey
I want to like see one of her rituals like the mistress of the house and so they go a spy on her
She like rubs the stuff on her body that she turns into an owl and flies out the window and he's like, okay
Turn me into an owl
She rubs like some salve on him and then he like turns it to the donkey, right?
And then he's like, okay, well, do you undo it undo it or whatever?
And then she's like, okay. And then she's like, oh, shoot. I don't I forgot.
I don't have like the right the antidote and then so she's like, we have to eat a flower.
Like if you go eat certain flower and so he goes and then he goes to the flower
but then he keeps getting like attacked by like all the people and he gets sold into slavery
and they just beat him and stuff and he's trying to become like a human again.
You know I almost spoiled the story, but he became rich
He became now he began he turned back human. I don't know if he became rich
Except the golden ass like the golden yeah, because he was he was golden because
Uh, he was actually like he was only temporarily in that trans like the metamorphosis like you know, he was in that
I'm gonna use that. I'm gonna anytime someone pisses me off. I'm gonna be like kiss my golden ass motherfucker
I am I'm gonna use that
You should do you should do that and then a page right down on the
Writing it. I knew you would just in case if I forget to
Kiss my golden ass. Oh
It's good. We've got some serious merch psych. I need to talk to you, but because I've got I've got okay
Yeah, for my day one stuff, like I've got stuff that I wrote.
I'll show you, yeah, I'll show you how to make stores and stuff.
Okay, let's do it, let's do it.
I can also help you with your logos and stuff too.
Actually, all you have to do is, I think you really can, but too,
like it's like they have a free trial, like two week free trial.
I think it's a free trial, just like do all you can, like in about two weeks,
and it's like you want to keep it, like keep it, because you can still,
it'll be useful, but it's like
Mean to say the free version is kind of expensive, but I would say you can get so many things done like that are with like
thumbnails you can have a cool a really cool thumbnails in every video you can have
Other like big banners really really easily and I'm incorporating more and more and they like they look pretty good on
I don't know. It's just like I'm just trying different things with them, but
Yeah, I'll show you some stores and stuff whatever you interested in doing I can tell you
Your advice I'll tell you what I use and stuff. I gotta give I gotta give everybody it pertains to half the profit though
That's fair, right cuz like
There's a lot of them right everybody's saying like things that they've said so I have to give them credit for it
Well, yeah, I was yeah, that's what I'm saying. But yeah, you should I'm saying you shouldn't like have your company. Yeah, it's like
your own
Proven wildflowers merch, but like we'll do it. Exactly. I don't change my name up a bit. I think I
No, I like your name. I may also do a different show for like like, you know summer's got her difference in the
Like a podcast I always wanted to start up, but
Because you could just talk about whatever it didn't have to be kind of a topic or a spiritual channel
I kind of want to keep it like to like trivia and spiritual stuff and like spend Ella and night golfing and things like that, right?
trivia
awesome
It's like I'm like a kid that hears ice cream
ice cream
Love trivia. We've been played in a while. I should I'll look up some questions
Okay, okay
Did you post that crazy
Country song on the discord too because like I have to show my co-worker that I think I did I think I
I put all the ones that I saw and yeah, my fools are there. So I should be there should be
That is so funny. I'll check it again now
She's just amazed that we can do these things. She's an older lady, right?
You're my mom's this is tiny crazy little lady that lives out there and she runs
And so she just fills that hole that I've been missing a little bit
So I call her mama and she never had daughters or she never a kid. So Grace and I you should make a song for her
Are her family. He would love that. She her name is Virginia. So it'd be super easy to
Do it. She's one of the apps is freaking pretty from him easy
We're gonna do some cool. I used to fuck around with AI music all the time, but after a while is like I
Did one for somebody and then it was just I don't know I
Like I like to do my own thing. Yeah, you know, you can write your own and then like, you know
Have the music put on there your actual lyrics
No, I didn't know that I generated one
Well, stop if you don't have a voice like me
You've done a songbird of your generation, like Bita?
Yeah, I'll write a song and somebody like Whitney Houston voice can sing it.
What was I doing, looking for again?
I don't remember.
I'm fucking...
Your pen?
Nope, it wasn't that.
No, I'm going to smoke somewhere we didn't know remember.
I'm just kidding. That was just a joke.
I
Right
If I should go nap, I'm not really
I just have a fucked up sleep schedule as it is all the time. I'd go check cows this morning, Bita. I
Know you guys. I don't know when you cuz I want to sleep. I want to sleep like around
Don't dirty and then I woke up my cat woke me up again. Me he has
I don't know what his fucking issue is, like every other day, like one day he's okay.
He just lets me sleep.
And then other days, he just like meow, meow, meow, meow, meow, meow, meow, meow.
And then I get up and I'm like, what?
And then he does a horsey cake, like, yay, mission accomplished.
It runs the household.
Just testing you.
My one or Raven does that.
She'll just sit under my front, like under my.
Put your little nose kind of under my door of my bedroom and just like that forever in the same
order and same timing and everything until the point. I just, she's like an alarm clock that
you can't ignore. Oh, I kind of ignore now for like 10 minutes and he just got worse than worse.
Like you know, I was like, okay fine. I get up. I'm like, what is it you're boring like this and that
Yeah, he's just bored. Hopefully with your frickin brother. There's other animals in the house
There's other things to terrorize leave me alone
Don't wake you up with your frickin taken them out. No, they don't care for that at all. They really upset us
How would you like it if you're sleeping cat and I just come in your ear and I'm just like
Meow! Meow!
No more trivia.
Trivia? Oh yeah, you want to look for trivia, I thought.
Yup, that's, I know.
No more trivia. You're going to listen to Arthur, because Arthur only likes drama.
He's not into trivia.
Arthur, look it, we'll make you a deal.
You by Jenny girl trivia for like a little bit and then me and beauty will create some fake drama for you to enjoy
And I'm kidding. I don't know the mood for that today
People are into the trivia some people are let's have a vote in the chat
Drop a one if you are a yes for trivia and two if you are a fuck no for trivia
AI stories versus trivia.
Yeah. Back to Chora's page.
Email me so we can discuss.
Easy. It's a whole different story with cats.
When you're sleeping and you're in the bus sleep ever,
and some cat goes meow,
and you're like, okay, it's just a meow.
You're like, you okay, Mickey?
And then he goes meow.
Meow meow and you're like, okay, okay, Miki come here. Come here. Just come here. Just come and call
It's that's a lot. Yeah, it's a whole meow orchestra
I love how you said that. Orkestra, I didn't say that. Orkestra? Orkestra? You made it sound awesome. It's Orkestra, but you said Orkestra. Orkestra. Yeah, it's pretty.
I think the trivia wins, right? It always does.
But yeah, I'm chose because if you play trivia site, he just pops up and he wants to answer. He's still competitive
He can't take it. He just like gets rid on the edge of his seat
And when he doesn't know the answer he'll like through like 10 until one becomes true
Like you have to be fair, okay, if you let the lesser, you know, we used to let us play too
I'll be asking questions this time. So then you'll have to do it and then I can play it next time
Come on television television. Oh
My gosh, have you seen fun with Dick and Jane and their kid speaks more Mexican than he does like whatever
Going home, what are you doing with the television taking it away? Oh, we're repo'ing it
No, I've never seen that
Okay, I don't know what's going on here. My TV's everything is falling apart. Just like my little life
to restart my TV
Wolf wolf when they jump on you and they're big mad
Who who's jumping on you the dogs are
Take me for a walk now
Yeah, when they want to roll up here easy get up here. We be rolling we'd be right in
Trying to catch me riding dirty trying to catch me riding dirty
We don't ride dirty the right kind of cleanish
Okay, there we go now it's working
Trivia for five-year-olds. I'm just kidding. We're actually all really quite really good at trivia
They have trivia for five-year-olds
Well, it's just that trivia for kids trivia one plus one
Fucking what color is this and it says blue?
I don't know it's yellow. Oh my god
What vegetables are considered good for like a green broccoli carrot pale spinach
They have like dancing vegetables. Have you ever seen the dancing fruits?
No, Grace loves the bubble guppies and that song is fucking catchy
That's you you see you guys are weak. What is this? What the hell is this? Am I in twilight zone?
What? Dancing vegetables?
Yeah they have like dancing fruits and then talking vegetables and then they have
they have some weird shit like I was watching with some
and my niece would choose it just a baby and
my friend and like her mom were over and Grace is with
this was like last year so we're watching this
and all of us are just sitting there with like our mouths open watching this stupid show
I'm like is this inappropriate?
Like should even we be watching this? Where did this come from who's doing this to us?
I don't know
Who thinks these things? I mean we all say some cook shit, but like that's people are making TV kids TV out of it
We're not doing that with our our content
I mean art too none of our content to be kind of funny
Have a good day Hebrew
Bye bye Hebrew
First trivia question will be harder than a buff. Are you smarter than a fifth grader?
Probably not. I'm probably not
Okay, so general knowledge, general knowledge. I like this trivia generator thing that I had before. Let's do that.
Where's Jabroni when we need him to do some extra trivias on the side?
He's like, oh guys, so, oh, I like how Oliver talks.
Yeah, I'm Jabron's.
Yeah, it is my favorite.
Generator.
You should have another like concert at good times. Oh
Yeah, it's happening. It's gonna be on good time stuck 2026. So, yeah
I'll let you know. I think I'm the flyers would should be sent out soon to all the streamers and the chatters
All right, and shout out to like everybody who like everybody played a part. Everybody was just so shout out to everyone that joined the last time
It was good
Oh, man, it's so funny to get his shit in a knot
He loves his lawn. I don't think that he'd love anybody else in a little more than that lawn.
Okay. An AI quiz generator, of course. Teachers would be using that.
Okay. Do-do-do-do.
Can you say AI? Can you ask me a question?
Looking for a smarter way to mom
Sorry guys
Your girls your cats are your cats are girls. I have two girls and I have two boys. Yeah
Okay, yeah Raven and fart being are the girls and bees and burr the boys. Oh
This is a good
tutorial on how to make AI videos.
What is happening?
Scythe, you've been talking about this way too long
in my phone.
Now it's time to give it up.
You're a bitch.
I can try to find one.
What's up?
Good morning to the panel.
Good morning to the listeners, to the viewers,
to the people that restream this stream,
to the people that flag the stream,
to everyone out there, except to the trivia people
and to the A.I. storytellers, good morning.
Good morning to YouTube T.O.S., Restrictions.
Let me give a shout out to...
Nightbot
Nightbot to insert buttplug all of that. Yep
No
You know, I think I think this channel has been missing its dose of drama for the last couple days and
Doctors here to give its dose
Dr. Drama
Dr. Do little drama
Now, um, I do want to start off with ask and beat it. Oh God, I'm not on the mood to answer any questions right now, except for trivia.
Why do people say that you talk through your teeth?
I don't know. Wait, let me try to talk through my teeth right now. Okay.
Your teeth I don't you talking about can you tell me why Jews talks like he is out of breath?
Yeah, yeah, I just I just ended work right now, man
I just finished recording a shower session female wasn't aware come on now
I see page left shout outs page page love. Yeah, I wasn't going to ask her anything about you
If you're going to leave
Damn it, did I lose connection? Hello
You're not a Samas panel. Oh
I
Yes, you
Let's see. Where is salmon? Oh
Where did peach go? Oh, your phone died. Okay. Okay. She'll be back
Okay
All right, so what's up? What's up? Okay. Okay, so I'm alone and psyche's alone. What the fuck?
Should I leave to?
Why here?
That was
That was creepy why?
Yeah, and you were so quiet no more the site leave to you like no, I'm here
Everything with the evil
Here's hanging out yeah, I don't know why they dropped off a bit she's gonna show me back her phone died, okay
Yeah, so this is kind of cool. This is like well that kind of expensive
But there's all these 136 vintage decor scrapbook paper set
What?
It's all these pin-up photos like 170 of these photos
Wait, it's like a collage. What is this? There's scrapbook
Paper set, but it's like it seems like it's all like these kind of crazy like like it looks really cool
It's hard to see. I'm sorry. It is hard to see. Yeah, I'm sorry. No, it's cool though.
Hey, Tricks. You're just going on out chilling like a villain. That's a better brand.
It's like the superheroes and the Vixens and the that's a cool, cool, uh,
Yeah, I don't know. Teemo is like I'm really I'm really addicted to it and it's like there's five dollar t-shirts
Okay, you know, it's like I've always wanted to be able to buy like a cool shirt
Like and there's like some a lot of them are not cool. I mean, there was I buy I think are cool
I mean, there's some not cool stuff on it
But it's like but the more you like do it think better kids that you're picking here you're you're like style
And so it's like you find there was like good stuff on that there's good stuff
Eventually it's finally showing up on my page. So
I'm uh, you're looking at his nails. This is so weird. Why don't you put hello in the back stage? Oh
Oh
Yeah, that is creepy. Oh
All right back
On to that bridge
Connection, you know, I guess that was
Juices ghost on to me and appreciate that joke I made
He probably videoed you through the maze. I mean the
But a psychic what are your thoughts on people saying be the talks to her teeth, I don't hear that I really don't
I talk to my teeth
Apparently she talks to her teeth like I don't hear that at all. I
Talk to my teeth because I have no one else to talk through through your teeth through your teeth
Yeah, like you bite and then you speak you bite and then you speak you don't open your mouth when you when you speak
No, no, but obviously you got open your lips is just your teeth are shut
Your lips are moving everything except your teeth
I don't fucking know what I'm doing. Okay. I have no idea. I don't have like a gap to so I don't know how to whistle through my teeth
Maybe you can ask that question from just a little I
Mean Kate and juice have said that I really don't hear it as much as I love
I'm sorry
You know, I just talk whatever I talk boy. Is that a shot?
Who's shot that?
I don't know
Both of them
You're breaking out
Sir to turn off the fucking VPN, can you hear me?
Yo yes, I hear you right now. Let me turn off the vpm brah
Let me go ahead and turn off the vpm roll. I grit I grits my teeth when she wait
She grits her teeth when she's drunk like Sean Connery the fuck are you guys talking about?
And you know what? If you don't like the way I talk, I don't really like the way you talk, Kate.
You talk like you're fucking like a dude.
You're like, hey, why are you guys going to do this?
I can't take it anymore.
Yo, drop link, drop link, drop link.
I haven't spoken to El Do in a while.
Yo, say drop link, dude.
Drop link, drop link.
How do I share the link?
Are you there?
He goes, yes.
Oh my God, I haven't listened to fucking Eldor in a minute, bro. I missed that.
No, he said the enlarge.
I can't say.
Psyche.
Don't say it.
Oh my God, he is there like a conductor.
He's always working behind the scenes.
Yeah, so can you lay off the chat GBT the AI shit because you're ruining your channel with this shit like I get it
You know, it's it's fascinating what it could do, but that's all you do now
Like oh, let's just go ahead and read AI story about the fucking YouTube channel. Yeah, that's
Okay, first of all, I haven't done one AI story. I've just sent a few AI songs
They probably like know just a few because I have like 30 days to use the like a thousand credits
I'm just saying like your channel isn't AI. It's fucking terrible. I can have whatever I can you don't tell me what my channels
I get to tell you what you get to tell you what my channel is. Okay, you don't tell me what my channel, okay?
Thank you
I'm just saying as a viewer, you know, I'm just giving you my review my thoughts
Thank you. Thank you for your opinion
Send it to the complaints department as
Under some bridge the marks
I'm just saying like put out a poll and ask the chat. What do they think?
I've gotten your feedback. I know I mean I don't even play that often I play a song like you know
I did that I like song I played a song when I open maybe and I played a couple few songs last night when I was like
Doing something else and I just didn't want to end the show. So what's the problem? It's like do you care?
I can't play other kind of music so like so give me the fuck alone if I could play a music
What do you fucking care?
I don't care. I don't care. I don't care. Don't tell me what to do. Stop
I don't tell you what to do. I'm just giving you my thoughts. I don't okay. I hear
I don't care
I hear it, but I don't care
Oh, my god, where's Aldo?
Shut up bronzy
I can't stand Bronzeberg, man.
The guy, the guy always gives us thoughts on like stuff that have nothing to deal with him.
He hasn't been around here.
He has his own.
Okay, let's not forget that every time you fucking write in the chat
You're writing about me and how you're trying to throw everybody else under the bus to make a point
So whatever elder and Arthur did
It's none of your fucking business and I can move on how about you move on and not mention my like fucking name every other second
Arthur give me what is going on it's taking not allowing people up
Well, you know, I'm afraid to point it out. I'm so sorry. You're not the biggest like, you know, analytical light person. I mean, I can point out a whole bunch of hypocrisies on you. All right. You also call me an uncle effort and much more. So let's not forget that Jesus. Yeah.
I've been I'm pinning the link right now. So, you know, now it's there. It's tense. Okay. We need easy up here. We need bronze up here. We need
when the guy was knocking on your door he was like fuck out of here man fuck out
all right that's just like uh that's just a friend and so is Trisha and Sam
because they're just yeah that was just them being a good friend
uh-huh what do you want him to be like yeah get her get her i want him to keep
his fucking mouth shut
And I can't I think he has a horrible voice. I think he's probably top three of the worst voices in this community
Who are the top two me and Alex Andrew McQueen? No, I actually like your voice
You know you what's his name? I just mentioned bronze bird
The one that speaks fast the other bird. What's his name bird? Oh, see all these birds are weird
Bird bronze bird bird. Oh fucking weirdos
Was another one
Oh, um, the he she the tranny the tranny the tranny. Oh, uh, Mr. Big Pipes. No, no, no, Mr.
Diamond. I think those three are the worst because fucking Diamond doesn't know how to
Like what the fuck is it like a fucking Mario game? It's a video game. It's a video game
It's a video bid bid bid
Dio video
the bitch pronounces fucking
video a video it's a video it's a me
Bitch like I said those two birds are the weirdos and then
The he she those three have the worst voices
Thank you. Are you doing a science experiment talking doing another fucking AI story behind scenes?
Okay, this is what he does he gets the URL
He gets the fucking URL to like a previous stream of his
He puts it on chat GPT then it as he asks. Oh my god. Can I get a rundown and then he tells us what happened in the last week?
And he keeps doing that
Like good God like I get it like there's chaos is fucking mayhem. There's breeding care
It's our carrot tart reading wherever it's called
like, okay
Eat some constant like
Yes, like 10 people backstage
There's nobody backstage. Oh really? I'll just check it
I
Let them on I bet yeah, like Arthur. Don't fuck yourself. Who cares what you think Arthur?
We're just not driving on fucking psyche and stop being a George. All right fine fine fine
No, you lay off
Sure
You know I'm in it today
Like
I'm not in a bad mood, but it's not a bad mood, but you would come
If you like you think it's so easy to do you think you're on show and then you can run it like you want to run
I won't I won't ever tell you what you can do
Well, I don't like to be told what this I mean, I'd like to be told what people think but I don't like to be told
Uh, criticism like in front of everybody like when you and like, you know, I mean, how else do I like reach you?
I can't speak to you. I don't know. Like I said, send in send in the kind of complaint department as
But fuck eases or something like that. See there you go. So you're being the smart ass and then why can't I be a smart ass?
But okay, I'll lay off. I'll lay off. I'm responding to you. It's like you're being a smart ass. I don't know what it's like
I'm actually like just like
mirroring your behavior
I think your channel is amazing, I think your channel is amazing, so keep doing what you're doing.
The channel it's it's has to be you know sponsored by YouTube. It's it's one of the best channels out there
Nothing but positivity nothing but great storytelling nothing but great trivia questions
All on
365 days of entertainment here on fucking psyche awakens terror the greatest channel on fucking YouTube history
Nobody will ever beat this fucking channel because it's the best. It's the most donated the most viewed the most reviewed the most fucking
And you have to go overboard about it because it's like then I don't think you're genuine
It's like if you just say yeah
Okay, so it's like okay, but it's like, you know, you're just playing overboard about it like being
Being the opposite of what you're saying, so I don't
Okay, I
Won't take you seriously. It's okay. I mean, I can't like I don't get it if I sit on the channel. I'm bad if I give
Yeah
Just like talk about something else. You don't talk about my channel. It's like it's like kind of like
Yeah, we talked about talking about my show on my show is like kind of meta talk about my show somewhere else
You know, you know, my show we can talk about other stuff and have the show to talk about if I talk about your show somewhere else
Then you'll be like, oh my god, you're talking behind the scenes
Well, no, but because you're what you thought you'd say something negative probably
You should not be like you should be like promoting my show I'm saying if you really talk about you want to be a monster
Bad and you are a mod right now. I do
Talkie. No, I know before now, but you're pissing off again
I'm about to take it back away because it's like you're not you don't represent the channel
Well, they type it in on YouTube and then you show up. I don't I don't think
You're doing a very good job as a mod. You know, it's like you're really disappointing me as one actually. Oh my god
Here we go. All right. Well, okay. How about this?
Erase everything I just said psych. I think you're doing a good a good job here at this channel
I don't know. I don't know. Hey. Hey, I think
Kimberly and say job brother. It's temporary insanity. I don't I don't know it's like it comes to me like
nice, nicely asked me and I was like, okay, well, okay.
And then it's like, they turn on me immediately.
Oh, here's Eldo, hold on.
Now me, you gotta be honest with me.
At least I keep it 100 with you, you know?
At least I'm here to be honest with you.
Whether you like it or not, I'm always on this.
I'm always on this.
You got it, you got it.
There's Eldo, Camdo, put the mask.
Of course, man.
Oh my goodness, yes.
Oh my goodness, they go.
We need them on solo, we need them on solo.
We need to analyze them.
The fucking go bro, that's the go right there, bro.
No, I was just taking a break.
Kate, why are you here?
Damn.
What's good, Eldo, man?
You're the go, bro.
Come on, man.
You messing my camera, man.
I'm about to leave though, so you don't have to fix it again.
How's it going out there? How's the trucking man?
Good all today. Yeah, man
I'm out of hours breath right out of hours not hours man ran out of my my my lovin man
Nice. Thanks, dude. We got that money though. We got the money money in the
I suppose I just want to be I just want to be successful
Oh, why did uh, why did psyche leave?
He went backstage but I'm gonna hop off just to hear you man. You're the goat
What I'll be the what I'll be the how you doing
You don't like Arthur that much
No, I'm sick of it. I can't I'm gonna
Damn, he was unmodding you. That's why he dipped off. He was unmodding you. God damn.
Psyche, if you like, you can change the layout to the square one where it's like, uh, you can, we can see our elders like, well, we can see more, if you like, you know, when you go to layout, let me just go clamp.
He's busy like he's busy making he's making things happen for the channel. He's gonna give us surprises. He's making merch
moving forward
I'm gonna get some booty shorts and the mail that says psyche awakens in the back of it
What up chat? What up chat?
Hey, what's been going on man, you've been going live beater
Mm-hmm
Yeah, I'm in license. I was gonna go live. I think yesterday, but no the day before yesterday something came up
I might go live tonight or tomorrow
Okay, okay. Yeah
Alright, that's what's up, man. I might do it live too. Just you know go over clips and shit like that, you know
Do it just do it do it do it
I should put my number up right just in case people want to call because I do got it set up
You know me. Oh, yeah, the phone calls
But uh, yeah, I hope the diamond is doing okay. Oh, yeah last time we talked to her. She was gonna bust right homeless
No, she was moving somewhere. I left her a message. I was like, hey, I hope you had safe travels
But I don't even know if you thought or not. Did she uh, oh she didn't DM you you didn't hit you bad
No, I mean you got to realize too that uh
Um
Me turn my shit off real quick
You know she got raging now so
Yeah, maybe yeah
That's true. She got raging so
He might be helping her
You might doubt it. It's what I'm saying
I doubt it
You don't think he helping her he got money you got clubs
I've never seen raging demon ever donate to anyone or I've never even heard of him like ever ever
now
That would give out his identity.
You think so?
No.
I don't think he has money.
So, oh God, I'm going to talk and he's going to come back and scream.
Why?
I don't know if his name is mentioned, he gets highly offensive.
Why are you mentioning my name?
I wasn't talking about you, but Aldo brought you up.
I think he gave up on the internet. So yeah, I mean you've brought him up plenty of times already
But you know me and he hasn't showed up so we'll see him at the next gay parade
Thank you are you mad at us should we go should we leave them again
Should we go psyche? What you doing site? Did you on my oh, yeah, he did a mouse Arthur. Damn
Arthur pissed him off. He's like he was in a great mood
And Arthur gift you
Come on our two row you don't fucked up now. Yeah, I don't know what's been going on man
I mean last thing I remember is Kate, you know was telling people she's taking a break
But she was in chat. I guess she disappeared the girl Kate, you know, cuz I don't want to see your dumb ass, you know
You know I'm saying I don't want to have to you know talk to your mother again. You feel me to allow Kate back up
But uh, yeah, man other than that I've been chilling man, you know, I just got done watching Jurassic
World or whatever the fuck the movie called Jurassic Park
Superman was a good movie I got done watching that that was a real good movie
He's getting there watching like old movies
Not they're not old. They just came out. Oh, the new versions. Oh, okay. I don't know
Like who left I mean
Okay, let's see what the chat is saying.
What was y'all doing prior to me coming up here?
What was y'all talking about, you know?
Well, I came up and then Paige was up here
and Psyche was playing a song
and then we were just talking.
We're just joking and like, I don't know, we're gonna do a trivia and then Arthur came
and said fuck trivia and the AI stories and then Psyche went on mute and Psyche said it's
my show, I can do whatever I want Arthur and then I don't know, that's pretty much as far
as I know.
Okay, so not much. Okay. All right, you know sometimes it ain't gonna be drama out here
But uh a horse thing. Yes centers was was definitely better than Superman and fucking Jurassic world
You ain't lying there. That shit was that shit was good, man
That shit was good
Hopefully they do a part two man. I see I see them doing a part two with that the way it ended I could see him doing a part two
centers to
But yeah, man, I mean, it's gonna be boring man because there ain't no drama going on from what I know, man
beta seemed to be a normal today, you know, I don't think she's too drunk today
Have you drank any today beta it's 7 a.m. No, I haven't drank since Monday, but
Um, I will definitely do a live, but I'm not gonna be normal. I'm just normal cuz it's 7 a.m
Like what do you want me to do get buck wild?
But I'm not trying to hear that shit. You've been drunk at 5 a.m. 6 a.m. 7 8 9
I made it. I made a bet
with salmon
What
Is he gonna give me money because he is not a bet it's a challenge he goes he goes beta beta
I bet you can't drink for 30 days. I bet I said I bet you can not talk about me on your stream for 30 days
He's like
Okay, you don't drink and I won't talk about you on my stream and I was like, okay, we'll see
But I'm still gonna do lives without drinking in the 30 days
I'm drinking something right now called um remedy vanilla dream working protein almond milk
Yeah, I don't know I don't I can't
I don't know you're bored
No, I'm saying you drink them. You're not drinking for 30 days. It's not realistic to me
What the fuck like why isn't it realistic? I didn't drink for years and years and years and years
I never really was a drinker anyways
Yeah, I just don't see it happen
Well, we'll see
August 18th
Yeah, I'll get I'll get really drunk. I'm gonna go crazy
What does my fuck a psycho man, I don't know he's he's like being really mean and rude to us. I think he doesn't like us
No, he was up when you was up here. I mean, is he that irritated?
I mean, did did Arthur really piss him off like that because I know he ain't got no problem with me. So let me see
Psyche
See
Yes, Kate disappeared. I'm sure she's still lurking but who Kate the fucking tell people who to give a wrench to in
Psyche chat, you know, but you that's why she disappeared because she knew I was about to be on her ass like
I hope site didn't take fucking Arthur wrench because it Katie
Arthur had a wrench. Okay, I don't even know
Hey Christine, how are you?
No, no bronze bird. I'm not gonna shut my mouth. Stop it
easy your
Easy like Sam as like other brother real twins
Drugs yeah, I'm smoking some marijuana judge me judge me
Let's see
Hmm that's about it. That's a man been around
Yeah, yesterday, um, yesterday I was on psyches. He joined for a little bit.
I put, um, I put catnip on top of my salad instead of like, you know, dried, like, you know, basil or mint.
I'm just kidding. I don't know if anybody's ever freaking ate cat, uh, catnip or smoked it. Hi, He-Man!
No, I see you psych have it all over his couch, but you know, there he is. Oh, no, that's not
This author
He needs to apologize to psyche I think
Like he got hurt. He's mad and he doesn't want to come up until Arthur apologizes
No, I do want to say I've been the knee to psych and
You know
I just like to stir the pot a little bit man. You you got to understand. I'm not here malicious if you can forgive
The dude from New York the fake cop if you could forgive him
Even though he's wanted to you know flag your channel and he has I think you could forgive me man
So I've been the needy you
Sorry brother. I
Don't know man. You've been working with Kate, you know, you can't be trusted man. You a flip-flopper man
What the fuck are you doing?
Arthur flip flops too much, man.
Oh, man.
Eldar goes from one M to the other.
He goes, what?
You took Arthur's wrench away.
And he comes up here and then he works again.
So these flip flops too much.
I'm just saying.
Can't trust them, man.
One minute, you know, he's this inside.
I'm just saying.
Fuck that.
Yeah, he needs to bend over and he needs to bend over on his knees and have like paint a spanky
I mean psyche spanky him
It's like here you crying psyche come back. Don't cry. I love you. I
Can't get tattoos. I don't know. I'm scared of tattoos, but I'll get a henna tattoo of psyche awakened Sarah
Yeah, you should you know, you may say get that be BK GTAT, you know
So it's only right that you get a tattoo, you know, I make him do it. What the fuck? Oh, you make him do that
No, he did it cuz he loves me
He's back
Where'd you go like he did you go poo-poo or did you go take a shower?
He's mad at us I'm mad I'm mad
Um, you know, I did not uh, I was just sitting here. Will you accept his apology?
Uh, yeah, I apologize. Like he thought just an appropriate mod. I don't think for the channel
It's like I'm gonna have to like yeah, it's like
I have to go about my gut
He doesn't have to be more he can still
He's been begging for like weeks and then it's like I give it to him and then he like comes on like fucking
Yeah, that does hurt Arthur you do play that like actual like, you know, you're there
It's a quarter then you come here and like become a sarcastic and like judge
That's it. I mean, it's okay. I don't
Know no, uh, no opinion really. Let's see
The beta can't be trusted either. Yeah, I'm saying
I know. I mean, how about they trust nobody? That's like, first of all, that's the worst person to trust. He changes pictures. He does all these fuck shit.
So what?
We've got to like make no sense.
Look you do it. I mean, it's like, yeah, I got I got the I got the best picture changes if you ask me
I never do that. I'm I just sit here and I just chill
Sometimes I scream and everything get mad, but I don't change pictures. I got the best picture changes. Look at that
I mean, what a dick. I mean, he knows not to do it. It's like, right. He's such a dick.
Oh, man.
I like your glasses.
Thank you.
I have my readers under them, too.
Can I get it? Yeah, it's like, Vic, what's the fuck, Eldo? Maybe...
Right, you're gonna do that on my channel. I told you not to do like the exact same thing before
She's like he's like threatening like so it was like when you come up here trying to I just can't have people
It's like I don't know just being a regular chat. Thank you. Can you still apologize?
No, I don't care and also also and also like from now on it's like I'm also gonna like charge
I mean, I charged, you know, it's for to open a panel
because it is like, they're so,
people just went hours and hours on panel
and they expect, they feel entitled to be on the panel
for the hours and it's like,
some of these conversations I'm here.
And it's like, you know, it's like,
not even like, no one even cares, it's my show.
I mean, it's like, I shouldn't be running it better, right?
But it's like.
What do you wanna do?
How do you wanna run your show today?
I don't want to run the show today, I just like, you know, see what's happening.
I mean, it's like, I always like, I always like to just be like spontaneous with the show and I am, but it's like the panels are getting ridiculous and like, it's not like, I mean, some of them, it's just like, it's not, I mean, it's like, I don't know if that's the point, it's like, just to give me like, to like, you know, not want to do it anymore or whatever.
But it's like, I would like.
No, I think you just.
It's like there's a lot of different personalities, like some here and some come here, you know, with like humor,
drugs, some come here to troll, some come here, you know, for support. But at the end of the day,
if you have the same people coming back, they like you, you know.
I know, I know, I love so many people.
They respect your wishes. So like that does annoy the fuck out of me. Like when people change the
pictures, it's okay to change it, but at least change it to like your picture because that I'm
Yeah, but I think it was a good supporter. I think he cares about you. I think, you know, he's he has done
He has been but
He shouldn't have like I can tell me told him not to do that exactly and it's like, you know, he should just know
They're brass. They don't look it's like they're it's like they just don't listen. They just do whatever they're brass
So is there like, you know, it's like it's gonna try to I don't know if people are gonna try like
Some people don't like to channel like I get like a lot of people saying they hate me and stuff like that
So it's like of course people are gonna try to like
It's like for all the people that hate you there's a whole bunch of people that love you
You don't have haters then you know what you're not doing something right. I guess that's what they say
but I mean, I'm never it's like always
I don't think Arthur hates you. I don't think Elzo hates you. I don't think any of the people actually even the chat
I hate you. Nobody hates you
Well, it's like even if like people do hate me it's fine
But it's like you don't have to be like like you know me to me or whatever like we're disrespectful or whatever
Yeah, I understand. I mean, you know, but they can I mean it's like I'm
Seriously, okay people are used to being
This is it's the lines you gave them your own time out. Yeah, I gave him a timeout you put him the in the green room
Well, yeah, I mean just I
Don't feel like talking to some people like so there's some people like like to get some guys came on last night
They're just like retarded like there is like
they're like
big there's
Even though they just say just stupid shit. I can't even remember it was like DJ likes was there and we're like
Kind of have a conversation. It was just it was just we're like some people
I'm not talking about the Trump and RFK those were they were okay. They were kind of funny
I heard on people's podcasts. They all they believe those were real. That's crazy, right?
Yeah, that's a long time ago
Okay, he'll be back
You just need your time. Yeah, I can't I can't have people this they see like thinking that that's okay to do like
I tell you how to do that like oh
Yeah
feel like when people like do that it's almost like you're breaking the rules
you're kind of like not respecting me you know but they're here to troll and tease
and like roll things up and make it spicy but at the same time if you don't
like it it's like your rules like yeah it should be like that no but it's
anything it's like it but it's just been like really negative lately as like a
It's like I'm the same person I was in person. I have it was I don't know so I don't know
We're good or for bad. I'm
Hey olives
Negative, let me see. I went out my eyes hold up my eyes are really
Hello my glasses are oh my god your hair stuck up again
Yeah, well over there in the back look right there. Yeah, like yeah, I'll file flower or something there. Yeah, okay, okay
It's like I don't want to annoy you. I just came here. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. No, you don't I love you sweetie. You're like my best friend
I don't have really anybody here like that's why
Well, somebody nice come up here and cheer up our psyche
Page was supposed to come back all of her come back
Yeah
I don't know. I think Aldo left my arm. I'm like fucking just a couple beers and like the
McDonald's
caramel frappuccino and
A lot of the sweet
Yeah, taste of this
What I can tell my tiny little bit
You gotta go
I'm stoned as fuck. I woke up and I smoke way too early. When I wake up and I smoke, I get like so fucked up.
Yeah. Yeah. I mean, I, I, I'm pretty fucked up too. Yeah. Um, it's basically pretty strong.
Pays the best guess.
I guess Arthur is backstage again, and then a mouse-looking person. I don't know
It's JT. Oh a mouse-looking person. I'm like what?
Really a mouse?
I mean no, it's just a mouse emoji.
What's wrong is there's been a lot of negativity going on?
Talk to me psyche. What's going on?
Beta what's what's going on nothing? I'm just chilling with psyche and then he's trying to do his
You know stuff for his channel and focus on that
And then he gave Arthur a chance to be mod and then Arthur came here and started being a bride
So he's just kind of like not having a drain. Oh
Yeah, the mod thing gets it's crazy it gets out of control so fast
Like yeah, like what JT does he gets out of control sometimes, you know, super so out of control, you know
Not even that bad really compared to a lot of the shit that you that I've seen up here. I'm not that bad at all
You're fine, I don't have a phone with you, you know your bullets and respect
Oh, that's the eye the evil eye, right?
But the evil eye
Yeah
Are you get does that mean you're giving your audience the evil eye?
It protects you against like an evil like if somebody's like jealous of you or like, you know
They think that or you know, it's like protect
It's like gets rid of the evil people
But then what's the little one with the hand on it with the little eye isn't that the one that's supposed to
That's the hand of Fatima or Hamsta and it's like for protection.
It's like stop any kind of the same as the blue one.
Like that one, is it the same as that eye right there or is it?
No, but sometimes they combine it.
Sometimes they'll combine it.
They'll put the hand and the eye in the middle, but yeah.
Yeah, but no, they're two different things.
I don't know that much about that. Yeah, and Pervian cultures. They also use the evil eye, but they they don't do the blue
They do red, you know, the red is like a lot of cultures use the evil eye
Hold on elder
We should check on a we should check on a flirty man
Message that like I think today before yesterday. I was like, I hope you made it safe and you're okay, but I don't even know if you know
Hold on let me you're gonna call her
You hear that
No, he's calling her on this court
Yeah, she might be sleeping. It's pretty early.
Let's see.
Would you call the other day some dude?
Come on, Jesus, chill out.
I don't know why the same anyone ain't working. That's weird
Christine you don't want to come off hi Christine
I mean it was like having fun like just like the increase like
You're not having fun right now. What's why no no no
Who's got you discouraged what's got you down I say
I mean there's 45 people here like so that's really good. It's just like yeah
That's good. Well, but something's wrong though. What's wrong psyche?
It's right. I don't know
That Arthur guy pissed you off
Arthur well
Arthur's like he's fine. I'm getting dirty on the ones for a while. You know, yeah, I
Mean, you know, these people pretty good, right? I mean you've known her for five months now, right? You know what they do
Not really you don't know them. I don't really like you know, I did them on my show like I talked to this
Doctor beta outside the show, but like not I'm gonna talk to too many outside of the show
You really know these people
What you do decide beta, please I didn't do anything to sign wasn't you beta?
No, me, Paige and Psyche, he was reading us a story and then we were just playing around
with it.
We changed our witch names to Paige and Bita and Good Times and this and that and we're
just laughing and having a good time and we're going to play trivia and then I don't know.
I really don't know what happened.
I just think like Psyche, just do whatever makes you happy, whatever you want to do.
I mean, I am, and it's, I am, it's like, just, it seems like
The thing, if he does what makes him happy, other people are gonna bitch about it
Well, then talk to them, they can bitch about it, they don't have to watch
No, it's like
He's just like burning the show like all I want to do is like run this like I have an entertaining show
Everybody else wants to run your show too. That's the problem
Right, but it's like but no one's like if you want to be part of the show people
I mean like no one's like helping me like I had doing like this
I mean people are helping me that you know because they come on the panel and talking stuff like that
But it's like it's like I'm like
Yeah, the other day man, it's really whatever the fuck you want to do
At the end of the day, it's really whatever you want to do. Yeah
You already have like a merch out you got like your monitor
It's all good steps, I mean, I won't make any money like my immersion dice realistic, you know
It was two days ago. I mean come on like
Yeah, I know, but it's like I'm just like I don't expect like
I don't know people think I'm like trying to like I don't know what do they think you're doing. I
Don't know they think I'm like a horrible person or something like why?
I don't know you're a horrible person for doing what for running a fucking stream. Like what are you doing?
The thing is that you'll never will never be like an answer. It'll just be like a bunch of like it's anyway
That's the thing man
It's not even you're seeing the streaming shit. That's that's what it ends up becoming like you got to please every fucking body
And then you can't please anybody and then you can't please yourself. It's like really it's fucked up
It's fucked up. Yeah, but it's like
Cuz then you you end up realizing like most of the people that watch your shit not about well
Yeah, I'm gonna say most there's some good ones, right? There are good ones, but a lot of them
Maybe even the majority they just kind of want to run your shit
like
It's kind of like that and then if you alienate those people
It's like you're alienating the people that want to run your shit
It's like you're like do I want to keep them or do I want to do what I want to do?
You're like I like I like certain people and I say I like and then it's like a certain people like other people like it
So I'll take I'll take people and people I don't like and people will get mad and then I'll bring people better
I don't like I don't even like on like I think else. What's the guy's name? Like LD or whatever?
He I can't like that's not I couldn't stand him and I was like it was just like cringing the whole time
And I can't I don't like him and then it's like and then he's so judgmental of me
I was always tried to be like like at least like
Give him a chance to like explain himself or whatever
You said all day or no, no, no ld ld right is that his name like the guy like yeah, ld right ld. Yeah. Yeah
He just comes here he just comes here like bugs me like and then it's like that ever that everyone's mad at me like I'm like
Don't fucking let him on he brings nothing to the table bunch of controversies and it's just
Why just don't let him on it just you don't have to I don't know if it's LD that's got you fucked up
Or if it's the way people don't like you know, I'm not sure which one I know
No, I mean, I don't I don't really have a team. I'd like his dog and he's brought his dog out a bunch of times and I look like
He's a dog. It's a nice dog. Yeah, it's like a greyhound and stuff and the dog's always happy and it's like I love him
Yeah, happy dogs because I don't have a guy on my channel. He doesn't really do anything. He just kind of sits there
He does it. He sits there. Yeah, I know and it's like and then it's like
Or just like it says like
The shit that people say about him and I don't fucking know one way or the other about it
I really don't give a shit because it's got nothing to do with it
And I say yeah, it's none of my business and it's like but it's also had nothing to do. He didn't do it on my show early
So I don't I just
He's doing something crazy on your show like is he doing? No, he did nothing. He did nothing
He just threw the shirt off and like I guess what did you do last night? I don't want to be like
No, you know what it is. You got everyone bitching about you. Oh, you got LD up there
Oh, they're they want to associate you with whatever the fuck they they they say about LD like oh psyche has LD up here
Oh, I didn't know you support this shit
Yeah, I know and I agree. He meant what you're saying. Yes, it's our Smurfs. Exactly
He's like, you know, whatever he was like, he's just not interested in it, but it's like benefit. I kind of like sometimes they like
It's not worth the bullshit for Abbot in here. That's basically the gist. Yeah
He's not really doing anything, but he doesn't have to his reputation. It's already fucked. I know
But I keep saying I'm gonna like I'm gonna like
They have like less people on the panel like more selective and like sometimes like I won't well
I want to open a panel for like a while and so it's like it's like
You know, but I think that that'll be good because it's like even if people don't like me then it's like that at least, you know
Even I can monetize maybe I can monetize hate toward me. I guess that's the next step to go, right?
I don't think you need to worry about like starting little people, you know
If you want to have them up here fine, but look at like um, I always say chat wins, you know
What the chat wants and if you're gonna have a bunch of people leave because somebody up there is just boring as fuck and
Well, I can I there's certain words I can't say up here, but yeah, you already know
I know, but it's just not that he's also kind of like
Cranches like the nigga suspect. He had a little girl on this platform
And you know, that's what he's known for basically, right?
So he's got that reputation anybody that talks to him's gonna have that reputation whatever
That's the whole thing about it. So it's like if you have him up here, they're gonna they're all gonna be like
They're all gonna turn on you basically whether he's doing anything or not
Yeah, that's fine. I mean, it's like
I don't know. It's like
He just sits there, you know, he's got the dog
I was I would like to have like interesting people on the show and so it's like, you know
So so so he's just not interesting on the show
I think and then I like people have seen the show, but it's like yeah
Then Goddie's like good on the show like sometimes we've been the six. He's here a lot, right? You like Goddie
Yeah, he was here. He was on last night a bunch of times and like
He's a nice and you know, we'll see. Yeah
Yeah, I mean you're fine. Yeah
Well, yeah, the elbow cosplay as the unabomber. Yeah
Yeah
Interesting that guy was very interesting get to see his whole like you know look a lot
Why did he say some of these psychopaths type out this huge long manifesto?
And so he has this big manifesto if he's actually kind of a brilliant guy
I think we might was your college professor or something
The guy was the guy the UNA BOMB ER like whoever that guy is right
No, it's about the guy that was up here talking about spirituality and stuff and everybody
And then yeah, I like reading manifestos are kind of interesting right here. I haven't read I didn't read that one minute
How did we get on the unibomber? That's crazy cuz you did what you did so much just mentioned it didn't they?
Oh, they're saying Aldo looks like the unibomber. Oh, yeah glasses. Well, yeah, stop stop stop saying the word
Oh, I don't like that word. Oh the other guy. Yeah, okay. Yeah, here's a message for madness
I don't understand a gremlin and he's allowed who's gremlin?
You understand him and he's loud. Who's that?
I don't know man. It's like that. It's like, um
Do you want to run your channel or do you want your chat to run your channel? It's basically the question
I run the channel. I run the channel and I think I do I run the channel
And it's like I really I really am but i'm just like
I do let people talk and I think it's like, you know, so it's like, but it's not interesting for me
Some of it's not interesting for me or it's like just plain offensive or disrespectful to me on like my show
And it's like now it's getting to like where it's like, oh, like, you know, so many people have left because they just get chased away
Like so many things like everyone's here that comes in is like pretty much like, you know
He's pretty much has been ignoring me. Yeah, so
you know
So it's, it's fine. It's like, I understand.
All right. All right.
But if they're ignoring you, then they're not really your friends.
They're not your two friends because they try to, they try to.
No, it's not the panel.
The people that take the whole chat.
It's like everybody else.
You need to be in charge and you need to be like, you know what?
If you don't like something, you'll be like, you know, I like when you do that.
You're like, you know what? I don't like it.
Shut the fuck up.
Change the subject.
Yeah, be assertive and just say what you like and what you don't like you don't you know, no, I don't like it
Or I do like it
If you don't like religious talk just be like I don't want it
Period, you know
Dude, the chat is gonna always try to run your shit as much as you as much as they can
Like that's always gonna be the case. So it's like
All right, either you know, you're you're always gonna be that position
The chat most of them I
Don't know I wouldn't even I mean it's up to you of course you know you want to if you want to grow your channel
You're gonna have to have a lot of
It's gonna be more and more people trying to run your shit basically
Well, no one's going to try I mean it's like there's you know, but it's like why it's like no one tries to run other people
There's like why is it like all mine is like why?
That's kind of how streamers. Yeah a lot of the streamers
Like I don't say I'm gonna I'm gonna close down in Japan. I mean, I'll slow
I'll stop three panels, but or else I'll do panels that it's like I'm gonna need like
You know, I'm gonna have to have people sponsor panels if they want to have panels and then it's like
They know people are getting greedy now you're getting greedy because I'm not getting greedy. I'm not getting greedy
I'm not getting greedy. Oh, it's more of a structure the way he
I think $10 you're like
People can come together put $10 for it. I can have they can have three hours of like just say whatever they want on the panel
Pretty much and they can say whatever they want to me and that's at least like some kind of compensation, but it's like
So if I give you $10 I can say what I want for the next three hours, thank you
Say what in terms of tea not under to us, you know, you
But yeah, it's not as respectful.
You can see whatever you want to.
I'll call it open panel then.
Yeah, but see.
Yeah.
OK, well, it's closed, but it's like, it's open to everybody.
But I'm saying, it's not per person.
It's going to be like, you know, just to open the panel.
And then I've been so, I don't have to open the panel.
It's what people want to do.
No, it's not the panel.
The panel's not the problem.
It's the chair.
OK, guys, then I already did it tonight,
and Crucible Ghost sponsored the panels.
And so I thought it was just like so.
It's like, oh my god.
Most of the time it's not the panel.
I don't care. I mean, I ignore so much of it so much of that in the chat. I do. Yeah, I don't like really
What what it's always it's my whatever Doug. Yeah, come on
It's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like
I mean, yeah, and I was thinking I was like maybe one day where it's like I'll have like a free like open panel
It will just be like, you know, and then it's like and then but then like some other days
I wouldn't either have like people come up
I wouldn't either be performing like a like a reading for them or something like that or like, you know
like a good friend I trust not all these new people that are coming in and this like trying to like
Just be weird and it's like it's like
It's like totally not the topic. It's like it just things have been off topic of the show and I just feel like and I've also feel like kind of like
I
Wanted around my own show and it's kind of like having weird cuz a lot of me and I'm gonna be brutally honest with you
A lot of people don't want you they don't give a fuck about you or your show
They just want a place where they can come and do their shit
That's the fuck yeah, well, it's like that's like that's not here. It's like they can go do it like it's really
Well, they like doing it here because you're open a lot like you know what I'm saying like if that's well
I have it
Because they like you too, they just want to come in
That's true, too, but I know you got a lot more fuckers
You just want to come up here and use your shit to do what they want to do. Yeah. Yeah, same thing with the check
And it's like I don't mind people are allowed to like, you know, they can like post links in the chat
They can come up and like if it lets them promote their show I've had good interviews
But it's like people just been so they're so mean to each other. They're so like they're people are mean to me
They're like it is like I mean it's fine. There's interesting people and then there's people that are just like
Like so by bipolar, it's like there's there's too many personalities to deal with it. I don't know what I'm gonna get
It's like very throws me off balance, right?
It's a I can't please everybody of course and it's like and there's so many different kinds of people and it's like
But it's like I don't I want to be able to like
Communicate with the audience and like you with the audience like it's like me. Let's say the audience hates me
That's what there's no point. It's like it's like it's like I'm not here. The channel is not gonna be your guy
It's like I just like
You are aiding you it's about using your shit to do what people want to do really and you have you have some people that like you of course
But the majority of them just want to use your shit to do whatever the fuck they want to do
Whether it's on the panel or the chat and a lot of them want to think they could pay you to do that
They could give you a little money and then just tell you what to do like I don't know
It's
It's like I don't mind. I mean, I don't mind and I especially I really don't mind anybody can promote their stuff here
I don't understand it's not a problem. I'm just saying like
At least like respect by respect me or like at least like, you know, I don't know. It's it feels like I like the likes
Yeah, because people don't see the like me anymore because I had like 500 people come in the last chat and there were like 12 likes
So that's a 12 out of like, I don't even know it's like one
It's like less than 1% of like people like even like it's a like button
What was going on on the pit where you doing what you wanted to do like when they when that?
Were you doing like
a lecture on and and then
And then there's two like weird guys. They had them on for a couple of hours. It's just like then
Here's the thing
It's just like the more the more drama the more bullshit the more likes the more abuse really
Well, yeah, but it's not it's like it's like not that's like no one's paying attention to anything all day. I mean they're
They're just talking in chat like
They don't really like here. I need you up there as long as they got a place to do their shit
Then you're not even you're in the background basically on your own. Yeah, but I mean, that's fine
I mean, that's fine. I mean, it's like it shouldn't be like I shouldn't be
Like a lot of times you can because a lot of people like, you know, forget to like like the chat
You know the mod is going fast, but you can do this like when I get to like 50 likes
I'll do like two card readings the short ones. You know what I mean. Yeah
Uh-huh, yeah
Yeah, I mean, I'll do things like that. I mean, I mean, I'm gonna keep like
Hold on to their content till they get like a turn on look at Elda. I'll go is like when I get to you know
And I'm gonna you know, I'll show this like whatever this and that so yeah, I mean you can do that kind of stuff
But you're still learning you I mean, it's like
have to be risky and stuff like that, but it's like, I feel like, yeah, there, there have some
people that have like, you know, like certain people have like, this is so like, you're pretty
generous, and then it's like, they either turn on me like in a weird way, or they think, or it's like,
it just feels like there's something, I'll turn your motor. You mean like generous with the money?
No, no, not necessarily that, but it's like, yeah, it's like, there's people that it's like
Or there's people that have thrown any kind of donation on my face like stuff like that
It's like yeah, that's the whole thing like they pay you and then they think they can run your shit like they can pay for it
Yeah, but it's like it's like but it's like I think it's like
It would be generosity or if I provide services and stuff like that. And so I think that's what they
There's almost always an ulterior motive
I wouldn't feel guilty. I would just do whatever the fuck I want to do at this point. Yeah, I'm going to I'm going to thank you guys
You're gonna take a hit on the likes and views and all that shit though if you do what you want to do
That's then right you're telling me
That's cool tonight. But yeah, it was like the last video I was on for several hours and let's see
And there was like, like 500 people came in and like, and then it was like, like hardly anybody, like even like, at least like,
So I don't know if that's my fault. I didn't even like say, oh, I'd like to video and like, you know, more like, uh...
No, it's not your fault is because you go live so often that it's like people are just here all the time. It's like, you know, sometimes they forget. Sometimes it's just like, but yeah, I think they just need to be reminded and then you can like throw incentive where, hey, when I get to 20 or 25 likes, I'll do one reading for randomly, you know, this and that.
you can get the likes but remember the dislikes also help your algorithm too.
It's hard to use in the fair.
Okay, I'm sorry
I think there's a huge misconception on what likes and dislikes do
First of all, these are our very tiny channels if you get a hundred people in here
So like would you say that that's good for your stream one of your streams? Oh, yeah
I mean, that's like, you know, I only hit over a hundred a few times
As a base right let's say you give a hundred people in here and 80% of the people hit the like button
that's not going to help your algorithm at all.
I know, but the point is, I don't know if people like this show,
but if they want to come in and give a like, I don't know if they're subscribed.
If you're using it to judge your performance and how well the stream is doing, that's great.
But if you think, you know, having 100 people in your chat and 80% of the people
clicking the like button is going to help you in the algorithm, you're mistaken.
These are our teeny tiny channels in tiny communities.
So yeah, it's the algorithm isn't gonna favor you, you know, they they want the bigger channels
I mean, it's engagement. I've been trying to do engagement like I've been I've been like talking to the chance stuff like that
I didn't make the child was going to get like I love there's so many people in the chap that it's like
They're so mostly negative or it's just like nothing to do with
You like Alyssa Alyssa Jordan, whatever the fuck her name is
Lisa yeah, she gets a lot more, you know viewers than any of us do right and even to her
Our RG you are wrong easy. You're one of those guys that think you're gonna be a YouTube superstar. No, these are tiny fucking communities
And a hundred a hundred viewers is nothing
It's nothing that the likes and dislikes mean nothing YouTube does not care about you
You're not gonna get thrown into the fucking algorithm out of nowhere and then start getting 10,000 live viewers
It's just it doesn't work like that anymore. No
Is that yeah, I don't think that's even what you're trying. I mean, or are you trying to like blow up or something because I mean, let's be real
No, you mean like no, I'm talking to site. Yeah. Oh, yeah
Someone says she's like to maybe short. Yeah, I do it. She did and it's like I'm just like they have like music
And I'm just being careful right now. My point is don't pay attention to the likes and dislikes
Uh, don't let that bother you. It's your your channel. Do
I'm worried I'm worried that is that people like the show and it's like it's or people like the show and it's like
Well part of it is like
people like doing what they want to do and when you do what you want to do they don't like that
that's just the reality like so you you have a choice to do what you want to do or do what
they want you to do simple but i'm happy like my numbers are pretty good um you know i do have like
10,000 watch hours a month and it got like, you know, like really like just the numbers like really good
You know, it's like just because it means like I talked at least I had like, you know
I think about 10 or 10,000 hours. She said she said it was really really good
You know, and she was like impressed because it was like pretty quickly after I
at the like
It's like don't got 30 likes
That's how you gotta do it site
Yeah
And we have like I went through a lot of like relationships. It's like I like really love people and
You know, I think it's really hurts when like I give you like
Man, you're not here to make friends. You're here to watch
It's extremely helpful for what would see what's overall goal here
But yeah, you know viewing the commenting all that it's all going to help
Yeah, you're never gonna get thrown into the algorithm. It's never gonna happen. I know I am in the algorithm
Yeah, they do I have I could tell you I have like half a million impressions like
YouTube like we'll put out impressions and it's like it's why I have like
Really like a lot of people come from this impression and like
They uh the demographics or whatever you chasing a dream that left 10 years ago
I was doing well. I'm doing well. I'm doing like I was I'm actually um
There's a memberships, you know, like a like a hundred memberships is like, you know, that's that's pretty good like with uh
That's good. I mean that's cool. Yeah, I don't think let's I mean being realistic. You're not gonna blow up being a streamer, right?
But I mean, it's like slowly, I mean, many, I mean, you know, like, you know, Emma did and like, you know, people have, and I think like I have something, like I have some kind of talent.
They've been training for like years, like Alisa.
No, she hasn't. No, no, no, no, Emma, no, Emma was just sort of shooting last year.
No, I'm not talking about Emma. Nobody knew of Emma until you told us about her. Everybody knows Alisa.
I'm not comparing myself to Lisa. I know Lisa's been doing it for like since 2020 or even earlier. She was posting stuff
So I know I just started and stuff like that
Post one or two shorts. It happens. Yeah, I can I can I do have one short of me
I just think like you should pat yourself over the back because you're doing good
You got monetized you got like, you know and slowly by literally surely you'll get up whatever to what you want
But you're very competitive and I know I've been going
You're very competitive, but you're just kind of like not patient. You're just in a rush. You do you want it like okay?
And now I got this accomplished. I want I want this. You know what I mean?
I'm I'm super patient. I am super patient and it's like I am patient and I but I'm like I'm doing a lot and it's like and then
It's like I get like a lot of shit and it's like
I'm trying
I mean
I'm doing fine, it's it's way okay, but it's like at the same time it's like it's just like I don't like the vibes lately
I don't like uh, like a lot of the way people that are treating me and
um, and just like talking to me sometimes and so I
That's well if i'm doing too much that's fine, but it's like i'm doing what i'm doing, you know, i say and uh
Whatever, it's like I'm
No, I don't disagree with what are you saying? I'm saying I'm saying I'm saying yeah
I'll probably have you know
I want to do the show like I'm trying to make changes to the show and do things differently and have like
Certain guests on if there's something I can't stand like certain people now like now. I hate to say like I don't like there's some people like
Used to like like Canada dry and now it's like he like drives me crazy and he's just like
Just so airy. I just like he just makes you
He wants but he wants to be here up
I know he wants to be up on the show and stuff and then it's like I feel like they get finally get annoyed
What do you just say? What did you tell him? Did you be like, yeah?
I don't know. Yeah. Well, yeah, I've kept them
I mean, I've taken them off the show and kept them backstage for like over an hour and like just ignore them
It's like and it's like I'll do that but it's like it's just like
some people just piss me off and I don't even feel like acknowledging them and uh yeah he was like
he's just like not a it's just like not a good guess and then but he wants to be here and like
but then it's like oh let me come in and just like ignore me be rude be rude to me it's like
my show I at least want to be acknowledged and like you know people to like at least like not be like
It's figure. Everyone's just like so like salty to me. It's like I'm doing good. Thank you. You annoy the fuck out of me
Not not Canada dry or whoever you annoy the fuck out of me if you want to be on the panel
You can be on the panel for an hour for a ten dollars an hour, but you still can't break the rule, you know
Yeah
Let's be honest
I don't know I'm just giving an example of whatever I don't know I don't know the more you do what you want to do
The more pushback you're gonna get
Okay, I know
What you want to do it's your fucking I know it gets it gets you know, and you're gonna get a lot of pushback
Yeah, people are gonna not like this
My stream
Yeah, I know
I don't know
Who gives a fuck what they like they like something one day they hate it the next day who cares you don't need fickle shit like that
Do which I guess I guess I guess you better take my yelling. It's yeah, I do care about
But the audio I do care about
Three viewers JT you ain't got no you got nobody been talking about my shit. I don't even do that
Well, there are they did does seem to be people come here to Sykes because on their personal channels
They get three or four viewers a big pipes is one Joker is another so they come over here
It's same thing with Scotty on beat of the channel. They come over here because they finally have an audience
And that somehow empowers them and that's pretty fucking weird, too
Three times and then I have fun of him or whatever so I don't even know you are he never came back thankfully
Yeah, he's a weirdo dude
He just likes to argue with like nonsense
And i'm not even throwing your old cats like that, but i'm gonna say probably the majority of them is like that
Yeah, well, I'm saying but I'm saying most of these people that are doing this have never like are not members
I'm not donated and they just like it. It's like come in like a great title sometimes some of these people and it's like better
You've got a personality that likes I mean, I'm not saying you're
Yeah, if they want to use the panel for like a long time, it's like, you know, it's like, you know
I don't know. I just think it just feels like I'm just being used and then it's like kind of like
Because you are being
Yeah, yeah, okay, so I keep notes if you have someone on panel in your chat drops by 20 make a note of it
So when the maybe not let them up next time, but you don't have to say it out loud
Say a big pipe comes comes up here and 10 people leave
You know make a little note of that
You know because you do have an appeal to the chat too because that's what these panel streams are right
It doesn't have to announce it, but just keep notes of that type of thing
Mm-hmm black RG. Are you are you pretty someone's uncle this troll king? Oh, that's cyber supreme. He uh
That's Jimmy's boyfriend. He cams up all the time. They take that's taken away from his stream. I'm not doxing
Yeah
That's not really his name
Okay, but I don't know I don't know I don't know I don't know I don't like it because people can think there's privacy stuff
I don't know
Channel when he babbles and nobody said three viewers
Like you're gonna jump down. I love you hang in there. You're doing good. Thank you
Do whatever makes you happy fuck everyone else that's my advice. Well, yeah, thank you
Thank you. Love you. Thank you RG. Oh, yeah, it's okay. It rains up there. Oh, she's a what we
I don't know you tell me rain. No, she's not talking to you. She's talking to chat
I
Should I but I do like you know I try not to take chess personally, but when it's when they're my chest
And that's like it out. I will take these personally like
Yeah, I mean if it's that you somebody's saying it to you sometimes you'll read something
I'll notice you'll read it out of context and you'll take it like it's like a directed at you
Yeah, sometimes even if it's sometimes this is a terrible thing for other people
I don't think anybody should be slandered in the chat or like oh, yeah, I just slandered up and down in this bitch
I don't care. I mean, you know, I know but it's yeah
I don't like that people are being bullied in my chat and it's like I'm I wish I could do a better job of like
Stopping it and like it's also people are also
It's hard
Show some love
Thank You be that 36 people and thank you 36 people like thank you guys. I give you a like fucking. What's how hard is it to give?
Yeah, and I do like I think the monitor guy also, you know, I
Don't know. I don't want to fit
They have a new thing where they have like these like text ads or something they put next to the screen
And so they're giving the creators more ad revenue. I think they're trying to but it's like that's like the smallest
portion of the revenue for the channel is like at the ad revenue
But I most of my videos I don't monetize them or I put it into like some numbers. Yeah. Thank you guys
So easy can make millions of one day grow up you to get a job on it. Uh-huh. Come on black
Come on, don't talk about something like that here trust on baby. He got plenty of money
I don't have any money
I'll probably get the rain got cleaned up that's the thing though. You got miles in here that just do shit. I don't mean
Yeah, it's not lie. It's not like you could do the lot about that. Yeah, I'm always get timed out and then they leave
They're like, wow, you know
The yeah, although it's like that's in your business and yeah, it's for you if you bring keep saying stuff like that
It's like really out of pocket. And so, you know, oh shit. What did he say? Oh?
Nothing. We don't need to refuse. Okay. So anyway
Yeah, it's better. Well, you what happens and sometimes like you get
Like you'll monster and people and then they want to gay keep your things like you're you're you're chat
So it's like they'll block people they'll time people out that they don't like or they don't like what they're saying the time
Like we're in just got timed out. She didn't say anything crazy, but it's like
People that kind of shit is gonna alienate you basically like
She's like, I don't know
She's not she's not nice to me in the chat. She's like rude to me in the chat
She's like she just talks shit about me. That's all I see for me. It wasn't you that timed her out
No, I'm gonna have my cat. Oh, why is she gonna be nice to you and you're just letting people time her out for no reason
Okay, now I'm saying like
I know before before before before before she got timed out
I don't think it's the first time she's been timed out, but I've ever heard of and it's like it's just happened
I'm talking about right before that it was like hey, that's fine
So as we feed is there unless she's like she didn't really say anything that bad. It's like it finished
You know, you know what happens when you get a bunch of mods. They want to gatekeep your channel like
Basically, that's why yeah
Okay, so I don't know did it. I'm not a mom. I can't see it, but I know she didn't say anything crazy
Oh, yeah
Let's see. Okay. Yeah, I know I'm basically I'm not letting them gas like me. I'm just trying to like
Cash like you
Thank you, I mean people are gaslighting me, but it's like you know, not necessarily you but I'm saying like you know
I understand I mean I've seen people try to do it, but I'm not doing that right now
Why is that the best thing I do the elders elders this page please be a little elder was saying some
Like things he shouldn't be saying like he was just like being really disrespectful to me, and I didn't appreciate it
Yeah
No, it's not about me heatman or whatever the fuck you call yourself
does he may never come up
you're a woman right
yeah
hi Paige
hi
how are you
I don't mean to the wine
we're just having a conversation
I know I wasn't gone for a long time
now let's come back to this
upsetting damaging chaos
what's going on
No, my show is chaos. I love a chaos. It's pretty chaotic, but that's why we love it, right?
Well, yeah, I mean I like it I like it but
I was
Psych let's get them
Just you know
It's a few that when you do it so many people you know some people are
Take it personally if there's too many I know can't identify one. Let's just leave it be
I don't know. I feel like you got to the point where your your channel doesn't feel like it's in your control
Maybe maybe that's what you feel. I don't know
You don't think it's in my control?
Wait, how is it not in my control?
I don't know, are you telling me?
Even if I was to let people run, it ultimately, I run the channel.
I turn it on when I want to turn the channel on, I turn it off.
I take people off stage if I want them off stage, I bring them on.
I'll do it unapologetically, I'll just do it like I want to do.
So how am I not into what is how do you say I'm not saying you're not I do I do all the work I do everything on it
Okay, so how am I not?
In control of my channel. No, I'm saying maybe it feels out of your control. Sometimes it doesn't feel out of my control
And that's the same that is they trying to like put that in my head like oh, I feel like I'm out of control
I understand what you're doing and it's like it's just a suggestion of it is like it was offensive
So it's like why are you like what would you say like maybe negative suggestions like trying to like maybe you okay?
Okay
What is it? How is it not they tell me how it's not how would
How is it? Who's running the channel? Who's running the channel? It's not me. Who is it? Who is it? Is there anybody in my stream yard?
Good morning everybody. I don't know, your mods, I don't know.
Tell me. What? What's mods? Mods are like fine.
I don't expect the moths to mob because it's like
They don't they just they don't like that's it. That's that's whatever who can't
Whatever it's like if she's got offended by something she said she probably how long she's time we're out for one minute or five minutes
It's like I don't know I can't say I'm the what you're acting like it's the end of the world
It's like it's like you know, it's just be out of the page chat for like five minutes
Okay
Happy birthday, I'm sorry. Thank you. I thought I like it. I can't also can't believe it. Thank you
Well, I didn't know that you knew that did you know it was on my birthday? I didn't know you I had no idea. I had no idea
I had no idea
Um, well, let's see. It's, uh, what day is it? It's the 18th. Oh, seven, 18. Nice. Yeah.
About 16. Yeah. I mean, it's cool to be able to find, you know. Yeah. What are you doing
for your birthday, say? Well, we're going out later. Yeah. Still early.
Well, obviously I just feel like you're gonna be like a family dinner and then go out go and hang his friends like what together
Oh, yeah, we're gonna do something with the family and then rain and I are gonna go out later
So yeah, we got we got a plan. Oh, it sounds really good. Awesome. It's gonna be fun
Wishing you the best day ever. Thank you. Appreciate that. You're welcome
We done tarot today
Kind of
Yeah, well
Number one's a card or few cards for you reading. Okay. Thank you, Chris. I'll get to you
You know, I'm gonna read from this Guardians of the night. Who's how long for you. Hold on
I'll check rain check not to use that next day by using medium some same deck so I'll have to do opposite days
I don't use that one very often actually neither do you hey?
No, I haven't for a while
Yeah, I love that too
Yeah, the meanings are cool the perception of the art I suppose you would see uh-huh
Yeah, there's some great stuff. I can't wait so my I have like fives x coming from from a chemo. Okay, so I've seen
Christine I have
Christine I have this king of pentacles. Okay, so this is like, you know, this is a beautiful bowl. Is this a beautiful bowl?
What deck is this? I like that. This is called the Guardians of the Night Tarot. I'll show you the cover of it.
It's like the pink firefly moon on the back that I used not long ago.
I used it just recently. Yeah, I like the artwork. Yeah, it's pretty cool.
And they have a great, this one has a great book. And so, you know, King of Pentacles is a man.
King of Pensacles says when you see the world as a place of abundance with
ever expanding resources you will feel the king of technical support of energy
and you will be financially free. The king asks you to let go of lack, be
generous, release resources because doing so opens the door for new
opportunities that will help you generate more wealth.
When you focus on lack of feelings, lack or feelings of scarcity, you create a block that will prevent abundance or financial gains.
The King of Pentacles asks that you open your wallet and give what you can without worry or fear.
Give the barista at your local coffee shop a little extra.
Buy a couple of boxes of Girl Scout cookies.
Do donate to your favorite charity.
There are plenty of ways to get the positive flow moving.
Open the door for positive energy that comes from a generous spirit as it holds the power to raise your vibration as a result
You'll attract more opportunities for wealth and abundance to flow to you
When you draw king of tentacles in a reading consider if you're stepping in
To help a situation or offering your services and skills to help others succeed or are you holding back?
Because of their eyes placement, cows have a unique ability to see their position from
every angle.
Cows or cattle can see what is in front of them and what is behind them.
Because of this, when you walk with the cow, not only will you gain a vision for the future,
you'll remember your past.
Call on the patient and reliable cow and you feel you need to find perspective when you
feel perhaps detached from your roots, it will lovingly lead you in the right direction.
Grace nourishment sacred guardianship good portion and focus so there you go Christine
You want to come on more I got first
so
Oh, thank you. Thank you, Joe. I like thank you. Appreciate that. Okay, anybody want a card if guys if you're a member
You can just put a little crystal ball in the chat and I will say reading and then I can I'll know you want like a card or two
Or three if you want to another card, Christine, I can I want to offer more cards to the members
So if you want another one, I got you I can do it
You'd like anytime
Thank you, Christine. Love you. Okay donated for a reading. Okay
Okay, oh, I'm so sorry. I didn't I didn't see Kate. I'm so sorry. Hold on
Usually would come up on my thing Kate. Okay, I don't see it, but I'll I'll read for Kate. Let me see
Thank you Kate very much. I appreciate you, you know, I
Did it come up as a not sure if it came up as a super chat or but I should have seen it on
Okay. I apologize.
I'll try to pay better attention to this chat.
Yeah. I got a source.
It's okay here. Hey, when do you get to do that?
I'll give you a refund. It's fine.
I just didn't see it.
Did somebody tell me in the chat?
I didn't see anybody tell me until this now.
I don't see it.
No, no, no.
Just for the chat. Oh, okay read for the chat. Okay. I'll do it. Oh, I'll do a collective. Okay. Did you want to throw one card Kate?
I want to do one car for Kate. Okay, it's okay. I put you one car three. I want to see like one person for you at least
They're like a pretty good
Jack I'll do one person for you
Okay
Do it
I just sent one saying, breathe, and how about a reading for a chat.
Aww.
Okay, here's your card.
You got the page, oh, come on, page of pentacles.
Okay, you got the page of pentacles.
A beautiful octopus.
Okay, page of pentacles.
Okay, so this is like, a lot of times we'll be getting at some kind of new, something
new financially, something that can grow into something, but I'll, I like the description
they give in this book.
The wise octopus brings a wealth of assets from the ability to strategically camouflage itself to regenerating a missing arm.
To your situation, when you call on the octopus energy, you will feel supportive forces from every angle creating and generating abundance.
The Page of Pentacles brings the message that you have the power to manifest that which
you desire sees the opportunity when it rises.
The Page of Pentacles asks that you take purposeful and practical action for obtaining your goal.
Your situational benefits from a realistic approach when that places a heavier emphasis
on doing rather than dreaming.
Your efforts will be rewarded.
Stay patient.
Focus on moving forward.
Manifesting a goal can take time and you may encounter challenges, use obstacles or setbacks as a way to prove yourself
dependable and dedicated to fully realizing your dream.
And then it says, in the page of Pentecost appears to be ready for an opportunity that
will spark a change, that the wise octopus help you find clarity in the situation as
it propels you forward from the murky water and into an open sea of possibilities.
Intelligent, flexible, adaptable, concealing, and regrowth.
I'm so sorry.
Let me see.
So there you go.
Ah, you're a thank you kid. You're so cute. I was trying to be nice and say that was really nice
Yeah
You get a phone call. Okay. I gotta take it. I'll come back. Okay. Okay. They always calling is driving me nuts
Up dad jts you want a card? Oh, yeah, it's a good card. Why not? Okay?
Okay, okay. Well, you got this okay, so you got the two of swords and it's a cute frog
Okay, so two of swords is all kind of cross drove but sometimes it means tunnel vision or
You know, it's a meeting to make a decision on which way to go like, you know
Which which path to take and it's like not necessarily knowing which ones to take
I might have an option of two paths.
Okay, but this says right here.
The fourth frog is stuck in the two swords sticking up out of the water.
Of course, if you ask this frog, he'll tell you everything's fine, he's just hanging out.
But in reality, he can't see land in the fog that hovers over the water reveals only murky shadows
of what might be potential threats and the frog is scared to death.
The energy of the two of swords is one that carries indecision of avoiding discomfort
because you do not have enough information to make a choice.
blocking you from moving forward. The two of swordsmen indicate that you know exactly what needs to be done.
However, emotionally, you're not ready to acknowledge the truth. As a result, you find yourself mentally unable to deal with responsibility.
You may be constantly choosing to stay in the dark. If others around you possess the information that would require you to take action or results and
losing a comfortable position, ignorance can be blissed.
But rarely does it help the situation advance. The frog represents possibility in your life.
Master of transformation the creature has moved up and out of the mud and into the clear night sky
It says when you connect with the energy not only we would enjoy the benefits of change will spark a transformation within
I'll open the doors for a new and fortuitous possibilities
But so it can mean growth balance prosperity transformation, which are all good things
It just means you maybe have to make a decision about it, right?
Decision but there's some things that I got to know first that I don't yeah
But the frog will be okay. He's gonna be okay, but he looks okay. He looks fine. He's gonna be fine. He's gonna be fine.
Looks like he's chilling.
Full the sec.
So, yeah, what is the deck? The deck is called the Guardians of the Night's Hero.
I got this from clumsy clairvoyance when
She's still talking to me from the book right on the novel
Guardians of the night remember there's a movie called the Guardians
But I think that's more about like you know there's Jack Jack Frost and like some like you know the tradition like Santa Claus
And so if there's a traditional like mythological
Guardians or whatever
There is a movie called that okay, so this card just popped out of the deck a couple cards. Okay. Wow, okay
So we had this one there's bees all over it. This is the tenophenicals. Okay, I think these are bees or these bees
Yes, tenophenicals and so the tenophenicals. This is the abundance card and so there's abundance and so maybe you will be
You know working together with others with for abundance
I just remind you kind of like the internet a little bit with the
That's the way it's connected and like people are at their each their little flower, right? And then it's like, you know, but they're communicating and
You know, collecting different honey and stuff, so maybe we'll make some money online.
And maybe make a lot of money online, because we got the Page of Wands, and again, these
pages are starting something you're repassioned about, and so maybe there will be something
working together that will help you profit.
And so I will read you about the Page of Wands, though, but I will tell you the 10 of Pentacles
It's a page of wands, it's going to be something to grow into, something you're going to be
really passionate about.
So I would experiment, what would you like to do online, find something that is, there's
so many millions of ways to do a lot of stuff, just make your dreams come true online.
Better opportunity than people had in a long time.
then keywords from the Page of Laws are creative, confident, and enthusiastic.
If you're thinking about these qualities, the bower bird comes to my mind.
Let me show you this bird.
And a bird is like sitting outside right now, right?
The fanciful bird is an artist or romantic and it takes animal creativity to a whole
new level by creating a work of art that seduces the mate.
The bower bird combs the land looking for bright, glittery, complementary objects with
an eye toward the aesthetic as it designs an entrance to its nest.
When the page of wands appears, your current situation will benefit from conjuring up a
little enthusiasm.
Adding a little panache take a deep breath and call upon the courage you have burning within because it is ready to ignite change
They're excited and motivated because there's no time to waste
Strike now while the iron is hot and holding back wait for some universal green lights
But you know, it's okay to go ahead with a new idea
And this is that you are in a position to make a change.
The page of Wands asks that at this time,
you allow your creative mind to explore all options
and gravitate towards those that spark passion.
When you hold in your heart,
you can achieve anything you set out to accomplish
to find the confidence to take a risk
that will lead to success, okay?
So creativity, passion, youthfulness, enthusiasm.
It says Bowerbird, kind of like Bronzebird,
but it's a Bowerbird.
The frog is one with the sword, yeah.
Reminds me of uh, we have the frog prince with that muppet sit in the 70s. There's like a frog prince. It's called a frog princess actually
He's like a little sword fight. I think in that movie
Well in the that when the frog wasn't really holding the sword he was more like sitting between these two
Leaves, I think these reeds. I don't know. I mixed it back in the next one. Sorry
Frog is dangerous tamales here. Mm-hmm. So, yeah, the brains already out of time. Oh, I mean jts you
Oh
What's that are you JT?
No, I don't know who I am anymore
Yeah, that's this person you're not this person right here. Oh, is that you who am I? Oh, no, that is a you
Yeah, that's me. I know
Yeah, I know who I am
Yeah, I'm having a you gave me an identity crisis for a second. They're psyche. Oh
Well, it's a
Whatever this is whatever this human body is it's not us
It's not that's not our true self and so it's like that's some true identity crisis
So we think where these human bodies we identify with the flesh the meat suits the flesh suits the dream
They basically just the spirits dream and I was living with it, but yeah, you're talking about like the yeah
The mind body problem, right like oh, yeah identity. I'm not talking about identity
That's there's something I'm talking about, you know, you're actually identity like who you where you really are you really a spirit
You're really not like a body. Maybe you're I mean, we're like in the body
But we're spirit they can the people don't understand that
The body is like pulling the body the body pulls us to the earth. That's why I like, you know
Things that are on the earth, like really attached to the earth, like what touches the earth, like the bottom of your feet, like that's part of us is connected to the earth, like the lowest part, like the hell.
Say, what if we were, hell, heal, right, H-E-L-L, H-E-E-L, what if, hold on, what if we take the past away, we're just gone forever, well we have been, it's like...
How that would be possible because well that would be first of all that'd be blissful because then it's like there's like we're in the non-existence
And so non-existence is like bliss, right? That's like the whole Nirvana
but
There is existence because we keep waking up. It's just like when we go to sleep at night
We fall asleep and we like lose consciousness our body's basically dead for all sense of purposes
You know, we're basically dead when we sleep unconscious, right?
And so but where we go we go to another place we like
We see things we can interact with it. We see people and so there's just dreams and dreams and dreams
I think it just goes, you know forever
That could shit. Oh, do you think cb? What are you saying things like that?
terrible dreams
Dreams well, we are this is a dream. It's like the work. This is just like a much lower. It's like a much more
Dense there's like a more I'm more density to it. It's like, you know, it actually is like a physical plane as much as it can be
It is like a what
Scary we're sharing this dream, right?
Haring the dream right a shared room, right?
It is a shared dream and I say we don't know how many people are actually real people like, you know
there could be like a lot of people that are just like
Either like not clones, but I'm saying
How these are like, you know, it's just not I don't know it's MPC or something like that, but
There's some people that might be on auto on autopilot
MPC yeah, like they're just
What I said, they're like how many is it like there's a certain number of
133,000 or something like that there's some kind of like number of like
This number of no, no, it's 140. It's 144. It's 144,000. Yeah. Yeah
No, you're talking about like the Bible or something
Well, yeah, that's yeah, there's like there's 144,000 something in the Bible
It's like regions of something or like a bit of I don't know or but also I'm thinking like also many people might share the same soul, right?
Have you heard of that at the same time?
Yeah, like I was saying like the soul might split into many different pieces and yeah more than one body has like the same soul
Yes, yes. Yes at the same time
So that's basically like that's how they have like the hive mind because they're actually the same story or they maybe even like
If there's something else like possession that would be like a spirit in different bodies like what was the movie Fallen?
Denzel Washington and then
They like it's the other person as a zazel
It's like the demon a zazel, but he'll jump into the different bodies and like give them all this
They're also seeing the same song and stuff like that, which is like interesting
But it's that you believe in it some people don't believe in that kind of stuff
I have to believe in it to talk about it though. You know I'm saying. Yeah. Yeah, it's interesting to talk about it
I like to talk about it. It's like some people get they get mad. Yeah. Oh
Yeah
Well, I don't know if I get mad about what talking about something even if you don't believe it
It's not a reasoning. Yeah
I don't think there's a lot of personal, but I don't want to start first. Yeah. Yeah
Yeah, it's like, you know, it is kind of personal police are kind of personally, but you know, they should be I mean
It's like like if if you're like telling me I have to believe that I'd be kind of turned off to that
But if you're just talking about it, why should I worry about that?
And I would never like I would never tell you to what to believe and I think I only I never tell anybody is
I think for yourself like think for yourself and it's like, you know
You can like maybe get new ideas from people or me or other people and stuff like that
It's like, you know, they're ideas and it's like, you know, that's what it is about sharing different ideas and you know learning things and so
But yeah
I mean, I like that even though I'll talk about stuff. I don't even believe in if I if I think it's interesting
I don't I don't I don't like people trying to force it on me stuff that I don't believe in but
Yeah
No, these are bits. I got these coupon
These are bagels and there's a coupon I got for it and it says this is bagel side a free bagel cream cheese with purchase of bagel
Cream cheese will score so I get a free bagel, right?
Right here. I can get a free coffee, too. Okay
So I don't know she got a coffee and a bagel with cream cheese
Yeah, I'll get I'll get two bagels because they I'll get a you know get one for free. Oh
It's not actually my I didn't like my McDonald's
So I still have like the fries and I got one one of the cheeseburgers left
I'll put it in the oven you later to you too early for that
Yeah, I don't know I pizza
It's too early for pizza. I like pizza. Never never too early for pizza. It's great any time
He's in the morning pizza in the evenings. He said that's the first time
Pizza's on a bagel you can eat pizza anytime remember that song
Bagel bites my childhood
No, it's more about pizza roll, but I do like the bagel bites once I tried it. I'll say oh these are actually kind of fun good
They really burn my mouth like burning like the skin off my mouth and shit like that. They get too big too hot
No, the bagel bites, you know
The cheese and the pizza would be so hot. You get all hot, you know, but they're very good
Pizza rolls always burn my mouth. I like to make my own like bagel stuff like I was just like, you know
Just regular bagel put some cheese on it and get some pizza sauce. Yeah
Anything like top chat. Yeah
It's funny how much the check it's it gets taken off the main chat
I see all the chat because it just puts all those comments through on my stream yard
But it does hide the chat on on the YouTube like just make sure you're on all chat
You can click on the little wheel at the top of the chat
It shows you everything right
But there's there's it won't show it type sometimes it might be a banned word, you know, there's some banned words
And so it's like you type some time and you can't
There's a come up. It might be a banned word. So just maybe try a different word
It's still a different way. Oh, you know, you can not that you want to but I think you can take off the banned words
Yeah
No, I have it you have to put the words in there yourself. It's not like
Think the managing mods can change those two
Yeah, I've had people change them and erase them all to put my name in there and she like that
But I hopefully I don't I don't hopefully well I have that problem with my mods again, so
Right since you haven't I know yeah, I had not had a problem like really like that at all. So are you talking about bring?
it's not going to bring my mouth
Okay, and uh guys I'm getting an anonymous donor just uh donate for a membership, so I need some to uh
I
Appreciate you. I appreciate you anonymous donor. Okay. Thank you very much on cash out
Uh, yes, they sent me so I would I would uh, yes
Okay, so you're back
Who's who's the troll where? Oh, that's a troll. Yeah, I think I take it in the back for free. Okay. Yeah, I didn't think they were
That was I was like
Hi psyche I've been beneath and I've been to me
It's okay. Yeah, I forgive you
I know I can be douchey, but look I'm always gonna be honest and I'm always gonna be
I'm only gonna tell you I think I gotta say I gotta say it to your face. You know, I'm not gonna do it behind the scenes
You know, I appreciate that. That's what I really would like with is like just people to tell me the truth
You know, it's like that'd be the best thing
I do have a question for you though, so I
What happened to elder where'd he go? I
Got pissed off at elder because he started saying some stuff
I he shouldn't like he's saying and like it's just like something I just didn't like what he said and so I
Kicked him off
No, she's up before that but then I
Because he was like put it Kate's photo and stuff and so I'm trying to like
You know
Everybody's explained to him not to do that and so I don't understand it's like why he keeps doing it and I
Don't know I just so I just I don't want to get parent paranoid. I just don't know sometimes people's attentions
To stream it seemed like he was ready to like really be here on panel for a long time, you know, it sucks
Well, I mean, it's okay. He has a channel. He's monetized. He can do his live and I'm sure he'll get a lot of people over there
Do you want to do that's fine? I
Mean, he's not bad. He's not in the backstage. I can't I didn't see him in the chat
I think he left like a quite a while ago, but you know, I didn't have anything against him
It was just I didn't appreciate what he was saying. And so I
You know, just I kicked him off because I felt like a good person
He was on for he's on for a while
Damn
What's your problem? It's okay. It's a you know, he'll be fine. Nothing has a cool dude. I think he's funny
I think he's entertaining as hell. I have nothing. I'm nothing against him. I like him
He just pissed me off at a certain time. So I get sure okay. I get your brother
Guys now this is the JT guy right this is a God he's best friend
You know, I
These guys have a discord behind the scenes they talk
I'm not gonna tell you who my
Who my offices are who my sources are but um
These guys are up to no good dude. I know at times they they can be like they're genuine
And you know at least for the most part gotty. He's you know, he's pretty funny sometimes
But when they get bored, bro
when they get bored they start doing malicious shit
so just watch out with these people man
yeah
there you go
sweet tea congratulations sweet tea got the membership
that's perfect
they like to switch photos
when you're not around
pee bomb
when they get bored
they do that shit
Yeah, I mean, I've been watching them watching them recently. So
What I say and do it's never
P-bombing, you know, I'm never trying to take your channel down
Yeah, I know I know
Tony's the only one that basically told me more like it's always him. I hear his voice. I don't even
even like tries but
Or I'm able to like
Basically, he just comes on as like beta or somebody like I always have on at the right time
And when someone says oh be the come up and then it's like open this right there
And then it's like sometimes other people you do know I you do know why his name is JT, right?
It's the answer for what?
It stands for just trolling like he likes to fucking troll or like maliciously. Oh, yeah
I am super malicious. Hey, thank you so much Christine. Thank you so much for gifting the membership
Yeah, you have to be careful. He's telling you right now. He's super malicious
You have you ever heard of the saying really evil have to listen to what people say about themselves because it's true
Did you know that I'm like really evil psyche, you know that now he's be sure
Like sometimes when people call them so like shorty and they're like, you know, we're tiny and they're like really like 500 pound or like really big
No, I'm up to a lot of various shit. It's like you need to watch out for me
Just you know, I'm gonna do the opposite. I'll keep an eye on you. How about you know, I like me close
How I just let you out of my sight. I don't like to do food. I don't feel like you know
I know he is I know he's really funny. It's really funny, huh?
Wow, I don't know
I want to be honest with you guys, I don't really remember shit.
Oh, yeah, of course.
This is the guy.
Yeah, that's a real fucking scumbag, huh?
Arthur, you think you're some kind of manipulator?
You kind of suck at it, man.
Such a scumbag, dude.
I can't wait till I take a note of who's the real you, man.
I can't wait.
I can't wait until you fucking expose me.
Christian, I love this.
Hold on.
Who's the real me?
I got this mama bear
I say this is a beautiful bird nine of pentacles. I think there's abundance around you like there's comfort you're they know you just
You look you like to be comfortable
And you know if we do bear it the bear energy also very protective
And it's also that you know the nine of pentacles is all about abundance is this being surrounded by a lot of wonderful things and so
It says the nine of pentacles creates an energy that supports some self-care some relaxation without worrying about all the things on your to-do list
Or the things that could go wrong
When I see this car come up, I know it's time to treat myself
This does not mean going overboard or spending beyond my means
It's permission slip to enjoy a moment of basking and refinement
It's like
Going out and getting the croissant from the authentic French bakery downtown versus defrosting the mass produced ones from the grocery store
Maybe your treat is getting a new haircut with professional opposed to the new kitchen shears and please we all have been there
and so it says
Call the bear's strong energy when you need to feel at ease with the pace and rhythm of life.
Let its presence help you feel comfortable enjoying a break or small insulgence as it will promote rejuvenation.
The bear is also one of the animals that comes to us during the night as it guides us to the dream world as we sleep.
When you accept the bear's help, you will gain confidence during times of darkness or uncertainty.
Rest, renewal, guidance, and inner peace.
So thank you. We don't enjoy emotional abuse in a minute. Oh, that's why even I am talking about I'm
reading these books that are telling you all about
The techniques I'm telling people so they understand like so it doesn't happen to them
Okay, and so also that I have understanding of what is being used on me, too
It's like I could I've been through it before
They're confused and all that kind of shit like what are we?
It's feeling to see you in the speedo again. It's in the dryer right now
If you send a donation, I'll make it in the speedo for you, but I don't feel like doing it right now
Okay, you said you're asking for the chat. Oh my gosh, well, I should put a speedo icon asking how much
Um, you know, it's like it's making makes you have to it's a you propose you propose it
Oh, I can say that set of $15 is okay. I don't see them say that I don't see them say that. Okay, Arthur
Is this all you saying? I
Know they don't have me blocked. You know, I would have to have done but they can't have you can't block me
No, they can't block me because I'm not saying anything in chat. I'll say it's extremely. I was like, okay
I think that you blocked it
You can't have me blocked. Okay. I have you blocked. I'll have you lost
Okay
$15 oh
They just they erased all the messages. They put oh my god. Oh my god. It's too bad. Okay. I heard this
Anyway
Yeah, it's like, oh, yeah, this play with me more like well next week sitting here. Wait, what happened with Arthur?
He's he thinks he thinks he's some kind of manipulator he kind of sucks at it
I mean, it's like please you can smell the
What is that?
The word that you're looking for
No, what's that? Oh, that's like a gasoline pump. Oh, it's gonna be gas. Yeah. Yeah gas lighting. Yeah, it's like, okay
I understand. It's like there's
when everyone's gaslighting you it's like can be like a little bit um
and then you're like high on weed and like
and uh, it can be a little disorienting, right? But uh
I do not see that shit
What?
I say you're not you're not that high to not see that shit
Yeah, but what shit like what tell me what you mean?
Whatever
Right now. Oh, oh, yeah. Well, yeah, Arthur
Like I say Arthur man work on if you think you're a manipulator you need to go back to school dude fucking suck
Not that you should be manipulating people, but if that's what you're trying to do you could at least try to be better
Yeah
Okay, not everyone's gonna have a nice big nice personality and I don't have not my personality is not big nice
And as far as I was trying to make me laugh,
maybe you're doing a good job because I'm not laughing
and he's done me well enough to know, just jokes.
Okay, I know, well, that's fine.
It's like, whatever it's like,
if I have problems trusting people,
so I'm having problems trusting some people.
Like the fake nice people that take me to take me to Brown another to try hard or more annoying in the trolls
Yeah, sometimes, you know, yeah, it happens
Well, what's your default your default is like don't trust anybody, right?
Well, it's like I mean that's kind of how it's like, you know
I would like to be able to in real life. You can trust like maybe the number of people on one hand, right?
You know, it's like that's if you can't if you have that many people you can't trust you're very lucky
But most people don't have that and especially it's hard nowadays with everybody. Just think it's like, you know
Cuckoo for cocoa puffs or whatever. You know what they say, you know what I've heard trust but verify, right?
So you can give people a benefit up a double check what they're saying is right
Well, even if they're right, it's like just because everyone's saying something and something is right or something is wrong, it's like, you know, it's like, it doesn't mean anything.
People will say a lot of things because I don't know.
There's no force. There's nothing that's ever put out as an accusation or anything
It's just like this innuendo and just like bullying, right?
But it's like you're playing I eat to the bullshit to get out here
Otherwise watch the trash people do not trust any the way I know I see what I mean
I see like I'm being bullied and stuff, but I'm kind of used to being bullied. It's just like now. It's like feeling
Spreading yeah, you don't see if you see like what happens on the panels like how people treat me on the panels
I mean, I figured like you I don't know you'd like it or something because you let them do it. So I don't know I know
Well, I'm just like I'm letting people talk. I am interested in like people talk and make meaning people and some of the people were new
And some are interesting, but it's like they were they all just seem like there's like
Just seems like people are coming just like fucking
It doesn't just seem that way
So what but why
Fun I guess
Oh, I don't know because I haven't been
Coming to your channel that long so I really couldn't say I know when Goddy and I came like a bunch of new people came
Obviously, but I don't know who else is who other what other new people you're talking about really?
Well, that was like, I mean, that's what it's when everything's basically started right around that time, right? Yeah. Yeah, I
Don't know how it was before that
But yeah, it wasn't it wasn't I mean it was like
It was similar, but it's like, you know, it's just like it's gotten weirder. I think yeah
It's like yeah, like
There's making some mod problems and stuff like when sake he was truly Michael. Yeah, I love that like in the
Mike I was like saying I have to share your butthole and he's like what you don't know you don't and I think yes
I do and I was like it's what I did
And then like of course I didn't know he says human things for the advice, but it's the weather of the center store
So, I'm sorry, I shouldn't read some comments out loud in your comments. We did the same as 10 yet dumb dumb
You're a sweepiest power tripping on that's the thing
I don't want to cut you up. What do you say?
Crucible's ghost says dumb dumb, you know, yeah, I don't know everybody's been saying dumb dumb now. I don't know
Yeah
saying lots of me so
Pretty much
It's purely I don't know when they got in a car accident. Yeah
It's the human got it got a bunch of new people like Hannah and see he
Brains people and I brought them. I like I do that. I like gaudy and you know, you're cool and these fine and sick
Yeah
Like I like spunky and I like
Yeah, well, it's just like there's just like certain people have good hearts and they're like other like they're like kind people
some people
Okay, sleepy come on up
Or does sweepy come on the chance here or does sweepy come up in
He has been on the panel. I paid. Oh, yeah. Yeah sweepy. Please come
Hello
Arthur
So, okay, I feel a lot better guys. Thank you for this for like guys. I don't mean to like
Signition moan about things. I'm sorry. Thank you for listening to me
So people here are here because it's your stream don't let you make it. Oh, thank you my TMC. Thank you, Mike. You make thank you
Yeah, I mean it's like some people like I think that
They even if they don't know they like me they would like they would like me or they do like me
I think it's like they don't know me or like I don't know. I don't know
I mean, I'm sure a lot of people like I've always been used to people are always talking behind my back and everything
But it's like it just seemed like it was like every everyone's kind of turned on me all at once and like
you know, and then it's like then
Very cryptic, but it's like, you know
It's like I said I've been on the rabbit hole before with this and it's like so
It's like I know
I don't know I don't know what they're trying to say or it's like they think it's that they're operating on sub like by doing subliminals
But the thing is like I understand the subliminal so they're not subliminal and it's like so wait
Who is where we referring to right now?
You know like a like a like a lot of people a lot of people
Do you know you want more reading? Okay more reading cards. Who wants a card? You want a reading beater?
Let's bitching. Okay. Okay. I'm bitching too much
Okay, right. Okay. Yeah, but you know, I'm I'm tough guys. I
See I like have been like has the whole school hate me basically, you know, and I've survived so you want a reading easy. Okay
Let's see. Do you want?
Which text do you want the villains guardians? Who do you I can know I have just have the
Guardians deck right here. You want you want a reading Katie? Okay, gotcha
You said with the guardians. I mean, yeah, they said
Okay, you like you would get a reading we're causing anxiety. Well, it's like you want the Star Wars cars
Yeah, like I said, like it's not a big Star Wars person
But those cars that they had you would appeal to the Star Wars people, right? It's like you're Star Wars crime
Okay, so who am I reading for right now? Easy, easy. Okay, I'll pull one out of this deck.
The Guardians of the Night deck. Okay. Oh, you want the Voodoo deck? Okay, Voodoo deck.
Gotcha. I'll be right back.
Hmm
Okay
Bader once arena. Okay. I got you. I got you guys. I'll do some food cards. Okay easy
Okay, I'm through for easy please
Sorry, I'm gonna get my table more cleaned off and I'm gonna start like chef like on the table for you guys
I think you guys want I'll try to like learn how to shuffle better. She went like I'm not the best stuff a little bit
I do like a different, I like doing this method.
Okay, one, oops, one, two, three, four, five, six,
seven, eight, oh, okay.
Oh, okay.
And there's one fell on the floor sheet,
so I'll take this too.
Okay.
Okay, so just a couple of things.
Okay, so this is, you gotta, you gotta put some baskets,
and baskets are the cups, okay?
So this is gonna do with some emotional stuff.
So something, this is like your, you know,
your cup overflowing, you're like very happy lately, okay?
Or like, you know.
So, but I'm going to read some of the book on these and I'll tell you this one at a time.
Okay, so it's just because we're concentrating.
So we see this basket being kind of filled.
Okay, it says ace of baskets.
Okay.
Ace of baskets.
It says, the plant is wild lettuce, and it says the image, a basket overflowing with water sits atop a lodestone.
Lodestones are used in who do to attract love and prosperity.
And so it says, positive meanings are compassion, emotional renewal, having a sense of peace, falling in love,
a conception, new relationships, happiness, messages in water, abundance, empaths, intuition.
Feeling refreshed spiritual people and healing old wounds. So these are all good things, of course
But yeah, so it's just the beginning of something good that will really benefit you emotionally
And then we also had the six of baskets and the six of baskets six of cups
And so this is also what I consider a nostalgia card
I call it nostalgia and it's just like remembering
It's having happy memories or something like, you know, very pure innocent memories of like, you know
your past and
Bring those memories back up. It says a little boy and a little girl are standing in a sugar cane field
It says sugar cane is the plant in South Carolina
The little boy offers his crush a basket full of rice with bits of sugar cane on top to win her over
There's an old saying in the South if you can't afford to give a gal jewels give her sweets and she'll be sweet on you
It says so it's a rekindling an old flame getting back together a clear
Conscience restored harmony
Indulging and play reflecting on the good old times happy childhood memories people have made their peace with the past
So maybe that's about actually like that new beginning for you that you wanted and also
Making peace with your past right. I like that a lot that maybe you know, whatever it meant to you, but
What I was trying to say you can't see to understand that we see through that's all you need to know. Okay, so I don't know. Yeah, you're talking
Okay, it's okay, you're not obligated to do anything right it's like you don't have to support you at all
You know, but you know not to be like you got it. Okay?
Cool again. I think she's that's a being addressed in the chat. Okay. Okay. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. No, you're good
Okay, so let's see, okay, Bader, money, if you have a problem, I'm sorry, this is what
the channel is, it's a tarot channel, so if you don't like tarot reading, it's probably
not the best channel for you.
So, um, Vader, you won a one? Okay. You like one, Vader? Um, I got one for you. Um, I got some cards for Vader, too.
Vader said, yeah. Or, and he said, hold on, JT wanted some. Or, no, no, no, I'm sorry.
No, no, you gave me one. You gave me one.
Okay, if this, it was K, um, it was, uh, K...
I'm sorry, someone asked.
I got the frog, the sword frog?
Yeah, you can do that. Yeah.
If it's somebody asked for one, let me just say the real name.
It was Kate, Kate, was it KT?
Kate?
Yeah, KT, KT.
I'm sorry, I took a while, but that's what it was like
a little bit ago.
Let me see if KT's still here.
Oh yeah, she's here.
Okay, KT, I got your reading.
I'll do it from this who-do deck, okay?
Do you want to give me a number?
I'll shuffle it that in the amount of times,
but I'll just start shuffling now.
But tell me a number,
and I'll start doing the other kind of shuffle.
okay there you go let's see okay okay yeah you pick a number okay three okay three
Ace of Coins. Okay, so this is gonna be like a new beginning financially. This is like or some kind of this is seed for a bigger
Business or some kind of idea you're putting into the world. I don't know if you started something new
But yeah, that's it. This would be a good and I
Mean do two cards read but I'll read this first with ace of coins
Yeah, so it's a seed basically, you know, it's a pinnacle the coins are pinnacles so it says pomegranate says the woman holds up a slice of
sweet potato pie
on a serving knife to offer her guests.
The pie was baked with a lucky Indian head penny,
a tiny piece of ragged cloth, a matchstick, a pea,
and a ring inside.
Inspired in the traditional Irish barn-book bread,
the coin symbolizes wealth, the cloth symbolizes poverty,
the pea symbolizes not getting married,
the matchstick symbolizes domestic discord,
the ring symbolizes getting married.
The guest shown here is not only receiving the slice
with a lucky penny,
but also has received a message in the tea leaves for telling good fortune ahead.
It says meaning. It says receiving money or gifts, new financial career opportunities,
productivity, fertility, job offers, abundance,
achieving tangible results, blessings, windfalls, good omens. It's all good things, okay? That's all
I say and best it is something right we can do parent here on peace
Yes, we're doing parent peace and have another cart for you. I can't see if we like these
And so it comes up and pop up shit time this pile
But pop it up. Okay. Oh seven of baskets. Okay, so this is the seven of cups
Seven of Cups is having a lot of options in front of you. This is the bathtub
So you have a lot of options in front of you a lot of and they might be confusing because there's
So they can look all look good, but some of them are better than others
So make sure you just pick the right way you your intuition tells you there's the best way to go with that
The thing that I think you want the most go up to them one at a time to you seven of baskets says
It's by Hisop and Eluthoro, or the woman with her head in a thick cloud, has decided it's
time to get out.
She decides to take a spiritual bath using Hisop to bring a state of clarity, calm and
equilibrium.
And so I would say, yeah, maybe a good spiritual bath, and it's, you know, it's like, but you
can have a vision quest and vivid imagination and realities, but it's also going to be confusion
You know confusion maybe a little bit of illusion and stuff like that
It's sometimes called the acid trip card when thumb for psyche went for your butthole. Let's go. Oh my gosh
so I hope you like those those cards and
Who's next?
Thank you guys
Thank you guys you guys are awesome really appreciate you and that you were is how many people are 43 awesome
Being a crack I like ghosts, okay. Well, I have to have a wonderful day and thank you again because it was easy
But if you did
You did purchase, you know these cards for me. I really appreciate that. So thank you easy
So I get I don't know all my phone man. I kept getting kicked off
We were talking and then like my internet kicked me out. I don't think it was you I got kicked out. I
Try joining
This new VPN
I don't know if that's what's going on. That's what's ruining it for me
Yeah, how you doing there, brother?
How you doing there, brother? Not too bad. Not too bad
I'm good today. Hi. We're having some fun doing readings and
You ever heard of the Snickers commercial have a Snickers you're not you when you're hungry
Nick is really satisfied. I know I don't know. I don't know you're not you when you're hungry. I know that one
I'm actually eating something right now, and I feel so much better, you know, sorry
Okay, oh, yeah, that's good. I hope you feel better. I might get a I might get a
coffee and a couple bagels today
I got a good old Italian sub, you know what I mean?
Did you want a reading or a third now?
I think Saman wanted one the other day. He's not here right now, but I know he wanted one.
You should give it to him. I think he'll take the reading.
Saman wanted one.
Don't be modest. You want a reading too.
It's okay. It's okay. I'm not gonna force anybody.
Anybody else want one?
For you guys, you know, I don't expect it. I just would like to
Help you give a message, you know what I want but I would it's just it's just against my religion, you know, okay?
Okay, I know I understand what religion is
Your mother's religion keep fucking talking. It's what I thought
Wow, I'm sorry. Who are you supposed to be again to me?
That's why he's not a mod. That's why you're not a mod or sir because he's hot like that. I'm your fucking mod
You hear me? I'm the mod here. I'm the moderator
I'm not you. You're not me. Nope. Yeah, here
Now you're in a better mood, huh? Is he on me? I don't know. I think his microphone passed away
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
You heard that fuck fuck fuck me like this
Whoa, whoa, he just switched his photo dude. See it. I didn't I was watching it. It was so quick
Yeah, I gotta set you up for that one. Yeah, he didn't do it. He didn't do it. I know
I was thinking about it though. I was thinking about it. Don't do it. Don't do it
Yeah, I got it. Come back. This guy's a real scumbag from a real piece of shit
Rehearsing up saying a Friday night stream. Yeah, I hope so. Yeah, it's in policy today and then
You know
For the midnight stream. It's got him JT. Let me tell you about him. He changed my life. I really obsessed with the guy
I'm yeah, I'm JT. Yeah, we get me right. Are you talking like it? You see the are you part your part cat now?
He changed my life. I'm obsessed for the guy. I know what you're talking about CB. Yeah
of the
of
I don't have any thoughts about that.
Okay.
Do you stand with the LGBTQ?
Stand with
Why's juice how like why is all these all these trans jokes are being made and like why'd they say JT's one trans like what?
What is that why was that funny tell me why that's funny though. I don't know what that even means
What is that you're laughing? Why is it laughing about it? You don't sound funny one trans come on down. He said it three times
I don't I mean that's juice. I didn't I didn't fucking say it
It doesn't seem that funny to me.
Hold on.
Wait, what is your opinion about the trans people, Psyche?
I have no problem with trans people, but it's like, you know, I don't agree with like
Probably agree with like, you know, they having surgeries and stuff like that. I mean, it's like it's a bit much, right?
Like mutilating your body and stuff. It's I think I don't think they know what they're
Necessarily getting into and it's like they think it's something else and it's like I don't think you could become a minute off of the sex
I think you can emulate them and you can like, you know, do like it
Some people can get closer than others, but there's some
I don't know. I just think I don't think they're like a like a gender kind of like a gender dysmorphia kind of thing
almost
I mean look yeah
People are very impressionable and so people can be suggested things and then all of a sudden they think things about themselves
That's why it's like you it's very dangerous to you. So I actually agree with you about that. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah
It's like they're suggestible. So it's like
yeah
It's like you've said many things in your life and I got to say this was
that was very smart of you which you just said
Well, yeah, I'm not I'm not like no, sometimes I have a
That's both to me like the other shit that he says
Sometimes I like you know, sometimes I don't I don't like you know
He's from the heart he doesn't speak from the brain
What do you think about the LGTB community arts there?
I think that they should do whatever the fuck they want to do, but once they start messing with the kids and once they start allowing kids to fucking, uh, I guess, general, what is it, identify themselves as a gender, or sometimes they're even considered fucking bipolar or binary.
Especially straight parents are doing it.
Yeah.
like this is I agree I agree I agree I agree I agree with you but I'm saying it's it's their parents
that are like and they're usually straight parents that are like I don't know if they're super woke
or whatever but they're trying to like or like trying to be trendy I think that jazz Jennings
parents are trying to be trendy with her gender stuff it's like they're trying to just be on
tv and stuff like it was really obvious but um yeah so you know sometimes the kids are the victim
of the parents desires like that like and that's so I don't agree with like transitioning at a young age
So pretty much adults should do what they want to do but leave kids out of it
I think everybody
Kids have parents and so parents how much the parents have the medical stuff like right through kids
But no, it's not to have kids involved in any of that stuff. I know but it's their kids their own kids
It's like so it's like really difficult to like tell people didn't know though. I mean fuck. I I know it's kids
the
Hey, exactly. I mean, that's what I'm saying there. It's like a different category. No, but they want to lump it together though
As if that represents everybody
They always try they always try to lump things together, but it's like we're all
Black lives matter with the whole
Trance matter. They were doing some weird stuff with that. That was a big. Yeah, we were stealing all of it. They were stealing from people
Yeah
No, I agree
He's like, oh, I love his opinions.
Who's Arthur?
Who's opinion you want?
No, not Arthur.
Oh, she likes your opinion.
No, Arthur.
His VPN is killing me, bro.
It's telling me I'm in Ontario and it's fucking everything up.
Yeah, because it was VPNs are not as great real quick. Um, yeah, so I think what you're saying and even do tea
I think I agree with a lot of things you guys saying
It's like you as a gay
What are your thoughts on Gaze for Gaza Gaze for Palestine?
Okay, I don't want to I don't I don't want to talk about like like that
You kind of worse stuff or you can't talk about political shit. Yeah, I don't talk about political shit. No
It's like but I'll say
Like that
What about Gaze for like, you know, TRMP, you know, I don't like to say that that name really okay, but it's like yeah
So what is being gay got to do with any of this other shit like?
Why you know what I'm saying like
Like a political movement and kind of such way it's not it's not it's like you individual they need to kind of like
Gay doesn't have shit to do with anything else except being gay and even that is not your entire identity
No, and I know that's what I say and it's not saying it's like people are sexualizing the gay so much like it's like
It's like just he's like coming out having sex all like all over the street
And I did all this crap like every whatever you like whatever you do. It's like part of your identity now
Right, but now it's like it's not only sexuality. It's also if you are saying, oh, I'm a unicorn. I'm a fucking, you know
I'm a butterfly. They'll say this people identify as different animals and stuff like that. It's like a lot of it's free
Like it's silly, but uh
I'm a psyche awakens look at me. Yeah
Look at me. I'm a psyche awakens. Look at me
Make it fun I'm right now
I don't know what the joke is, look at me, I'm safety weakens, what?
Hello?
What is it?
What's the thing?
Is there something funny about it?
Explain it?
No, explain it though.
You can explain why it's funny.
No, it's not my name.
It's like you're saying that that's what you sound like and then you identify it.
You identify it.
That's what you're like, you're saying that I sound like that?
No
Yeah, he's like he's like I'm psyche look at me fucking psych
Yeah, me know what there's only one and only be one
I can be some kind of cloning program or something. I'm not aware of it. Okay. I'm sorry. No, no
No, but it's like even you. Oh, I don't know. My bad. You're reading something
It's so funny, but where are you laughing though?
Don't you hate when motherfuckers just start laughing like like like you want explain it like you want explain
You know what it is. There's nothing to even explain that that's he's laughing at your confusion. Like yes, yes
But you know, he was before he even asked
Started laughing I asked the question and he's still laughing
But that's all that's so funny
Is this the way I go fuck yourself
Really go fuck yourself
Not confused. I don't think I wish I was confused, but I know exactly what he's doing
I know exactly what he's doing. No laughing at some kind of inside joke. Yeah. Yeah, that's the feeling, right?
It's like, yeah, thank you. We were all sticky, right? It's like, who knows it's like
There's like I don't know. They might have clones. I don't fucking know
What's the fuck is going on is like who knows it's like I don't know I hear a million things about people
I say even I don't care I people tell me police reports. I don't fucking care
I'm like whatever are they in prison right now that obviously they're not that big of a threat to society because they'd be on like
You know whatever that new Alcatraz is or whatever. So it's like
But whatever it's like
If I'm so dangerous send me there. I don't know. What do you think? I'm some kind of dangerous person. I've never heard of fly
I mean, what's the hell?
Okay, well, what am I
You're psyche
Okay, what is it? What is anybody are we are what is what are what are you saying? What's the problem? It's like
Tell me
What's so funny? Are you asking me? Yeah, you can explain
What can you say? Let's see. I don't know what you want me to tell you
I don't know. I don't want you to tell me the truth. That's all I want you to tell me. Let's hear like in general
I can like yeah, go ahead. Give me your your assessment. Give me your assessment. I don't know
Arthur's backstage. I see him. He was he was on camera backstage. I see him like in regards to what now?
You got to be specific cuz I could just start telling
Just tell me what like whoa
Like a general like it just a general. I don't know you
You seem nice enough you see like a nice guy. I think you get I think you got kind of
Um and don't take it the wrong cuz you're asking me to be honest
You have kind of like a
You're a nice guy, and I think people almost kind of take advantage of it sometimes you're kind of got like a
You don't want to you don't want to upset people you're I'm not gonna say people pleaser, but damn near close to it
so
And I think people are like pick it up on that or something and they're like, ah, he doesn't want upset
You know he doesn't want to upset people whatever and sometimes you're like caught between
I mean I do yeah, I do upset people, but it's like I bet it's like I tried to like
I don't think you're trying to upset people, because I don't think you are, but you're like almost overly concerned if you do, like, I don't know what you want, like, is it that you're wanting people's approval, I don't know, I don't know, I can't say, I really want, I want the audience to be happy, but it's like, and I want like to be like, you know,
I think you're doing okay. I think you're doing all right. Maybe you're a little hard. I think I'm doing it. I'm doing okay
Maybe I am but it's like
But I think you know what is I think you're you're internalizing a lot of these criticisms. You're you're almost I
Think you're I don't know internalizing some of it. Maybe I'm wrong, but you asked me what my opinion was maybe
It comes from internal. I mean, it's like it isn't I'm a very I'm a very internal person
I'm an introverted person. See what's funny is like, I'm not even like that's why I like sometimes I just like disappear
It's because I'm not extrovert and it's like it's so stuff like
confrontation actually like we should really uncomfortable and like or just like but then like it's bad vibes or just like being like
teasing or homophobia or like
Just like well, I think this kind of stuff is that it's like giving you more versatility in a way
I was just putting my now Arthur has my profile photo up
Yeah, I don't know I'm gonna leave it off
I don't know what he's saying. Okay, he turned it off
Come on dude, I was just randomly laughing, you know, I was like an idiot. There was no joke against you
I just
I think he just wanted to make it. I know but I really know it's not I just want to like
I like when I ask questions that it's like at least like you know
You know what?
I think he's trying to give the impression that there's an inside joke when there's actually not to try to like
No, there was no joke when he asked
It was like it was so like the way he asked to me. I just found it funny, you know, I don't know
Okay
I don't know which is good, but sometimes I feel like your radar is up too high where it's like you're almost paranoid
No, but because it's that was like that's what happens when people try to make you paranoid
They would people say oh when you start putting up like little like, you know, if it's about animal porn like when I'm trying
To have a show if people send me the next day people the next day say oh here like you see he put up like this
Why would you put that up in the first place? Why would that even be a thing?
It wasn't long enough for anyone to see.
It was not a war.
It was a woman having sex with a dog.
She wasn't having sex with it. That was Tiffany.
Okay, the dog was riding on her back.
Listen, I'll admit, out of context, yeah, and Tiffany knows this.
Like, yeah, even I say, I'm like, you're a little too comfortable with your dog.
Little too fucking much. Okay. Okay. Yeah, let's not get into the peanut butter allegations
You're going further than that you're saying she's having sex with it. It looked no, no, no, no
I don't say that. I said
There's a dog. She's giving a dog a piggyback, right? Okay. That's what I'll let's all
That's all I'll say, but it's not appropriate to do that. It's a nude
Yeah, I think it it was
Yeah, it was just I'm sure it was no
She wasn't naked right so obviously the dog can't fucking do anything. I don't know no
It was just it was like hey the pictures this big first of all
He was like it's epic and second of all you could just be like all you can see was like the back and like the dog
I mean you could not see even see it was just weird. Why would you put that picture up?
And why would you even have a picture like that in your in your hard drive?
I mean, I yeah, you know, it's like why is the better question is why is she playing with her dog like that?
You know, look at me. I'm playing with my dog dog. You don't have a dog, right? Yeah. No, yes
Look, I've had dogs. Yeah, right never play wise. Yeah, why are you posting a picture of Tiffany?
Do you just do that? What was that?
Yeah
Oh, yeah, oh, yeah, that was a different the dog. Yeah, I'm playing with her dog, right? Why'd you put that?
Why'd you say that? Why'd you put Tiffany's picture up on my street?
You tell me what her with the one where she's playing with the dog. Yeah
Oh, I put it up so that people would tell you like that. He's doing something fucked up even though I really wasn't wait
Let me see
No, well, if I show you now all he's gonna he's gonna that's weird
But that's weird. I mean that's like a little bit like obscure like why would you just say? Oh, I'm just gonna they try to make
Psyche you gotta look at it and see how ridiculous this some of this stuff is pretty fucking ridiculous. Wait. Why did you take?
I don't need to know I did not you say you don't need to teach me a lesson. Okay, you're not teaching you anything Psyche
It's like you're like
No, what's the point? What's the point then? It's like it can't be a normal teaching you anything. No
It's like the people hear the nag to you and like
Okay, let them let them nag it. It's fine. They can nag it. I don't give them a little something to nag about
Not even that serious
I just want to make this I just want to make this show a success. I want to be
Okay, I think
It's not getting numbers all the time big deal. It'll you know
No, I'm not the numbers because I have like I'm already I'm like I have the numbers and stuff like that
I like my numbers are fine. It's you're doing okay
What makes you think?
Because I'm just because it's been not as much fun for me
And it's like I've been having these super long panels and people are just ungrateful and you know, I'll bet on the panels
It's a very thankless thing, but yeah, but it's like the way it is now, but I'm like, but there's not like that always
I don't have to do this. I'm doing it. I'm doing things because for my enjoyment and mostly right. So it's like I'm gonna do it
Are you enjoying it sometimes like you're not well, it's because nobody would you enjoy if people are just picking on you all day
like every day and like, you know, it's like, you know, you're paired to an animal and and
You know, it's whole
Yeah, it's just there's just horrible things just things are said and it's like oh, they said to other people or whatever
it's like I do I do hate I mean let me ask you this I'll be I'll be offended for other people
I'll be offended for other people if it's about other people are these people that you like or respect or
Some of them are you know, some of them are friendly friends, you know, it's like I'm not I'm not trying to explain myself
I'm just no, no, I'm not asking you. You know, you're we're just talking but I know I'm gonna say
Hey, man, you're you keep asking me amazing. We don't need to go over it
I mean, it's like I all I want to do is like chill and just have fun. I think I'm not trying to like be
But you're talking to me about it for some reason so I know but you but you're asking and it's like you also like early kind of like
not prodding but it's like if you want to talk to me about it then how can I not ask questions about what you're saying
You know what I mean? Like you don't want me to ask anything. I won't I know I went I want you to ask that is like
Kind of like they're kind of like subtle
Kind of like I'm not trying to be invasive. I'm asking you like point your questions
Yeah, it's it's a it's a what I'm saying psychies
It there's a difference between like brand and people telling you shit and people that you like or people that you know
Or people that you you know, okay, there's a difference when your friends telling you something
and just ready to do it
It's just people kind of like some people's personality change like almost I know I'm not going to explain
No, no, no
And it's like I just answered but it's like we can stop it stop asking me about it like
I know I will answer but it's like like what are you trying to like ask like is there
Keep it saying. Oh
You you seem to be you seem to think everybody has like an ulterior motive and you're probably right about that in most cases
but to the point where you can't seem to distinguish what somebody's asking you a genuine question
And you asked me for your
That's the point. That's what I'm saying is like that's why because when there's so much is thrown at you
It's of course they think when you like all day every day, right? I know I agree
What to do about that? I don't know maybe have you
a break or something. I don't know dude. It's because I feel like you're asking me stuff. And then when I tell you
I'm not trying to ask you you're asking me stuff or you were telling you also to oh, don't you're telling me like
I'm doing stuff wrong just say hey, you know, I'd like it, but you're you're keep you keep like
You I'm not criticizing you. Okay. Okay. Okay
No, I think you're doing okay, man, I think I think you're you're criticizing yourself
I don't know. Well, I am tough around myself than probably anybody else can be so that's why it's like I really don't
I'm worried about other people. I'm harder on myself. Okay. Well, I feel like yeah when other people tell you stuff like
Didn't you get people can say anything people get this point is people say so many things
I mean if I believe everything people told me I've been told it's such a billion different scenarios with billion different things
I'd be fucking chasing around my fucking tail for like ever so it's like I just know it's all gonna be some bullshit unless I see
I'm not gonna worry about what like what could be whatever. It's like, you know, this is life
It's like I feel like I protect it. I feel like I'm fine. It's like I'm you know, it's like I'm wrong then and whatever but
it's not like it's not like it's not like it's not like it's not like it's not like it's not like it's not like it's not like it's not like it's not like it's not like it's not like it's not like it's not like it's not like it's not like it's not like it's not like it's not like it's not like it's not like it's not like it's not like it's not like it's not like it's not like it's not like it's not like it's not like it's not like it's not like it's not like it's not like it's not like it's not like it's not like it's not like it's not like it's not like it's not like it's not like it's not like it's not like it's not like it's not like it's not like it's not like it's not like it's not like it's not like it's not like it's not like it's not like it's not like it's not
Wait, what am I doing? I don't know. It's a you're like
You know
I'll just leave I do that. I do like you but I'm asking you
I don't know. You don't have to ask a straight question. You can ask me a big beat
I appreciate it if you asked me straightforward
But I asked you asked me a straightforward question because and I do when you get upset about it
Okay, ask me a question
We always have like a little put down in the questions like there's something wrong with me what I'm doing
I don't know like why do you get so offended when I ask you things? What do you think about?
Okay, well, see you're right. He keeps doing this. You keep doing this. You keep saying other stuff
Okay, when you say you feel like I'm putting you down. What do you mean?
I don't know. It's like kind of like word salad or just like kind of like
You know, I don't think you like me very much
Actually, dude comment you said like you said like the bearded like the ugly wolf beard is like making fun of me and stuff like that
Like what is that about? I had this way before I even knew who you were
Why would you say that to me and then people are calling me man. Who said that?
So is it about wait question for you serious question about what I'm saying is about what people say about me to you
No one talks about you really I mean say I'll be able to say good things about you basically every people like everyone
Like seems like everybody else is that for me? Everyone likes everybody. It's a problem. It's like well some people don't go
You don't like me. It's okay. It's okay. I like it. I know I know I love I don't just like it
I love people and I love people. I'm not talking about people. I said me
Okay, you I love everybody people. You know trust me. It's right
I don't know you I don't know who you are your guy know what you don't I mean I seem like
What have I
You seem particularly distrustful of me. I'm not saying you should trust anybody
But I'm just saying what you came in and you came in at the same time as Dottie and like you kind of like have been kind of
I mean that's like the nicest always all the time, you know
Well, it's psyche everybody's not gonna be nice all the time, but at least you want people to be honest with you, right?
Yeah, but I really don't want that
Okay, would you say Christine I should go? Oh, that's it, huh? I think I've been pretty nice
You can take him off
Shit if you're gonna ask them if you're gonna ask them. I'll just leave. It's no big deal. Oh, yeah
No, it's okay. It's okay. I
Don't know
We're trying to confuse me
I'm not and what am I doing?
Find the twilight zone right now. What am I doing? I don't know. I feel like so. Are you I dude? I think you're
Worry, yeah, where are you dancing? We're dancing around. I feel like oh look it. You just want to be afraid. Okay?
Okay, good, but it's like there's just a weird look you said yourself. You just wanted to show right? That's all I'm doing
You do
I miss a big person. I know we all have opinions and it's okay.
Everyone has opinions. I want people to have opinions. I want people to at least like you know
there's just there's just ways that people act that is very
It's very it's very I don't know hive mind. I almost say hive mind is hive mind is like not a bad thing
It's like hive mind is okay
unless there's like a
Evil because the hive is controlled by the queen, right? So it's like as long as there's a good queen
It's usually like, you know a friendly hive, but there's a
Evil Queen hi, I don't just I there's a I think Flurry diamond has a beehive. I mean, there's a drag queen. Hi
They're incredible. No, I
Usually okay, so I don't know. Yeah, okay, whatever. I'm just kidding. I'll be honest with you man. I don't know what you're saying
I don't know either. I don't know. I don't know. I smoke so much weed. I think you're how I shit me now like
Yeah, he's squeezing you I know he's just asking me these questions and then but then he literally told me to ask you
I know but then you weren't asking but you're asking me like a weird question. You weren't being to is like or you weren't
It's still the base of
We're answering questions with questions kind of like that feeling like
I'll be asking you a question and then all of a sudden I feel like you're asking me a question
And that's like and I asked you the question you didn't answer you just didn't ask me something
That's what I feel like
Ask me a question
How are you today? How are you today? I'm doing pretty pretty good. Have you hung out with the brain lately? Yes
We just talking to you on the phone or DC's are there in person a lot. No, no, we live
Are you live together? Okay?
Okay, well congratulations
Happy your does engaged or
Boyfriend girlfriend
Okay, okay
Well, I wish you the best. I love I do support, you know
Straight couples and which straight couples the best, you know appreciate that. Thank you
Welcome
This is for two hours looping on some calm. I know I'm kind of like I feel like I'm like my mind
We're gonna get a figure eight or something like that. I'm like, whoa, it's like
Jesus Christ, you know what goddamn dude if I was actually a piece of shit like God forbid
I'm up here being okay, but it's like sometimes
There's like
When Ziggy came to me, he was being too nice. I'm like a Satanist
Satanist
But I'm not I just want to realize that it feels because both both are not the real thing
I don't know like nobody's like too nice. Maybe I'm too nice
I know that Ziggy came up like when I first met him. He's like, you know what?
He's like, you know what Goddy and rain and who's who has never been like really nice me at that point
He's like he told me good things about you. It's so I like you
It was just like so like first of all, I don't say good things about anybody. I don't
You know, who's a really great fucking guy psyche. I don't do that shit. Why the fuck
Let's say, huh
So who says my face? Oh, let's see. Let me see
I'm asking people to drop my name. No or yours. Jesus
Hey, so yeah
So, yeah, I don't like I did talk to a psychiatrist at one point in my life and I was in high school and
I did not enjoy talking to me. I enjoyed I
appreciate some people have some people but
Yeah, we didn't like it
now
But I say it because it feels like this kind of cat
It was worse, but no, I feel it but it's worse. Okay. I'm just kidding. I'm just kidding. I don't enjoy chatting with you
Kind of
Yeah, if we a you can tune over hold I need to put the okay
Yeah, the Q&A is over because let's let's not talking about that. Maybe so I need to go
I don't I just want to show you some things
What does it say it's a Q&A
Yeah, you asked me Jesus. I have the key. No, no, no, no, I know I'm showing you the Q&A right here
This is this Q&A right here. I have an icon for it now
So the next time we do that conversation
Where is it?
Vita the reality is a lot of these motherfuckers need a shrink really
Wow, wow, okay. Okay. So there you go these motherfuckers. So who?
Who reference you when I'm saying let's say these motherfuckers I mean in general a lot of these people that are chronically online
They do need a shrink
Okay
Would you disagree with that? I'm asking your opinion now
Yeah, I agree because what does online mean? It's like, yes, you're like what you're logged in
We usually we usually logged into something at some point of the day the DSL on a percent of times like radios on the TV
We're usually have something going on or we're asleep, right?
And so it's called like entertaining ourselves while we're like on this earth dude
Let's be honest man. A lot of people got a lot of fucking things going on. It's not it's nothing against anybody. Jesus
I'm speaking in general right now
Okay, but you're like, oh, yeah, so we were going to be throwing the insane asylums or something like what he's saying. No Jesus. God damn
Well, I'm saying that that I'm not saying motherfuckers are on here like schizophrinic and shit having delusions
The problem is the problem is that there's people that are happy to look delusions
And then people are fucking with them and it's like there's people that are like not mentally all there
And it's like probably not the best people to be working with that way
It's like, you know, you don't have some compassion for people with mental illness and it's like
That's why I think all these like supposedly all these
Shootings and stuff happen because people are like this can't take it anymore
They get fully to a point where they like go insane and they just like lash out of society and then everybody right?
And so a lot of them were crazy before they logged on and then like this kind of stuff
Gives them like it makes it worse. I don't know like
There's drug abuse schizophrenia. There's also like, you know, there's there's also
Mindfuckery there's like mindfucking if you guys are not familiar with like mindfuckery manipulation all these things that everyone's doing today
The number one book in prison is like 48 lots of power
Art of seduction say, you know, it's like you guys know about things. This is like all it's all about
Manipulating I think I've I've read those books, but I say I do not agree with the methodology. I just read the kind of stuff to
Show me like it's fucked up. You know how how people are different people do you know it's like it is
I don't know
There's ways there's ways to mark like marketing it does not require you to like it's like oh, it gets it ways too
Too much in criminality. It's like you can do things. Those books are evil. Yeah, it gets way into like
Just like looking at people as you know, it's very mocky a billion looking at people as like, you know
animals or just pieces or appliances, I mean
it's like
or
I don't know
What am I seducing if I was seducing you you motherfuckers wouldn't hate me like what are you talking about?
It's just a bit techniques techniques to like seduce people like I teach these guys that's work with other guys
And then you know in certain things
Crazy my god
It's like it. What do you want me to be an asshole if I'm an ass
I don't want you to be just be just be yourself. Just be yourself. So don't be fake. I'm so sick. I don't like care
God damn what so so either
No, no, no, no, no, no, this just like just be real. It's like you don't just be this be yourself
It's like you don't think I'm being real with you
No, you're very you're very polished like we didn't talk to me. You're very like, you know, you're very like
Oh, yeah, you have the same song you think your voice and like this is what I'm talking where it's like. I
Don't know. It's like you're a little bit. It seems like you're like a little bit
But it's like because you're like not that nice like that is yours to me like it's like that's
So what do you want me to be a hassle to you? No, I don't I don't need you real
You know, I don't know it's a cargo explains. It's be real. It's like it's
Being you don't think I'm being real with you
No
Why not?
Just the way it's kind of this way you sound and it's like it feels like you're like not
Being honest to my boy. Is it what I'm saying is it? Yeah
Yes, it's everything. It's just I got the feeling I get when I talk to you. So if there's something a little off about this guy
I'll like her to the microscope and I'm like
What what like what like what's it? It's an interest in me. You don't like me. You're not interested in like my
Why do you say that? Why do you say I don't like you?
Because you think you never worry. I don't know you're here with all these people like they're all friends with them and like
Everyone just ignores me. I can disappear from chat for a few hours. No one would say anything. It's like so what it's a
What do you guys use here for airtime like what is the what is the?
What is it? It's taken a while to talk to you on the troll. Okay, but like why like what is the attraction like you?
Don't like me. Why are you saying that? I don't like you. I don't know it means like today. Just it just feels
I'm just suspicious of certain people like okay, so like this one time
I thought what other guy was really cute here around the college that was really cute and he was really nice
But he was like this Christian guy
And then he was like so funny to me. He's like, hey, do you want to like hang out or whatever? And I was like, okay
I know I know but I go in the room. He tried to read the Bible to me as like
I was like, it was like it was just trying to convert me to Christianity and maybe he thought like, oh, okay, okay, that'll be extra
extra points
So shit, dude, what are you talking about? No, but I'm just saying that it's like I just think I don't trust people
Sometimes when people are like nice, I like I'm like what I just like my I just don't I
Just I still know I just don't know. I don't know. I'm just flat badly out of my ass
I'm sorry. And yeah, the part of the character is weird. It's like, but if it is true that you know, we do have a
Social mask people wear they're called the persona
And it's like, it's not, it's like, it's like, basically, it's still, it's a bit of like, it's like a self, to keep yourself, you know, it's kind of like a safety kind of thing, it's like a self-protective thing, so I don't know.
You're playing a character, you're playing a character, basically.
Well, let's say yes, yes, so it's like, yeah, so we never show everything, right?
Well, no, nobody's gonna show.
No.
Yeah, yeah, we don't we don't show that's the world, but it's like yeah
But then it's if we are wearing a genuine mask like a real mask
That is like really like changing our personality and being fake, right?
So that mask will drop like all the time because it's like it's too hard to keep up all the time
So yeah, it's like too hard to keep up the life
I don't do it. Yeah, cuz that would be that would be a pain in the ass
Cuz then what you can't ever change your personality cuz then everyone's gonna be like, oh shit. He just changed
No, I'm pretty fucking consistent. I mean, yeah, but then again, people's personalities can change
drastically based on certain things, especially around different people around you're a different
person to everybody you're in contact with. It's a different relationship. And so they're in a
different relationship. So there's like a million relationships with two people.
It's like this, man. It's not being like you at work versus you with your parents versus you
with your friends versus you here. You're going to be a little bit different depending on the
it's not like you're being a different but human but we're not just like the simple people it's
like people are very very popular a lot we're pretty we're really the human brain is the most
complicated organism on the planet earth okay so there's like a lot going on in this brain okay
There's a lot of manipulation that's playing people playing with subconscious the subconscious mind and they playing around with people's minds and
Like if you believe in that
Magic, but that's me. That's yeah, but that's it is manipulation. That's what a lot of witchcraft is like this manipulation
I agree. It's true. Yeah, okay. Yeah, I mean that's what it is
I mean, that's what the witchcraft is witches has been like spelling and spells and like, you know cursive and curses and
You know, you know, you make incantations and everything and grimoires and all this kind of stuff
So a lot of stuff has to do with books and all that kind of stuff
But I want to put a sheep was like icon if I wanted to be if I wanted to be fake, right?
What I would be like a sheep the wolf wolf
I think right. We added that warrior. No, I'm a sheep. Well, you are a wolf your dress is a wolf
You are dressed as a wolf. Yeah, but if I was trying to get an oculus, right wouldn't I?
Are you wearing as wool a wool sweater under that under that mask?
Maybe you're wearing you're wearing
How did you worry? He's wearing that she's clothing guys that a wool sweater in the sheets clothing. You know that yes
She's clothing. It's made of sheep. You're a local to them. Okay. Well, whatever they can go fucking milk my fucking tits, okay?
You know you see these inflammatory comments in there. It's not me saying that shit
Well, it's inflammatory to say that that you think I'm just like a joke. That's a plan
You don't think so. She should hurt my feelings more than hurts your feelings
But it hurts that you think something it's like I'm the one that's insulted in this situation
You're just one supposed to be thinking it right why it's an inflammatory comment. Yes, it's to get a reaction
Yes from you not me shit. No
But I don't know you're talking in circles again
Okay, I feel like you're too. I don't understand me man. I'm not you. I'm keeping up with you
That's the problem. I'm like I'm like ahead of you a little bit. Like I'm like
I'm like trying to get you to catch up. Okay, please was behind the couch. Look here
Hi
Hey, Tricks. Oh
What are you looking your balls?
Tricks
My camera
Five
I know it isn't well, it's like because I but I the thing is it's like sweetie
It's not not being fooled and it's like also
Like I said, it's like I've been it's not my first rodeo, but second of all. Yeah
The guess that he is but it's an occult leader. Yeah, I would not be a cult
Everybody's a guy
He's a piece of cult. He's like a cult member. He's not it doesn't have the I don't see like the cult leader qualities in him
Dude, I'm not any of that. I don't I'm not in cults. I'll do that. I know I know
Okay, not in cults. Okay
No, you're gonna work. We everybody's gonna call it the culture is a cult so like the Americans just being American
That's a cult. We're also in our state is a cult or city whatever you identify our
Family's a cult. It's like we have different cultures and however, whatever the dynamic is with the certain groups, right? They're all
Okay, I
Say this channel is a cult
it say
Right, but it's like so when you join organizations, or you're going to a hive mind you take on one the one mind
And so basically that's the mind control right there. It's like it's all thinking the same
Doesn't it doesn't it yeah, but is it doesn't it depend on whether you're actually agreeing with the people or not like?
Well, that's what I'm saying. It's like, I don't know. It's like everyone is supposed to agree with on everything
Every there's a hundred percent agreement. Oh, no, they're not
That's what a cult is is trying to make everybody fucking think the same thing, right?
That's what I'm saying. I'm saying it's a hive mind and so with it
So when people go into that they they give up some of their sovereignty
Like it is an eighth and then they call other people sheep when they're actually following in a car. It's ridiculous. Okay. Anyway, it's fine
I'm more of a stigma of personality, I think, where it's like I'm just like playing the game alone and and I'm doing okay
I'm enjoying it. It's like, you know, but you know, it's I'm vulnerable because I'm alone
You know and people that are alone is also because I'm nice, but also I've made it this far. I'm like, you know
How do I make it this far anyway? It's like, you know, if I die tomorrow, I still made it this far
So I'm happy. I look way longer than I thought I would ever live. I thought I would live to 30 years old
I always thought that hey, I live now I'm 44 so I'm already like
Like an extra quarter of my age. I thought I live
Hi, babe. Oh
So anyway, I'll be I wasn't even trying to help. I was just talking
You're making me work. You're fucking with my head. Hey. Oh my god, dude
You know what's crazy is if I actually was trying to fuck with your head God knows what I would do
I'm not even doing Jesus
It's crazy as fuck
Damn man, can I motherfucking just be normal without people accusing him of doing some weird shit
No, no, right
All right, it's like you look you look relaxed man, I'm gonna I'm gonna leave you to your channel
I got I got shit to do
Thank you for not being a piece of shit to me, okay
Okay, well, I'm not I try not to be to anybody. I just to be like a full person, but thank you. Okay. Peace
Hi, babe
You guys you see him, okay, like he's so cute
Oh, oh, he's looking at my nose you look at my nose
So cute hey, baby
Hurrying
It's a good cat
It's such a good kitty cat. Hi tricks. Hi tricks. Oh, you can see him. I'm sorry. Thank you for good. Thank you guys
here he is
Okay, it's kind of been putting other people's pictures in JT's profile picture. Okay, so
Wait, what's that? Okay. Yeah, don't want to load here with a good board split. Yeah, there's a fun innocent
rift by psyche
Guys, I printed that on AI. That's why I did it in the games. You know the AI wrote that script, you know
I have no imagination or anything. But anyway
No, I do even even
Guys, I mean, it's like there's people like there's there's people right
There's a writer on the writer department that will have the concept and then the writers will write about the concept
But he'll have the concept. So that's basically what AI is. It's like you're pretty a concept in and so
I don't know, it's like, it's not like, I'm just like,
I'm like some robot, it's like programming a robot
to like give a robotic thing.
It's like, that's why I think some of the AI is pretty good,
but it's like, I'm not saying I'm,
I'm not fucking making it, it's like, I'm just prompting it.
I'm just, I'm inputting some instructions,
directing how it, the output, okay?
So they get good answers, okay?
So thank you. Yeah, I wish yeah, I wish I wish some things were scripts. I guess I don't I never get the scripts in the mail
I set the improv, right?
Okay, hi, baby. This is Mr. Chris. He was just walking out. Hey. Hi.
Praying. You purring?
Yeah, yes monkey. Got me. This is really cool. He was a cat. This is you guys. Yes, you get you this is great. You're just this
Oh, he's so good. I love this kitty cat. Hi
So sweet
Hi, let's say hi to the chatty chat
Hi
They can get miserable people like whoop would I have him kiss up to just be allowed to hang around. It's just super power
He doesn't have to get this gets up to me. That's why I don't I don't want people to kiss up to me. You know, it's like
Gosh
I mean
I can't look like the green I can't look so much like the green goblin and not have like 5% troll at least in my blood or something
Yeah, I don't know. I'm like some kind of a little bit of a troll, but it's like just enough to like protect me
That's why that's why I read you tell you all like the stuff I know because a lot of stuff it took me a while to figure out
Yeah, it has been, you know
Several years
I like it's been pretty crazy though, but
That I'm like still like around it's like saying it. No, I'm just believe I'm
I'm blessed and protect this
I wasn't I don't think I'd be here still
That's a close calls
Oh, yeah, yeah, no you didn't you don't you didn't you don't think you did and you did that come on
I don't know how to troll come on. Okay, so I'm gonna read this story. It's called difficult damsels. It says
Not all girls are made of sugar and spice and all things nice
There are girls made of dark lace and witchcraft and a little bit of vice
These are daughters made cloth first and story mad tiger roar and wolf bad
These are women made of terrible tempests and savage storms and the untamed unwanted.
These are damsels made of flawless beardlessness and more made of bravery, more bravery than
knights ever have seen. These are princesses made of valor and poison alike. They're here
to hold court as your queens. Okay, that's that one. Okay. Okay. Come on guys, these are good.
The moral of your story. Oh shit. Okay. Where'd you go?
There's the moral of your story it says
This is how they lie to us love love so selflessly that you can change the world
The truth is brutal if you care this way the world will get you mercilessly and harsher still all of this love
You hold is too selfless. Yes, my dear too selfless exists no matter how much they deny it
You see they have been taught do you have been taught to give too much without wanting anything back?
What no one tells you is that constant sacrifice is designed to keep you clients
It is designed to keep you weak, and one day it will devastate you.
And what good are you to destroy, to anyone, to anything, especially to your own truth?
Okay, this one's called charming. Okay, you like these are good. This is called fierce fairy tales, and they're really cool
It says if you so says charming said if you want to know him watch his mouth
Ignore his see-god eyes
Ignore the fullness of his laugh the air around him is a charade the only thing that cannot lie is his mouth
Mouse are entrances to the soul house inside, and people who do not mean smiles cannot send the joy back to the empty room that is their eyes.
Your parents, your friends are all under his spell. He is charmed personified, compliments galore.
That is what bewitchments looks like. They all defend him when he calls you a whore.
The first night when you wore that top, you've walked on eggshells ever since. And it only got worse from there, didn't it?
He fed from your sadness till you were almost hollow, until all you have is your loneliness and a loan that you can depend on more than family, more than people that once said they would protect you from everything.
No one said everything didn't include part man, part fiends, who wear such angelic masks. His words have slowly become ugly dark bruises on your whole soul, whilst he still makes others laugh.
Everyone has forgotten that Lucifer was beautiful, too, and God's favoritly fell.
He doesn't need to be this way, though, and all the stories of the chosen one is always alone.
He's not the Prince Charming he was supposed to be, and said he turned out to be a demon made of apathy.
He's isolating you from everyone around you, yet he cannot isolate you from yourself,
but he doesn't know your greatest secret, your quietest and greatest strength.
You have Persephone hiding in those bones, Warrior Queen of the Dead, who's been waiting to help.
Remember him, why people say of you,
she wears strength and darkness equally well
if the girl has always been half goddess, half hell.
That's pretty good.
There's one for summer, I'll read that later.
Okay, let's just see.
This one's called Devour Your Monsters.
It says, the world is not allowed to make a,
it's not allowed to make a meal of you, girl.
If it is there for your consuming,
first you devour and spit out the bones of the men
who try to turn you into a punching bag.
Second, you eat the kings that try to lock you up
as gifts for princes.
Then you spit out the bones of princes who try to turn you
into a good docile, faithful little wife.
Then you reject every person who chides you
about your obligations and your duties to men
before your duties and responsibilities to yourself.
the castle doors and walk alone into your beautifully crafted sunset.
Wow.
How about this one? This one's called How to Save Yourself and it says,
Understand this first. No one is coming to catch you. That misery belongs to you first and no one
else wants any part in that. Might as well start breaking your way out of your tower. Might as well
trick the vines to help you. Might as well turn your own hair into a ladder. Turn yourself into
a rope and find your way down, down into the aspen grove. The trees have always been your friends.
More than tower walls or saviors ever were. If you ask them kindly enough, I'm sure they'll
You may even suddenly find your wings instead.
You will never know until like Icarus, you risk the fall.
Easy's not up, he's not up here.
But I would.
Okay.
So how about this one?
You guys like these?
I like these a lot, it's not a cool, okay?
He says, for all our hidden wishes, that night after the last betrayal, I reached inside
and pulled the grief from my belly, stared at the dark things that all these people had
done to me.
We told myself that there is still a God that resides within me.
Something softer than what the mirror lets me see.
that some which ancestry in me is still left, a few potions still within this heart, to
punish without mercy those who have given me lies.
They tried so hard to end me with words, took their time and poisoned every friend I had
in the sport in place, no home to me, but still my fate.
So too I open my lips and let out a curse to refrain, the curse being formed not from
magic but pain.
Let me live this life better than my enemies.
It has taken some time to learn that although karma exists, you can let your hatred go,
not by destroying your own magic, but by letting it grow.
Okay, there's one more I'll happily ever after I was never talked graceful love until I met you and found my heart in sync with yours
You helped me build a happily ever after and made me believe in my own souls core
Thank you for opening your souls to me my sisters when all others were closed doors
Thank you for loving me when I still tasted of heartache and war
Baby don't hurt me don't hurt me no more
Bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum,
I do love you guys. I love you guys so much having fun having fun. No, it's freaky Friday guys. I don't know
Let's get freaky. I don't know. How are we freaky yet? I have a whole beard. I mean Frederick doesn't want sip
What's the link you want to come upstairs when I come upstairs?
Thanks about pins like I'm up sick give your ass up here like
Guatemala and hunk
Whatever you are the moment while I'm all in. What am I drinking hard lemonade harder lemonade?
Yeah, I'm having Coca-Cola
I'm in the 90s. I was you know, I'm 1981 so out my senior prom. I think yeah senior prom. I was at a club
You're not in the mood for
For
I can't read any what but but I have no vision. Where's my glasses here. I
Have now the mute a fair warning say okay, she's on the mood say
These are good
I'm never gonna get sick food on say
I'm never gonna say he's a he's not a bad he's a nice guy
A lick of a lick of boom-boom down. Just shake your running. I want to shake your rump. That's not that's one
Okay, hi, did I do that? Hey region team. No, I meant say to you now. Yes. Yes. I'm not in the movies. Yes
say
Just bear warning. Say if you say what went around there
Say what you want
Say la how's that black eyed T song go
Six second be there gonna have a freak off. Oh, that'd be interesting
What do I got here, okay
Sweet he likes honey like I can't a driver remind me honey never expires but
I think it's just crystalized.
Okay, I
Seriously have some of the best books in the world
But I've 10,000 of them and so it's kind of hard to find like the right one at the right time, right?
I do I do believe I will
Okay, boomer, let me see if they will open, open some of these, I don't know if they will open.
See, it kind of sounds funny.
Okay, oh, I read it, that's a good sign.
Okay, it's kind of stupid.
Like it's describing the boomers from like 10. I think this book must be like 10 years old
And it's describing boomers for like 10 years ago. I think that
Boomers have funny
Okay
So we're gonna see you guys to come up and then you don't come up see I mean, what are you gonna do?
Okay, so you guys liked the Twilight Zone, though.
The Twilight Zone has a really good episode
called Talking Tina, and it's about this doll.
And it starts like talking to this step dad.
I'm like saying, I don't like you.
You're gone in a bit, okay.
And then he would try to destroy the doll, but he couldn't.
It was just like, he would try to cut off its head,
and it was like, it couldn't,
like it wouldn't cut through the fender.
It was like, and then it's really good.
Yeah, it's a really good episode.
I love highlights and I used to watch all those old ones and I watched tales from the dark side. I watched
The outer limits I watched. Yeah, and I loved all that. I love their tales from the crypts
Eve show
Okay, let's see
I have some funny books
It's a matter of finding something
Some books are just like too a lot of stuff. I don't really want to discuss on this show because I don't even think people are
I don't know. It would be a lot for people. What is it? A battle for brains. Okay, this sounds good.
A battle for your brain. So where is this book from?
Okay
Okay, so this book looks like it's actually by some paranoid person
I'll see if there's anything good in that though.
Okay.
Do you believe in like frequencies?
I'm not taking, I'm not making a biscuit emoji
unless you're...
It's like I found it by it follows it on the biscuit joke. I'd be so down to make a emoji for that
I only have 13 emojis to make and
Maybe
And the biscuit seems like a free free like lame thing to put on it, but I put a cinnabon
cinnabon
No, I can cheese it nasty on some pans actually big fucking cheese and pasta. So it tastes good if you put it in the right, right?
Right mixture of it, right?
Don't make it here. Oh, yeah, you can just make your cooking glass. I use the I use the pre-cut
pills very
Ones, right?
Okay, I
Don't know
Okay, okay, so yeah, this I guess the person that wrote this book was a
Apparently a little paranoid she's like everything was some kind of thing
Yeah, this is a good list like
coughing clearing throat sneezing fake laughing hitting see fake laughing someone was like fake laughing and it was like
Striving nuts being objects with their hands or feet multiple people playing the same song on their phone. Yeah
There's always somebody and these jails are in conversation with you. That's the person that who pushed you in the slope kill program. Okay. Wow
That's kind of scary, okay
There's like a street theater. So street theater is something that I've experienced
Okay, so it's like people are like, oh street theater. What is this? Okay? I know theater, right?
So the street theater is any premeditated harassment that takes place in a public setting
Ranging from dumbfounding these stupid and simple to the elaborate sophisticated plan
of deafening was not worth it, as leaving dead, dying animals and targets, paths, squirrels,
rats, mice, dogs, birds, dogs, leaving small feathers and targets path repeatedly, saying
first or last names of family members, close friends, loud and public within earshot, strangers
saying targets in the public, crowding stores, shops after you arrive, causing delays of
checkout lines, preoccupying employees with stupid questions, paying for items with copious
amounts of change.
Having cats, dogs, children suddenly run into the road as they drive by, couples fighting in public with loud abusive language, younger males cursing, speeding using vulgar language, people talking about severe AB USC and aliving drug abuse in front of Target, people premeditate, pretending to smoke hard drugs in front of them, people breaking down and crying, sobbing in front of them, same time entry exit.
Insulting comments about body, hairstyle, peer, and social-skilled intelligence level
often sit in front of a group of people, including the ignored by retail staff, using artificial
telepathy to block target plans to buy the store.
Well, that's a little bit crazy.
Using directed conversations to humiliate target and public, experiencing these types
of harassment on a daily basis for years can lead to PCSE, nervous breakdowns, complete
Analyzing what's the purpose of the accomplished complete dehumanization destruction of the target target is playing for all their own problems and the first walkways got free
Okay, go ahead
This is the gravy. Yeah, I know it. I do know what gravy means. Okay, so
sabotaging the target's reputation and that goes with the ability to earn a living business
of personal relationships in a very special operations category. Newer community-based
agents will not be assigned to engineer the method, but will assist in passing rumors,
which are the main means of destroying a target's public image. Rumors consist mainly of lies,
however, in order to secure cooperation as specific members of the community participate
in the punishment phase. Additional information keyed to appeal to the patriotic or community
As mentioned earlier, the organization has many top psychologists and psychiatrists on permanent staff at headquarters, some in larger population centers.
It's their responsibility to design the campaign to destroy the target's reputation.
These people listed below can be approached and given information.
Oh, so it says business contacts, supervisors, coworkers, casual social contacts, friends, local fraternal organizations, store staff.
target landlord, target neighbors, tradesmen who are likely to serve as the target's home car business,
city employees, family members, surprisingly many are ready to believe negative information, especially personnel.
At places the target applies to or work, sabotage their reputation.
Okay, ruining relationships, isolation.
Loneliness can be damaging to both our mental and physical health.
Socially isolated people are less able to deal with stressful situations.
They're also more likely to feel depressed and may have problems processing information.
This can in turn lead to difficulties with decision making and memory storage and recall.
People who are lonely are also more susceptible to illness.
Researchers found that a lonely person's immune system responds differently to fighting viruses,
making them more likely to develop an illness.
I mean, a lot of people get a bunch of worse than I've ever done, so it's like, there are, you know,
there's also color harassment,
color harassment, bicycle harassment, pedestrian harassment, number harassment,
or the same numbers, yeah, extortion, death threats, RAPE intimidation, color harassment,
there's technology, it gets scary.
All the patents, they show all the patents of actually things, and then they show all the codes, criminal codes, espionage, court cases, interesting.
Do not tips. Do gather evidence, pictures, call recordings, voice recordings, text messages, emails, mail, screen, screenshots.
I would say collect evidence, but they don't, just collect everything. They collect actual evidence, like actually like something, not just like everything.
I don't, I like the, like, I like the best thing, but I have to have the frosting on it, because I'm just making it seminal, right?
Because it keeps multiple copies of your evidence online offline and inform people about
technologies, hold on.
Social media block, everyone harassing you.
Share resources.
Do not, do not buy, do not stay quiet, do not believe everything you read online, do not overreact, do not give up hope, do not, I'm alive.
Also, a lot of stuff is put out by the perpetrators, right?
So there's stuff that is like, it's a little bit of all this stuff.
You have to be careful with what you assume is entertainment.
I'm doubting it.
I bet we can get the couple on the panel for a couple hundred dollars.
Wow.
Let's see who gets the couple.
What
What are they called they're called a why don't you
I said biscuit that's what came up
Sir I'm streaming to 40 people on YouTube I know
I was like, I was like, how does that work?
I was like, well, if I have no, nobody in the chat,
if I have nobody, I don't talk to anybody, obviously.
Well, might as well just like not, right?
Unless you guys, if you guys want to have that,
that would be truly parasocial.
I don't want to like be parasocial.
I don't want to just do like pre-recorded things,
like talking to you.
I want to like talk to you, with you, you know.
to each other, not just like, talk at you.
I'm not insulting you, I just typed biscuit and that came up.
Maybe it's a chocolate chip biscuit.
Have you ever thought of that?
Oh, Limp Bizkit, I like Limp Bizkit.
I think Fred Durst is pretty cute.
That what he's talking about?
Yeah, I can do a song in the Limp Bizkit.
Tell them about the he said, she said bullshit.
Okay.
They're adding to harm. Okay. Yeah, that's what oh, yeah
The evidence into this this is interesting about triggers
That's blasphemy
Why are you promoting other cults in my in my my chat chat?
The triggers are part of a behavior modification program called NLP, Neuro-Linguistic Programming,
which uses anchors and triggers to promote change.
An anchor is created when an emotional state is linked to something such as an object, person, sound, smell, place, color.
Whatever the individual was exposed to during the anchoring process becomes the stimulus,
a trigger that will provoke the emotion, which is basically Pavlov's dog kind of stuff where it's
like they can do with this conditioned response to certain stimulus. So it was the bell in the
Pavlov's dog and they would salivate because they were used to like being fed food when they were
reading the bell. But then they would just ring the bell and then it would start salivating before
So it says, write down the anchoring, words, numbers, colors, phrases, objects, document,
everything online.
Remember, this has been repeatedly, has been repeatedly, otherwise the whole program would
be useless.
Repetition is what makes it easy to be explained and proven.
Okay.
That's basically it from that book, I think.
I don't want to fuck with anything. Stop it. Don't put it. It's all over talking about biscuits, you know
It's like and again, it's one of those stupid like inside jokes that I'm no part of
Okay
I'm on the outside I'm looking at
I'm cranking if people are constantly picking at me.
It's like, oh, what did they think about this?
I just read, oh, no, let's just talk
about biscuits all morning.
It's an interesting book.
I wasn't interested in this book, hold on, I'll show you the cover.
Okay, go ahead, Armin.
Okay, they're about to ban the... hold on.
Okay, and who cleared the guys someone cleared out the dark the their bandwars stop that
That is not to be messed with
Okay, now I have a rogue mod the fuck who is it I'm gonna have to unmod everybody again. What the hell?
This is good. Oh, no one's doing anything wrong
I'm saying it is wrong. I was saying somebody deleted the block words list somebody deleted all the words on it
Which is weird
Hold on that's good. Hey summer. Yeah, I know manage it. Yeah, I know I know
No more mods and I might just make them all
Regular mods
What are you doing, guys?
Okay.
I'm sorry.
You were trying to make me laugh?
I don't know.
It's okay, no, no, you're fine, you're fine.
Oh, come on, Sweepie, don't be so offended.
I have no idea, Sweepie, please, you have little Debbie's.
profile photo. I mean, it's like, I don't know what to say. It's just pretty strange. It's like,
don't be mad at me. It's okay. It's like, you know, it's like when people start harping on stuff.
Much trust much how people get mad at me. I'm just I'm trying to make it mad. I'm just
Trying to entertain
No, I think you're very nice, I'm sorry, I'm just sure I'm fucking you know, I'm sorry from snippy
Trying to calm myself down I can't
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I don't need a nap on the end.
I still have this whole beer left.
I don't have a problem. I'm sorry. I told you I'm just being a dick. I'm just a dick. I'm sorry
Wow, that is kind of strong
Hi, I just want to apologize about the biscuits
It's okay. It's okay. You don't have to do that to your hair. It's just a biscuit. What's the point?
It's like I know I know the point is this like I should I'm not it's like now it looks like I'm triggered by the biscuit
It's not but it's just like it's just like you're like he's saying it's a
Okay, if it's a taco, but it's a biscuit, but what is it?
I don't I don't want tacos anymore. You guys ruin. What do you want? What do you want to steak?
I don't want to eat anything else the food is disgusting to me. I'll just shut up in the chat
You know what I really I want is a bag of cheetos. I just went a bag of okay everybody everybody cheetos
Cheeto puffy ones or the spicy. I know I went I like I like the coffee. I do like the coffee ones
But I like to like I like all of them
I like the I just like even like and I like to the Doritos talk is they're good to the one the Doritos taco show
You're acting like a pregnant lady today
You just want some kind of
Kool-aid tickles can you get someone give me Kool-aid tickles, please? That's what I want
They collated they put in the pickles and then it pickles like the pickles with the kool-aid and they turn in different colors
And they taste like fruit
That I really like sweet pickles, but yeah, this is popular in the south right now. I heard you guys tried that I
Like I love the big I love the I love the puffy ones. Have you ever heard of it? Okay?
I just recently tried fried pickles like a year ago. I didn't even know there is like such thing as fried pickles
They're good. Yeah, delicious. I mean, yeah, but I just take little ones as like pickled eggs
They have these eggs or that fleet base or fleets in a downtown LA. There's purple pickled eggs. They're so good
They're like, um, I would always have one there. They would go purple all the way through
So we can talk about chicken feed all of that, but no biscuits
No, no business. Well chicken feet is fine. That's it's even boo-doo. They're not really good to eat
Yeah, they use chicken feet a lot in Goodyoo and stuff. Also, I have a Bobby Yaga house that has chicken feet. It has on chicken legs.
She's a Russian witch.
Yeah, she's a Russian witch. Yeah, he's her forever.
Okay, so let's see. I'm looking for something to entertain people with, but I need to prepare more, I know, for the show.
You're already entertaining us. You're pretty funny today.
I am okay. Yeah, you just being a little bitch. He is entertaining. I don't know. We're just teasing you
Okay, good
Good. I want to send you that song taste of biscuit every day until you listen to it every morning
I've I think I heard this
All this yeah, I've already heard a song called biscuit and then it's like
It's not biscuit is taste of biscuits
Okay, well, I've been that word is now banned in my chat. So
It's not gonna be said anywhere in my chat. Okay, you have to be like this tweets like French style. I
Spelled it like that. I put that into the fireworks. Yeah, I felt like ten on different ways
I think of different ways to spell biscuits so I could take them off
Okay, I won't say that anymore. I'm sorry. Okay. It's okay. It's okay. It's like, you know, it's like you're like, you know, you're
Hotkiss makes really good biscuits. I heard
Did she make good hot pockets that I would that would be nice to everything. Hi pie. I
want to try
I want to try pot hawk is hot pockets. Can you say that three times fast? Please? I want to try pot hawk is hot pockets
I want to try pot hawk is hot pockets. I want to try pot hawk is hot pockets
That way pretty good. Yeah, you did perfect. Okay. You I want you to say taste the biscuit three times
Okay, taste the beta taste the beta taste the beta. Oh
That is a that is a it's under wrong
No, no
Okay, okay, I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm being mean
It's taste of brisket taste of brisket taste of brisket
Okay, so brisket is okay, but biscuits are not all right. We got that no more you guys
No, as long as I can I have like you send me can someone just sending biscuits to the house like with gravy
I like the like the KFC like those are good biscuits, you know, yeah
Yeah
That's and that's all and I like the ones I'm Thanksgiving is there a frog invasion. I don't know check out the video
What's it called Dorian Dorian Electra?
calls
My my intention my intention and it's about the frogs turning gay watch it my intention
No
We can't say the beat this kid word anymore. We can say anything
Taste the pot I can't taste the pot
You spelled it a different way. You can use you could have spelled it that way. I still at BISU IT
I know
I was kidding. You know, I don't care if you'll promote other channels here
Yeah, I don't think I've ever in my life
I've been on YouTube ever not let somebody like post a link or I don't like to take anything down ever is like
I'm fine. You guys see men. Do you guys see my new friends? I do have a new friend here
Let's see. Oh
That's cute. Oh
My god, it's an alien holding a little kitty. I
love that
Hi, be there
Is that me?
Oh, I met me that I guess. Oh, that's so cute
Kitty loves it too
Guys unless you're like sit and send me like a basket of biscuits. Don't talk about them
I don't want to just hear like about it. Oh, yes, it's just Bunky got me
Yeah, look up on Amazon. They could look up the alien. They have these really cute alien neon stuff
There's other ones too. It was I really
Love that and thank you so much spunky. That's so cute. Do you like that guy? Yeah, it's so that's funky
Yes, oh my gosh, she's so adorable. I love it. It's so cute
Perfect. I think you should try to put it somewhere. Well, you have a curtain back there
But when you're you know, maybe on your wall, so it's
They brought like they come with like screws right there, and then it comes with like a chain and then it came with
I came with
This hook thing so it's like I think you stick this to the oh hang it there. Okay. That's cool
You can't I think you pick this to the the neon thing
I'm just afraid it will fall and it's like I'm gonna put it in the best place, but I love it
I think I put it on this wall right here. I
Like it. Thank you. Thank you
Uh, we need to find the rogue. I don't know. I think that I did like
I'm modern Goddard than I'm very modern him. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know the rogue is
It's okay. It's fine. I don't care if it's cleared out. It's like what is it piranha? Is that the song taste of biscuit?
I mean a taste of the bread. Don't look at this. Don't look at this. Well, don't look at it. I don't know
What is it? What is it? Don't say don't look at this in the poster. That's probably about biscuits or something. Okay
Is that a self-portrait? What is it? Oh, it's her. She drew a self-portrait. Okay. Oh, okay. Okay. I'm gonna go check it out
Well, anyways, I came up here to tell you I'm sorry
We're not laughing at you we're laughing with you
I know you're a troll and you're scripted in and it's fun or maybe you're not I don't know we'll never know
I'm probably dumber than I look or maybe more smart. I don't know
if you're smarter or dumber. Are you gonna be smarter or dumber than I look? One of the two, guaranteed.
But I probably looked dumb and then I...
But you don't look dumb.
Sometimes I act dumb sometimes I am dumb, but I also have a good... I think you're just a good actor.
I love you. I thank you so much. I love you too, sweetheart.
I'll be back later. Have a good day. Mwah. Okay, you too. Talk to you soon. Bye.
Yeah, but it's hypocrisy. No one here was big. That's okay. Oh
Bandlist and all that it's thank you to work. Yeah
Yeah, I don't know like I guess because there's the ability, you know people will
Use it but
Yeah, I prefer if I put worse my band less because you know and I had like
Hundreds of words on her banlist you had hundreds of words because people would say vagina or they'd say all kinds of like other you know
Sexual things and stuff like that for her, right? So that was kind of like
That's how I like learned about the banlist that was like her mod so
And Paul went to hell so it might be a bunch of joking you see fun to joke in here. Oh sweet. He's still fun
Thanks. Just make fun of me
and then you should be happy.
I'm fairly, I'm fairly, very fun to troll, okay?
Let's go ahead and do it.
It's fine.
As a chatterer, the only chatterer in YouTube chat
is possible to see location.
I don't think so. I've never seen it, but I mean anything's possible. I suppose like there could be like some kind of like app
That does that or there could be some kind of thing I've missed in the back room or something
But I've never heard of such a thing
I would not know but
Perhaps perhaps perhaps
Okay
Who once said now someone shout out your your sign who ever says who the first person to shout out their sign
I will read about your your sign the dark side of your sign. It's called born on a rotten day. It's a really good book
Hey, sweetie, sweetie. I'm just kidding. Okay, sweetie. I love you. You're awesome person. Please. Just be my friend
Don't don't please. There's no stress right now. So now don't be mad. He's too much stress. Okay. Oh
She admitted it
Virgo, oh, okay. We said we said scorpion. Okay, so I think I read someone's Scorpio, but I'll read someone's Scorpio and then I'll read
Some of Virgo, okay. Yeah, because I think I've read some of I just take a little bit of each of those, but not the main part
These Scorpio then Virgo and then
we'll see if
You guys want to hear any more of that?
Because this is really a
good one
Scorpios are super interesting
Okay, so the book is called, okay, so, so Scorpio.
Okay, so Scorpio, there's a pirate flag, picture of a pirate flag, it says Scorpio.
It says, let the games begin, elements, water, Scorpio is a bottomless, roiling paradox.
Fall in without protective armor and you'll come out a skeleton.
Quality fixed, Scorpios, never forget, forgive, or let go.
Symbol, just as its crusty little namesake, the human version will destroy itself trying
to get revenge.
Ruler, Pluto and Mars, suspicious hothead, compulsive, obsessive two-timer, favorite
pastime, plodding their next move, favorite book, the Klingon Guide to Mercy, role model,
the mass avenger, dream job, judge, jury, and lord high executioner.
Key phrase, I'll get you for that.
body parts, sex organs, a terminal case of seven-year itch that scratches frequently.
Approach with caution. Scorpio, the ape sign of the zodiac, lives in a house of death, sex, and other people's possessions.
Conventional astrology describes Scorpio as an intense mysterious, sensual creature with a gift of regeneration, the phoenix rising from the ashes.
Make that Dracula rising from its coffin. Rotten Scorpios are obsessed
Selfie, corporal control freaks who replenish their egos at everyone else's expense.
Scorpio has two ruling planets, Mars, the God of Conflict and Aggression, which shows
a prime, suspicious character.
That friendly surface is separated from boiling miasma of emotion by only a couple layers
of very thin skin.
Pluto, the God of Extremes, instills an unmatched instinct for survival.
Wooden stakes, holy water, or a stretch in the pen, nothing could harm Scorpio but Scorpio
itself.
Scorpio's favorite game is Kangaroo Court.
They subscribe to the Salem Witch Trial version of Justice, die in your innocence, live in
your guilty.
Feel free to ignore yours as you would a perpetual teenager.
He or she will bite his or her own foot while a while, then curl up at the nearest dark
quarter and go to sleep.
Scorpios are extreme, not rational.
They view life as either black or white and rarely compromised.
Being born with the all-or-nothing gene has voided their ability to form lasting relationships with anyone who refuses to submit to their control.
Argue with one and suffer a verbal beating that makes you wish they had slugged you instead.
Prove your point and they will give themselves an ulcer trying to get even.
Never give up and never under any circumstances face the facts. That's Ruth Gordon October 30th
Why is your life so difficult because you are still repaying the bad karma you earned in the last go-round when you were
Tokamata's rackmaster during the Inquisition you
Exaggerated nature provides extremes of every kind
compulsions and obsessions
Explode within your psyche a startling a large number of you either become geniuses or sink into the lowest depths of depravity
You ladder types make ideal mates for Pisces
Your favorite TV shows are reruns of Dark Shadows and you wear a Barnabas Collins ring
on your forefinger.
You love to point randomly at unsuspecting strangers and mumble gibberish.
Your moods range from irritable to pissed off and you frequently silk, brood, intimidate,
spy, and cheat.
That's all on one of your good days.
Unlike Taurus, who's blind to his faults, you're actually aware of your flaws but excessively
proud of them.
Being a fixed sign means that your emotions and opinions rarely change. You are rarely described as a as you are kindly described as steel waters run deep
You're more closely resemble a boiling cesspool of hydrochloric acid your metaphorical
Stinger is always pointed for attack, points for attack, and you are supposedly known for vicious verbal barbs.
In reality, most of you are merely cantankerous boars who constantly posture and gouge lines in the dirt of daring others to step across.
You're a private...
Even your relatives don't know your unlisted phone number.
You have a no solicitor sign on the barbed wire fence around your property.
Anyone attempting to reach your front door will need a map and a flashlight to make it through the overgrowth.
You're so paranoid that you think Alcatraz would be a safe place to live.
Scorpios have bumper stickers that say things like,
my child sells drugs to your honor student.
You are chronically cursed.
Have a badass son of the badass and mother of badass tattooed on your neck.
You have a police scanner on the kitchen table to track movements of your friends,
both of them. Instead of family pictures, your refrigerator is covered with magnetic business
cards of lawyers, therapists, and bail bondsmen. Inside is a mini-asma, mismatched a variety
ranging from mashed potatoes to granola bars. Your eating habits swing as wildly as your
Scorpio is a sign of prostituting attorney, psychopaths, mafia negotiator, and more parts
than you are prepared to lose a surgeon.
Scorpio has also made good stalkers, astrologers, and psychics.
However, very few of you are in the latter profession because you refuse to acknowledge
your clairvoyance.
Your fellow Scorpio Adam Antz views on sex.
He said, I like sex.
My songs are about sex.
Sex is my life.
I find it the most exhilarating experience, and I think it should be done on stage.
You're the most intense of all signs, telling you to learn to go with the flow or to lighten
up.
It's ridiculous.
Control is your forte.
Learn to use it on yourself before running over your children, friends, and lovers with
your steel-belted emotions.
You'll quickly discover that most people like to be around you because of the sheer force
of your personality.
Is it good?
When angered, you choose to slay every sign walking with alarming ease.
Earth signs fell like dolmenos before you.
Nervous Virgos won't survive one round if you're not so subtle sarcasm.
Capricorn and Taurus may try to intimate or bellow,
but wither under the intense tell-it-like-it-is sessions.
You're easily drive air signs Gemini Aquarius out of their minds with
frustrated fury and the first of suggested improvements,
Lieberhand, you will find his way right up to pointy little nose.
You're well chosen sarcasm, staying worse than any lion's claw.
You quash steered serious armchair philosophy with one or two brutal facts of life, and
Aries Childish's angst is no match for your verbal stinger.
You and the other water science cancer and Pisces understand each other on a soul level.
Your philosophy is mind-drown business. You are guided by instinct and driven by passion.
Let the rest of the world spend a time on frivolous pursuits and TV games shows you are too busy, quietly forging a solid-goal future.
Years from now,
when your ex-lovers and other strangers are playing shuffleboard and remembering sex with a nostalgia,
sigh, you can send them pictures of yourself, one hand squeezing the bottom of your 20-something sweetheart,
the other accepting the reward for the sexiest senior citizen in Rio.
Figured moist. Oh moist is a terrible word. Yeah, moist is one of the bad ones moist like you know moist critical
Moist is just like it sounds like it reminds me of like a wet vagina. Isn't it kind of like I don't know it's weird
They're always kind of like wet. It's like
I don't know. It's kind of
It's cool. Okay, welcome. Okay, so we'll do a Virgo next
Okay, I'm sorry I'm just
We're doing Virgo? Okay, let's look at Virgo.
Oliver, I know what Oliver likes to eat for dinner. It's a hair pie.
Okay, so it says Virgo.
Virgo, everlasting, know it all, need love to, element earth.
Virgo earth is a solid parcel of common soil that provides everything you need in a predictable manner.
As predictable as Burmese grass, mow it, water it, mow it, water it.
Quality, mutable, Virgo moves swing from nitpicker to crank to critic, symbol the version in your
dreams and their minds, in their dreams and their minds. Ruler, Mercury, the god of telling it like
it is, whether or not you want to hear it. Favorite pastime, worrying. Favorite book, 100,
2001 steps to total organization, Rolex role model, Felix Unger, dream job, closet organizer,
nervous system. You can always port Virgo by their raw bleeding fingernails.
Approach with caution. Virgo, the sixth son of the Zodiac, lives in the house of
service and health. Tactical astrology depicts Virgo as modest. Practical
peach of a person who's superbly logical, discriminating, and meticulous. A more
accurate description might reveal an anal, subjective, self-absorbed, thus budget
bucket, thus budget, who's critical, and sanctimonious, and cheap.
Virgo is ruled by Mercury, the same breezy character that rules pesky Gemini.
However, in Virgo, Mercury's mischievous, light-hearted nature is trapped in Earth,
where it becomes critical and irritable.
Virgos would like to be as unstructured as Cousin Gemini, but their feet are sucked firmly
into the ground.
Virgins sweat the small stuff.
These folks are compelled to heal the sick, save the sinful, and correct everyone who's
else's spelling.
They dispense unsolicited advice with the authority of a second grade teacher and about
as much insight.
Virgos are deliberate, not spontaneous. They are so busy trying to perfect everyone else.
They have lost sight of their own flawed natures. Of all the signs, Virgo is least likely to admit
a mistake. For with the nothings ever good enough, Jean has made them unable to relax and enjoy life
surprises. Bring your lunch and dinner if you dare argue with one, because they will never admit
they are wrong. Prove a Virgo version wrong, and he or she will say, oh, I didn't realize that.
Well, that changes the whole perspective. And if you would only explain it to me,
Then it goes
If you're a poor one
I'll just read a few paragraphs. It says,
If you're born one, rotten, don't get mad, get even.
You have one belief. Everyone in life is beneath you.
There is an idea that you can't improve upon, or a person you can't whip into shape.
You may pride yourself in being a discriminating perfectionist,
but everyone else sees you as a royal pain in the ass.
You're very intelligent, but can't make any practical use of your knowledge,
so you end up spouting platitudes and pumping gas.
You have the force for the tree syndrome, you are so bogged down in the excruciating
minutiae of daily life that you let the world and your dreams pass by.
But that's okay with you since it gives you the reason to blame your faults on everyone
but yourself.
Yours is a sign of the scribe, prosecuting attorney, mimic, despot, and anything with
critic in the title.
Burgos make excellent bureaucrats because they love to make people stand for hours in line
that go nowhere.
You spend your life moving your metaphorical piles of dirty laundry from one side of your psyche to the other without resolving anything.
However, this is fine with you because it gives you something to do on Saturday night besides rearranging your medicine captain.
You're so concerned with your health that you rattle when you walk from the pill bottle
ziggling in your pocket or purse.
Your home serves as the satellite pharmacy for the neighborhood and you're lightened
dispensing the latest holistic advice on every ailment from boils to constipation.
You're the type of patient who hounds your doctor for double prescriptions just to be
prepared.
Is that good?
Hold on.
Your favorite game is mountains out of molehills, and you have sets over things that will never
happen.
You spend hours worrying whether or not you should use milk that's one day past and
a pool day, and your tires have enough air to get you to your next sentence appointment.
You are in the only one sentence zodiac that looks forward to a tooth cleaning.
You have more systems for coping with life than the IRS has for tracking down tax dodgers.
In life you are a romantic as a top sergeant.
During the troops you expect your lover to adhere to your timetable and preference for
and bulk at any variation.
As you invariably get dumped, you cry for,
hold on, what's going on in chat guys?
What's wrong?
It's okay, but I don't know what's going on.
Is there a reason?
It's okay, I mean, it's okay guys.
I don't know what's going on.
Who is she hiding or she just?
You don't like your free for you're paying free porn pie don't put for you for it
Why are you posting for you for report in the chat pie? I don't post more in the chat
Hi
You came in try to turn it to go hot hot good hi, how do you do me like this?
Pi, did you delete the words too?
Can you unhider? Is it possible? Let me see if I can.
Okay, Pi, you're not supposed to do that. Okay, I'm closing down this slide. Okay.